<POLICY modification_date="" policy_url="http://www.kia.com/us/en/content/privacy-and-legal/privacy-policy" website_category="Recreation" website_index="096" website_url="kia.com">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>Maintaining the privacy of your information is important to Kia Motors America (“Kia”).  This Privacy Policy describes Kia's current corporate policy on how we use the personally identifiable information (“personal information”) that you provide to Kia both online and offline through postal mail, contest submissions, telephone requests, surveys, etc or to Kia dealers who then transfer the personal information to Kia.  You should read the entire policy carefully.  By continuing to use Kia websites or by providing Kia with your personal information through a website or through off-line methods, you consent to this Privacy Policy.

On occasion, Kia may revise this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in the law, Kia's privacy practices, or the features on Kia websites. If any such changes impact the way we collect or use your information, those changes will be posted in this Privacy Policy and the effective date will be noted. Therefore, you should review the Privacy Policy periodically to remain aware of Kia's current policies and practices.  If Kia materially changes its practices regarding collection or use of personal information, your personal information will continue to be governed by the Policy under which it was collected unless you have been provided notice of, and have not objected to, the change.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Who We Are</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>As used in this Privacy Policy, the terms “we” and “us” mean Kia and its subsidiaries.  We produce passenger cars, vans, cargo trucks, parts and accessories.

Our “dealers” and “licensees” are independent companies that sell our vehicles, parts and accessories and are licensed to operate such businesses using a trade name, trademarks, and service marks owned by us.  “Business partners” are independent companies that Kia has partnered with to provide you with or offer you other services and products.

Because this Privacy Policy sets forth only Kia's privacy practices, this Policy does not describe the privacy practices of our dealers, licensees, or business partners even when you link to their websites through Kia websites or provide them information offline through written or telephonic means if your personal information is not then provided to Kia.  Your linking to other sites or providing personal information to other companies through written or telephone communications is at your own risk and is not governed by the Kia Privacy Policy, even where those websites or companies' offline communications are co-branded with the Kia logo.  To learn about the privacy practices of any of Kia dealers, licensees, or business partners that link to Kia websites or that contact you through written or telephonic means, you should review the privacy policies of those entities, and not this Privacy Policy, which only applies to the information collected by Kia, from Kia.com, other Kia websites, Kia events, Kia email, Kia written and telephone communications and other means that Kia may use including when you purchase a car from a dealer and your personal information is shared by the dealer to Kia. We recommend that you always check the applicable privacy statement of non-Kia sites and companies requesting information before providing any personal information.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Collection of Personal Information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>This Privacy Policy covers personal information collected from and about you on Kia websites and by Kia through written or telephonic means. Personal information includes information such as name, mailing address, email address, and telephone number, and can also include the type of request, and any additional information you provide to Kia.  The information you provide is used by Kia to notify you about, and improve upon, the services that we provide to you.

In addition to personal information, Kia collects IP address, aggregate user data, and browser type.  This data is used to manage and improve Kia.com and other Kia websites, track usage, improve services, and for security and monitoring purposes.  Kia's websites are for general audiences, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Use and Disclosure of Personal Information and Your Choices</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We may use your personal information for a variety of purposes as described in this Privacy Policy.  If you do not want us to disclose information in this manner, do not submit your personal information to us.

Kia will not use your personal information for purposes that are different from those purposes detailed herein unless we ask for your permission to do so.  In addition, Kia will not share your personal information with third parties who are not affiliated or partnered with us unless you have chosen to receive specific information and the fulfillment of such a request requires the sharing of your personal information.

Disclosure Within Kia and to Kia's Service Providers.  Within Kia, we may share your personal information with Kia employees, agents, and contractors who have a legitimate business reason to obtain access to your personal information.  Kia may share your personal information with outside contractors or agents who help us manage our activities (i.e., mailing list administrators, marketing agents, etc.), but they may only use your personal information to provide Kia with a specific service and not for any other purpose.

Disclosure to Affiliated Parties.  Kia may share your personal information with companies that are affiliated with us such as our dealers, licensees, and/or business partners for the purposes of both marketing and administrative purposes (such as recall notices).

Legal Authorities.  Kia may disclose personal information without providing you with a choice in order to protect Kia's or its affiliated entities' legal rights; to protect the safety and security of visitors to Kia.com and other Kia websites; to protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; or to comply with law or legal process.

Corporate Transactions.  Going forward, we may acquire or sell assets, and companies may acquire financial interests in us.  In connection with those transactions, personal information may be among the transferred business assets, and we may disclose your personal information to any company in connection with a proposed or actual sale, merger, transfer, or exchange of all or a portion of a business or operating unit.  Any such disclosure will be conditioned on that company agreeing to use the data prior to any acquisition solely for the purpose of making its acquisition decision and to observe the relevant provisions of our Privacy Policy with respect to the data.  In the event that personal information is transferred to a company acquiring assets from us, we will require that company to agree to observe the relevant provisions of our Privacy Policy with respect to your personal information (including any choices that you have made under our Privacy Policy to limit the use of your data).

Data Collection from Others.  We may also obtain personal information about you from our dealers, licensees and/or business partners.  We may merge or use that personal information with information that we collected previously, as permitted by applicable law and our Privacy Policy.  That personal information once in Kia's possession is governed by this Privacy Policy.

Disclosure to Other Non-Affiliated Third Parties.  If you provide us with permission, Kia may also share your personal information with advertisers and other companies who are not affiliated with Kia, but who would like to send you information about their products and services.  However, you will always have the opportunity to decline the option to receive information from unaffiliated third parties (and thereby not permit this sharing of your personal information) when personal information is collected.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Aggregation and Use of Personal Information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>All of the personal information that you provide to Kia, our dealers, licensees, and business partners may be aggregated and analyzed to enable us to develop targeted marketing programs and service offerings.  We may also use your personal information to contact you regarding Kia programs and services or third party programs and services that we believe might be of interest to you. If you do not want us to contact you for this purpose, you may decline to receive such offers by calling our Consumer Affairs Department, 800-333-4543, at any time.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Security of the Database and Your Personal Information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Kia uses reasonable administrative, technical, personnel, and physical measures to safeguard personal information in its possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification. In addition, Kia uses reasonable methods to make sure that personal information is accurate, up-to-date, and appropriately complete.

Kia cannot guarantee your confidential use of Kia.com and other Kia websites and will not assume responsibility for any damage that you or any person may suffer as a result of a breach of confidentiality resulting from your use of a Kia website or any information that you transmitted to a Kia website.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Links to Other Sites</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Kia.com and other Kia websites may contain links to third party sites not controlled by Kia or covered by this Privacy Policy, including, as noted above, sites belonging to Kia dealers, Kia licensees, or independent product review sites. Kia makes no representation or warranty as to the accuracy of any information contained in any hypertext link to those sites. Any hypertext link to any other person or entity should not be construed as endorsement by Kia of such person's or entity's website, products, or services.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Cookies and Other Tracking Technology Used By Us and Certain Third parties</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>In addition to any personal information or other information that you choose to provide to us on the website, we and our third-party service providers may use “cookies”, “web beacons”, “embedded scripts” and variety of other technologies, now and hereafter devised, that automatically collect certain website usage information whenever you visit or interact with the website.  This information may include browser type, operating system, the page served, the time, the source of the request, the preceding page view, and other similar information.  We may use this usage information for a variety of purposes, including enhancing or otherwise improving the website.  In addition, we may also collect your IP address or some other unique identifier for the particular device you use to access the Internet, as applicable (a "Device Identifier").  A Device Identifier is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer, and we may identify your device by its Device Identifier.  When analyzed, usage information helps us determine how our website is used, such as what types of visitors arrive at the website, what type of content is most popular, what type of content you may find most relevant and what type of visitors are interested in particular kinds of content and advertising.  We may associate your Device Identifier or web site usage information with the personal information you provide, but we will treat the combined information as personal information.

A cookie is a data file placed on a computer when it is used to visit the website.  Cookies may be used for many purposes, including, without limitation, tracking user preferences and web pages visited while using the website.  You may disable many types of cookies using your browser's preferences, but some features of the website may not function properly or may operate slowly if you disable the cookies.  If you are concerned about the storage and use of cookies, you may be able to direct your internet browser to notify you and seek approval whenever a cookie is being sent to your hard drive.  You may also delete many types of cookies manually from your hard drive through your internet browser or other programs.  Please note, however, that some parts of our website will not function properly or be available to you if you refuse to accept a cookie, delete cookies or choose to disable the acceptance of cookies and doing so may also interfere with your third party opt-outs described further below.

A web beacon is a small graphic image or other web programming code (also known as "1x1 GIFs" or "clear GIFs").  We may include these in our web pages and e-mail messages.  Web beacons may be invisible to you, but any electronic image or other web programming code inserted into a web page or e-mail can act as a web beacon.  Web beacons or similar technologies may be used for a number of purposes, including, without limitation, to count visitors to the website, to monitor how users navigate the website, to count how many e-mails that were sent were actually opened or to count how many particular articles or links were actually viewed.  An embedded script is programming code that is designed to collect information about your interactions with the website, such as the links you click on.  The code is temporarily downloaded onto your computer from our web server or a third-party service provider, is active only while you are connected to the website, and is deactivated or deleted thereafter.

In addition, we may work with third parties such as network advertising networks and/or traffic measurement services to track your activities to better serve you contextually relevant content and/or advertisements on the website and/or to analyze traffic on the website.  Network advertisers are third parties that display content and/or advertisements based on your visits to the website and/or other websites you have visited.  This enables us to target content and/or advertisements to you based on perceived interest.  Third parties that assist us in this regard may themselves set and access their own cookies and other technologies on your computer and track certain behavioral information regarding users of your computer via a Device Identifier.  These third party cookies are set to, among other things:  (a) help deliver content and/or advertisements to you that you might be interested in; (b) regulate when and how often content and/or advertisements are served to you; and (c) understand the usefulness to you of the content and/or advertisements that have been delivered to you.  Note that any images (or any other parts of a web page) served by third parties in association with third party cookies and other technologies may serve as web beacons, which enable third parties to carry out the previously described activities.  Third party cookies, web beacons and other third party technologies are governed by each third party's specific privacy policy, not this one.  While we may use a variety of companies to serve content and/or advertisements on the website, you may wish to visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp, which provides information regarding this practice by Network Advertising Initiative ("NAI") members, and your choices regarding having this information used by these companies, including the "opt-out" procedures of NAI members.  Opting out of one or more NAI members only means that those NAI members will no longer be able to deliver targeted content and/or ads to you, which will affect this and other web sites, but does not mean you will no longer receive any targeted content and/or ads.  Also, if your browsers are configured to reject cookies when you visit this opt-out page, or you subsequently erase your cookies, use a different computer or change web browsers, your NAI opt-out may not, or may no longer, be effective.  Additional information is available on the NAI's web site accessible by the above link.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Access to Your Personal Information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>If possible, we will let you review your personal information that you provided to Kia and will take reasonable steps to correct any personal information that you inform us is incorrect.  If you ask Kia to stop using the personal information you provided to Kia, Kia will honor that request while retaining any record of your personal information that is necessary to comply with applicable federal, state, or local law.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Opportunity to Opt-Out</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>If you would like to communicate with us about our Privacy Policy or Kia's collection and use of your personal information, to review or correct your personal information, or to stop all future communications from us, please contact Kia Consumer Affairs at 800-333-4542.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
