<POLICY modification_date="April 01, 2013" policy_url="http://www.klm.com/travel/in_en/customer_support/privacy_policy/privacy_policy.htm" website_category="Recreation" website_index="053" website_url="klm.com">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>Back to Customer Support
KLM Privacy Policy
Version: 18 April 2013
On this page:

Introduction
Discover the convenience of KLM's website
What personal data does KLM process?
What if you do not wish to receive any information?
E-mail services
The KLM website's registration of clicking behavior
False KLM e-mails
The KLM website's use of cookies/applets

What security measures does KLM take?
Links to other sites
Special security measures to control aggression
Travel to and from the Netherlands Antilles, Aruba and Suriname
The transfer of data to countries beyond the EU borders
Contact
Changes</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Introduction</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>The Koninklijke Luchtvaart Maatschappij NV (also known as KLM Royal Dutch Airlines) knows, just as Air France (45 rue de Paris, 95744 Roissy CDG Cedex Frankrijk), that the personal privacy of its passengers and frequent flyer members (grouped together in this document as “customers”), prospective customers and the visitors to its website is very important. The personal data of KLM's customers, prospective customers and website visitors is thus handled and protected with the greatest possible care in accordance with the requirements stated in the piece of Dutch legislation known as the Personal Data Protection Act (WBP).

KLM's office at Amsterdamseweg 55, postal code 1182 GP in Amstelveen, The Netherlands, is the responsible party for processing the company's data. In accordance with the WBP, KLM has reported how it personal data to the Dutch Data Protection Authority (College Bescherming Persoonsgegevens - CBP) located in The Hague, The Netherlands. These reports are available to the public and can be accessed over the Internet at http://www.dutchdpa.nl/Pages/home.aspx . (Search by entering ‘Koninklijke Luchtvaart Maatschappij' under ‘naam' or by entering ‘KLM'.)
Back to top
Ads not by this site</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Discover the convenience of KLM's website</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>KLM is continually extending and improving its electronic services to make them more convenient for its customers, prospective customers and the visitors to the KLM website. One example is the KLM website that offers 24-hour access to online reservations and Flying Blue services. These e-services simplify everything from travel planning to e-tickets and e-check-in. And they can also be used to obtain information about hotel and car rental reservations and travel insurance policies with our cooperating partners.
Back to top</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>What personal data does KLM process</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Within the framework of providing you with its services, selling you its products and services, or allowing you to contact KLM for any other reason, KLM records such data as your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, personal travel preferences and interests. KLM uses your data for executing contracts, for providing services, and for informing customers, prospective customers and visitors to the KLM website about the activities, products and services of KLM and its partners. KLM exchanges for these purposes personal data with Air France and partners. One way KLM uses your personal data for your convenience is to consider your travel preferences and interests and to develop new services and products. Sometimes, KLM issues surveys or holds contests and/or competitions in which customers, prospective customers and/or visitors to the website are approached to participate.
Back to top</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>What if you do not wish to receive any information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>If you would rather not receive any information about the activities, products and services of KLM and KLM partners, you can indicate this by sending a letter to this effect and enclosing a copy of your proof of identity to the KLM Privacy Office at the address given at the bottom of this page. (Please refer to the next section in regard to applying for and discontinuing KLM e-mail services.)
Back to top
Ads not by this site</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>E-mail services</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Providing electronic services is important to KLM, particularly because these e-services offer customers, prospective customers and website visitors quick and convenient access to information. When you subscribe to receiving such communications as KLM's electronic newsletter, you are giving KLM and its partners permission to use your e-mail address for sending you the newsletter, information from her partners, and other mail such as surveys and news about special offers.

If you no longer wish to receive information via e-mail, you can click on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of each e-newsletter, or at KLM.com

If you do not want to receive Flying Blue and partner offers, you can update your communication preferences. Please log in to manage your subscription at https://www.klm.com/travel/nl_en/apps/myaccount/myahome.htm





Back to top</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>The KLM website's registration of clicking behavior</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>At the KLM website, general visiting data such as the most commonly requested pages is recorded without this data being linked to the identity of the visitor. The purpose of this information gathering is to make the KLM website as convenient as possible in regard to the needs of its visitors. This data can also be used to place information which is better geared to the needs of visitors on the website. In this way, KLM can continue to improve its lending of services.
Back to top</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>False KLM e-mails</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>If you received an e-mail about a flight that you did not book, this may be an attempt to retrieve your personal information (also known as phishing) or infect your computer.

Such messages you can recognise by:

the lack of a personal salutation
urgent request to answer
poor grammar and spelling mistakes
a link to an unknown web address
reference to a ticket number that does not begin with ‘074' and does not consist of 13 digits


KLM and its partners will never send you an e-mail asking for personal information. A genuine KLM ticket via e-mail never has any attachment or link to personal information.

We recommend not responding to this e-mail, to not click on any links or open any attachments and to provide no personal information. Please forward the e-mail to us via: email.abuse.qam@klm.com.

Please note that we will not reply to messages sent to this address.
Back to top
Ads not by this site</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>The KLM website's use of cookies/applets</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>In offering its services, KLM makes use of cookies/applets. These are compact pieces of information stored on the hard drive of your computer. KLM uses both temporary cookies and special cookies/applets.
Temporary cookies contain no personal data and are intended only to make it easier for you to use the KLM site. Once special cookies/applets have been stored in your computer, our website can identify you each time you return to the KLM site. With this information, the site can be designed especially to meet your needs – and to make our site nicer to use. Even if you have switched off the use of cookies/applets in your browser, you can still visit most of the elements in the KLM website. For more information, please read our cookie policy. In case you would like to remove the cookies from your PC, please

read more about how to delete cookies
Back to top</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>What security measures does KLM take</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>KLM is doing everything possible to safeguard your personal data from wrongful use. Only authorized personnel have access to your data. Should it be necessary for KLM partners to assume part or any of certain KLM services, KLM has reached an agreement with them that they will handle your personal data with an equal level of strict confidentiality.
Back to top</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Links to other sites</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Certain pages on the KLM site have links to the websites of other companies. Because KLM cannot be responsible for how these companies handle personal data, you are advised to read the policy (or statements) of these non-KLM sites carefully in regard to how they process and protect personal data since the conditions offered by these sites may not be the same as those offered by KLM.
Back to top
Ads not by this site</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Special security measures to control aggression</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>To promote public order and safety aboard its flights and how this is handled, KLM keeps a record of the names of passengers who have interfered with the safety, public order and discipline, either on board its aircraft or on the ground, to such an extent that they will not be allowed passage aboard KLM aircraft for an unlimited period of time, for a limited period of time or only under certain conditions determined by KLM. These persons are personally informed (in writing where possible) about the fact that their name has been placed in these records and how long these special security measures will apply to them. Interested parties may request permission to examine this data or to make changes to its accuracy by submitted this request in writing to the KLM Privacy Office.
Back to top</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Travel to and from the Netherlands Antilles, Aruba and Suriname</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>The names of passengers who have disembarked at Amsterdam Airport Schiphol and who have been found by the Royal Netherlands Military Constabulary to be carrying illegal drugs will be recorded by the State of the Netherlands. The names of these persons shall also be given to KLM. On the basis of this information, KLM will be entitled to refuse to enter into any transport contract with these persons for a period of three years.
Interested parties may request permission to examine this data or to make changes to its accuracy by submitting this request in writing to the Royal Netherlands Military Constabulary at P.O. Box 90615, 2509 LP The Hague, The Netherlands. If you reside on Aruba, the Netherlands Antilles, in Suriname or in Venezuela, you should accompany this written request with a copy of your passport.
Back to top</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>The transfer of data to countries beyond the EU borders</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>More and more additional measures are being taken throughout the world, particularly in the United States and Canada, for the purpose of tightening border controls. These and other countries are asking KLM and all other airlines that fly to, from or through certain countries for more access to passenger data for the purpose of preventing and controlling possible terrorism.
The possible sanctions applied to an airline for not lending its cooperation in these matters can be severe: heavy fines are anticipated and, in the most serious case, the retraction of the airline's landing rights. In addition, an airline's refusal to cooperate in this matter will still not prevent the requested data from being provided; after all, the passengers will be asked for this information at the airport, the result being extra long lines and longer waiting times for passing through the customs and immigrations services.
KLM would like to emphasize that the authorities involved have given their assurance that your reservation data will be used only for security purposes and will be accessible only to personnel authorized to deal with security matters (customs, safety and immigration personnel).
Back to top</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Contact</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>For questions, remarks or complaints about the protection of your personal data by KLM, please click and complete the form. On receipt of this form we will contact you as soon as possible.

If you would like to view your personal data, have this corrected or would like to lodge an objection against the use of your personal data by KLM, then you may send your written response, accompanied by a copy of your proof of identity, to:

KLM Royal Dutch Airlines
Privacy Office - AMSPI
PO Box 7700
1117 ZL Luchthaven Schiphol
The Netherlands
Back to top</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Changes</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>KLM reserves the right to revise its privacy policy from time to time. For this reason, please check regularly for the most recent version of KLM's privacy policy.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
