<POLICY modification_date="" policy_url="http://www.fao.org/contact-us/terms/en/" website_category="Science" website_index="069" website_url="fao.org">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>PRIVACY POLICY

FAO's Privacy Policy covers the collection and sharing of visitors' information on all sites within the FAO website.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>In general, users may browse the FAO website without revealing any personal information. The only information gathered during general browsing is from standard server logs. This includes user's IP (Internet Protocol) address, domain name, browser type and operating system. It also includes the files downloaded, pages visited and the dates and times of those visits. Such information is used internally for the purpose of website traffic analysis only.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>PERSONAL INFORMATION</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>To register for a newsletter, log on to a specific FAO website requiring registration, request information, provide feedback, apply for a job, join a discussion group or join an electronic mailing list, users will be asked to provide basic personal information such as name, postal address and email address. This information is collected only with the user's knowledge and permission, and it is kept in FAO databases and mailing lists directly related to the services provided.

Parts of the FAO website with specific requirements to collect personal information may publish additional privacy terms specific to that site.

Some parts of the FAO website registration processes use cookies to save details for the next visit. This helps FAO provide a better service. When joining an electronic discussion group, other participants of the discussion group (including non-FAO employees) may see personal information that the user has volunteered. For open discussion groups, this information will be public.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>SECURITY</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, this FAO computer system employs software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage.

Except for authorized investigations and to maintain required correspondence files, no other attempts are made to identify individual users or their usage habits. Raw data logs are used to determine the number of users and, occasionally, which general domains are accessing the FAO website. The FAO website does not use persistent cookies and data gathered are scheduled for regular destruction in accordance with United Nations and FAO guidelines.

Any information provided to FAO by users is held with the utmost care and security, and is not used in any manner other than that set forth in this Privacy Policy, or in any additional site-specific policies, without users' explicit consent.

All FAO employees who have access to or are associated with the processing of personal data are obliged to respect the confidentiality of official business matters, including personal data.

Notification of amendments

FAO reserves the right to amend this policy at its own discretion. Notifications of any significant amendment will be announced on www.fao.org.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
