<POLICY modification_date="May 01, 2012" policy_url="http://www.linguee.com/english-german/page/privacy.php" website_category="Reference" website_index="095" website_url="linguee.com">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>Privacy Policy of Linguee GmbH

Confidentiality and protection of your data is of paramount importance to Linguee GmbH (hereinafter "Linguee"). The protection of personal data collected, processed, and used in connection with your visit to our website is very important to us. Collection and use of your personal data is protected exclusively in accordance with the applicable data protection regulations. This privacy policy aims to inform you about the collection and use of your personal data whilst using our website www.linguee.com or Linguee Premium/Linguee Professional.

This agreement shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the German Federal Data Protection Act (BDSG) and the parties hereby submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the German courts in respect of any dispute or matter arising out of or connected with this agreement. Any translation of the German language or German law version of this agreement (the "Original Agreement") is provided for convenience only and you agree that in the event of a conflict between the translated version and the Original Agreement, the provisions of the Original Agreement shall prevail.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Contact/Data Controller</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Data Controller for the purpose of German data protection law:

Linguee GmbH
Theodor-Heuss-Ring 36
50668 Köln
Amtsgericht Köln, HRB 64606

Should you have any questions or suggestions concerning data protection, please feel free to contact us via email at privacy@linguee.com.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Purpose and scope of data protection</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>The purpose of the Data Protection Act is to protect individuals against infringement of their right to privacy as the result of the handling of their personal data. Personal data, as laid down in Section 3 (1) of the German Federal Data Protection Act (BDSG), is any information concerning the personal or material circumstances of an identified or identifiable natural person i.e name, address, email-address or telephone number and possibly data on usage. Data on usage is the data necessary in order to use our website e.g. characteristics to identify the recipient of the service, details of the beginning and end of the of the scope of the respective usage and details of the telemedia used by the recipient of the service. Increased protection is required for special categories of personal data such as information on racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, trade-union membership, health or sex life.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Data collection and processing</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Automated data collection
On accessing a Linguee website, your internet browser and Linguee Premium / Professional automatically transfers data. The following data is stored separately from other data which is possibly transferred to us:
time and date of visit,
web browser and version,
utilised operating system,
website from which you are visiting us (referrer URL),
name of requesting domain,
amount of transmitted data,
notifications of successful data retrieval and
when using a web browser, the search term.
The above data is stored solely for technical reasons and will not, at any time, be associated to a specific person.

Additionally, Linguee will log the IP address of each enquiring computer. This is necessary in order to analyse requests, ensure the security of Linguee's system, prevent unauthorised retrieval of the contents of our database and prevent fake comments.

Data entered by users of subscription service Linguee Premium / Linguee Professional
Should you wish to continue use of the subscription service Linguee Premium / Linguee Professional after expiration of the free test phase, a simple registration is necessary. Registration requires that you provide your name, email address, user name, password and the requested payment information. This data is not only necessary in order to create and manage your user account, but also to allow the maximum use of all Linguee Premium / Linguee Professional features. Linguee may also use this data in order to answer, at request, questions, suggestions or complaints.

Optional data
As an additional feature, Linguee Professional also offers users the chance to create their own personal translator profile in the translator database. Translators may provide profile information such as name, location, associations/organisations, language pairs, native tongue etc. The information provided for your translator profile is optional and not required in order to use Linguee Professional. Please note that all information you voluntarily provide for your profile may, for example, be used to recommend you as a translator to other users.

The Linguee website allows you to voluntarily set up a free user account. There are several advantages of being a registered user: enjoy search results free of advertising, suggest words and translations, keep track of your suggestions and edited entries and participate in vocabulary discussions. In order to register, you need to provide a login name, your full name, your email address and choose a password. Your full name is not visible to other users.

Naturally, you alone decide which data you would like to provide us with. We at Linguee are committed to the principle of data economy and avoidance. However, missing information may lead to restrictions in the use of Linguee Premium and Linguee Professional.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Disclosure of data</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>In order to process a payment, you will be redirected to the chosen payment service provider, where you will be asked to provide the necessary information for the handling of the payment (e.g. credit card details). Linguee itself has no access to your payment information. Solely the respective payment service provider is responsible for data collection and processing. Should future payments be settled differently, Linguee will forward the information for payment to the appropriate payment provider (bank, credit card company etc.).

Furthermore, the disclosure of your personal data without your express prior consent may generally only occur under the following exceptional circumstances:
In cases where it is deemed necessary in order to aid investigation of unlawful platform usage or legal proceedings, personal data will be made available to criminal prosecution authorities and, if necessary, to injured third parties. However, personal data will only be forwarded to the abovementioned in the presence of solid evidence of unlawful and/or abusive conduct. Data may also be disclosed should such disclosure aid the enforcement of terms and conditions or other agreements. Linguee is obliged by law to provide information upon request of certain public authorities i.e. criminal prosecution authorities, revenue authorities and authorities pursuing administrative offences entailing fines.
Occaisionally, to enable us to provide you with our services, we are reliant on contractual partners and external service providers, for example in the areas of advertising campaigns (sent only with your express prior consent), customer service and the processing of payments (credit card, billing address etc.). In the abovementioned cases, it is necessary that we forward information to the relevant party for further processing. In order to protect your right to privacy, our external service providers are carefully selected and periodically reviewed. The service providers are only allowed to use the data for purposes stated by Linguee. The service providers are also contractually obliged to handle your data in expressly in accordance with this privacy policy and German data protection laws.
Linguee GmbH is a continually developing company. It is therefore possible that Linguee GmbH may change it's legal form, or choose to buy or sell individual subsidiaries, company shares or units. In the event of such a transaction, customer/user information will be transferred together with the transferred part of the company. Linguee will ensure that each transfer of personal data to third parties (in the aforementioned manner) will be conducted in accordance with this privacy policy and the relevant data protection laws.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Search terms and search history</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>If you click on a word for which you require a translation while using Linguee Premium / Linguee Professional, the whole paragraph in which the word is embedded is sent to Linguee. This helps in offering you with a translation in the appropriate context. In order to calculate and display the results, search queries, including the context in which they are sent, are stored on a short-term basis in the main memory on a Linguee server. Data is not stored beyond the aforementioned retention period.

Please note that Linguee Premium / Linguee Professional is an automated process and is unable to detect the inclusion of personal data in the transmitted paragraphs. As a result of which, clicking on words found in paragraphs which contain personal data of third parties and/or sensitive data is strictly prohibited. Sensitive data is data containing information on racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, trade-union membership, health or sex life.

Depending on the your version of Linguee Premium / Linguee Professional, you may allow that your search history be stored. This can be done by changing your profile settings. As a result, your search history may then be included in your future translation searches. However, this is only possible if you have chosen to use this feature. You may revoke your consent that your search history is stored at any time with future effect via email to privacy@linguee.com or by changing your profile settings.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Newsletter</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Linguee offers a free newsletter service. The Linguee newsletter keeps subscribers informed about the latest Linguee news, surveys, new products or services and additional information of interest. Furthermore, we also provide information regarding offers and products from our cooperation partners.

To sign up for the newsletter, go to "Feedback" under http://www.linguee.com/english-german/page/feedback.php then the tick the box next to "Newsletter".

You can unsubscribe from the newsletter at any time. Each newsletter contains information about how to unsubscribe with future effect.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Cookies</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Linguee stores so-called "Cookies", in order to provide you a large array of features and an easy-to-use service. "Cookies" are small files which, with the help of your browser, are stored on your computer. If you do not wish that "Cookies", you can disable "Cookies" by changing the settings of your internet browser on your computer accordingly. Please note that this may limit the functionality of our service.

Linguee also uses "Cookies" from our cooperation partners. This is how our offers are provided with advertisements, for example from DoubleClick/Google, pilot media GmbH und Co. KG, Group M, Ligatus GmbH, Adcloud GmbH, Criteo GmbH, AudienceScience (Germany) GmbH und Nugg.ad AG. Linguee may place (or identify) a unique Cookie, from the customer referred to in the advertisement, on your browser. By placement of the advertisement, information about your visit to the website is collected e.g. how often you have seen an advertisement. No further personal data e.g. your name or address, is collected or forwarded.

It is therefore not possible for you to be identified on the basis of this information. If you do not want information to be forwarded or Cookies to be placed, or you would like to receive further information regarding the use of Cookies, please refer to e.g. http://www.google.com/intl/de/privacy/privacy-policy.html, http://www.google.com/intl/de/privacy_ads.html oder auch http://www.meine-Cookies.org/

Central opt-out available soon under: http://www.meine-Cookies.org/Cookies_verwalten/praeferenzmanager.html

If you object to information regarding this purpose, in connection with your use of our online service, being forwarded, you may deactivate the interest-based advertising with one of our cooperation partners:

Google - Zum deaktivieren bitte hier klicken
Nuggad - http://www.nugg.ad/de/datenschutz
IVW/Agof - http://optout.ivwbox.de/
Adconion GmbH - http://www.adconion.com/de/datenschutz/das-adconion-cookie.html
AdJug GmbH - http://www.adjug.de
adnologies GmbH - http://ads.heias.com/x/opt_out.php
adyard GmbH - http://adyard.de/privacy-policy
Criteo GmbH - http://www.criteo.com/de/datenschutzrichtlinien/opt-out
ClickDistrict - http://ads.creative-serving.com/opt-out
groupm - http://www.groupm.com/privacy-policy
Kupona GmbH - http://datenschutz.kupona.de
Ligatus GmbH - http://www.ligatus.de/global/popup_datenschutz_retargeting.html
Metrigo GmbH - http://metrigo.com/privacy
M,P Newmedia GmbH - http://www1.mpnrs.com/deliver2/optout.jsp
Microsoft Deutschland GmbH - http://choice.live.com/advertisementchoice/
myThings - http://www.mythings.com/Optout.html
Open Inventory media - http://de.adition.com/privacy/
Pilot 1/0 GmbH - http://www.pilot.de/datenschutz
plista GmbH - http://www.plista.com/optout/index
Specific Media Germany GmbH - http://www.specificmedia.de/privacy
Vibrant Media GmbH - http://intellitxt.com/opt_out/ch_optout.asp
Yahoo! Deutschland GmbH - http://info.yahoo.com/privacy/de/yahoo/opt_out/targeting/details.html
xplosion interactive GmbH - http://www.xplosion.de/so-funktionierts/opt-out.html
mediascale GmbH &amp; Co. KG - http://www.mediascale.de/de/datenschutz/index.html
If you have any revocation-related questions, please contact: widerruf@netzathleten.de
Please note, the implementing your revocation may require configuration of a permanent Cookie on your computer!</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Website Enhancement</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Google Analytics
This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses "Cookies" i.e. text files stored on your computer, enabling an analysis of website and Linguee Premium / Linguee Professional usage. The information generated by the Cookie about your use of the website (including your abbreviated IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by a Google server in the United States. Google will use this information for evaluating your use of the website and Linguee Premium / Linguee Preofessional, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. When using Linguee Premium / Linguee Professional, no search requests or sections of text you click on will be forwarded to Google.

If you object to a website analysis, you can deactivate Google Analytics with a browser add-on. Download the add-on here: http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=de.

Google AdSense / AdExchange
Should Google AdSense or Google AdExchange (a Google Inc., USA ("Google") advertisement service) display advertisements on this website (text ads, banners etc.), your browser may store a Cookie from Google Inc. or sent from a third party. The information stored in the Cookie may be recorded, collected or analysed by Google Inc. or a third party. Additionally, Google AdSense uses "Web Beacons" (small invisible graphics) to gather information, with which simple data such as website visitor traffic can also be recorded, collected and analysed. The information generated by the Cookie and/or Web Beacon about your use of this website is transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use the information gathered for the purpose of evaluating use of the website in view of the AdSense advertisements. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process thie information od Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You can prevent the storage of Cookies on your hard drive and the display of web beacons by choosing "accept no Cookies" (phrase may vary with every web browser) in your browser settings. In Internet Explorer under "Tools / Internet options / Privacy / Advanced", then check "Override automatic Cookie handling" and "Block" First-party Cookies and Third-party Cookies and uncheck "Always allow session Cookies". In Firefox under "Firefox Menu / Preferences / Privacy", then set "Firefox will" to "use custom settings for history", uncheck "Accept Cookies from sites" and uncheck "Accept third-party Cookies". Further information can be found under .

Criteo
For marketing purposes, the Linguee website uses Criteo SA (Unterer Anger 3, 80331 Munich, Germany) technology to collect and store information, in anonymous form, about website users' surfing behaviour. Criteo analyses the users' surfing behaviour, allowing a targeted and personalised banner with recommended products to be displayed when visiting other websites. You will find a small "i" (visible by mouse over) in the bottom right corner of each banner displayed . By clicking on it, you will be directed to a website, which explains the systematics and also offers an opt-out. By clicking the "Opt-Out", a Cookie will be placed which will prevent the banner from being displayed in the future. Data is, under no circumstances, used to personally identify website visitors. The data collected by Criteo is used solely to improve the advertisement offers. The collected information is not forwarded to third parties and is not used to other purposes. Please find further information or object to an anonymous analysis of your surfing behaviour under http://www.criteo.com/us/privacy-policy.

Scaleable Centralised Measuring Procedure
In order to determine statistical parameters for usage of our services, our website uses the "Scaleable Centralised Measuring Procedure" provided by INFOnline (https://www.infonline.de). Data is collected anonymously during this process. The (Scaleable Centralised Measuring Procedure) range measurement uses a Cookie "ivwbox.de" or an electronic signature (created using automatically transmitted information from your computer), to help recognise computer systems. IP adresses are processed in anonymous form only and are not stored. This range measurement procedure was developed in compliance with data protection legislation. The aim of the range measurement is to acquire statistical information regarding intensity of usage and number of users of a website. Individual users are not identified at any time. Your identity remains protected at all times. You will not receive advertisements from this system.
User statistics of websites and online services from members of the German "Informationsgemeinschaft zur Feststellung der Verbreitung von Werbeträgern e.V." (IVW - www.ivw.eu, German association for the surveillance of the distribution of advertising media) or participants of the study "internet facts" by the "Arbeitsgemeinschaft Online-Forschung e.V." (AGOF - www.agof.de, German association for online research), will be published monthly by AGOF, the "Arbeitsgemeinschaft Media-Analyse e.V." (ag.ma - www.agma-mmc.de, German association for media analysis) and IVW, and may be viewed under http://www.agof.de, http://www.agma-mmc.de and http://www.ivw.eu. Besides publishing data, IVW regularly verifies the rule- and data protection compliancy regarding usage of the Scaleable Central Measuring Procedure. Further information about the Scaleable Central Measuring Procedure can be found on the INFOnline GmbH website (https://www.infonline.de), the AGOF data protection website (http://www.agof.de/datenschutz) and the IVW data protection website (http://www.ivw.eu). You may object to the data processing via Scaleable Central Measuring Procedure under the following opt-out link: http://optout.ivwbox.de</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Deleting your data</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Your data will be deleted as soon as it is no longer needed for the aforementioned purpose. Should it be required by law that certain data is retained, this data will be blocked. The data is then no longer available for further use.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Changes to this Privacy Policy</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Linguee reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time. The latest version of the data protection policy can be found under http://www.linguee.de/deutsch-englisch/page/privacy.php</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
