<POLICY modification_date="February 07, 2013" policy_url="http://www.indianrail.gov.in/disclaimer.html" website_category="Regional" website_index="098" website_url="indianrail.gov.in">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>USER AGREEMENT</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Being allowed access to "www.indianrail.gov.in" ("the site") of Government of India, Ministry of Railways, you enter into the indianrail.gov.in user agreement on the terms and conditions set out below.

This Agreement is for an indefinite term. Either party can terminate for any reason at any time.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>COPYRIGHT</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Unless otherwise stated, copyright or similar rights in all materials presented on the site, including graphical images, are owned by Government of India, Ministry of Railways.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>LIMITED PERMISSION TO COPY</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>You are permitted to print or download extracts from these pages for your personal use only. Any copies of these pages saved to disk or to any other storage medium may only be used for subsequent viewing purposes or to print extracts for personal use. You may not (whether directly or through the use of any software program) create a database in electronic or structured manual form by regularly or systematically downloading and storing all or any part of the pages from this site. No part of The Site may be reproduced or transmitted to or stored in any other web site, nor may any of its pages or part thereof be disseminated in any electronic or non electronic form, nor included in any public or private electronic retrieval system or service without Government of India, Ministry of Railway's prior written permission.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>DISCLAIMER</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>All the contents of this Site are only for general information or use. They do not constitute advice and should not be relied upon in making (or refraining from making) any decision. Government of India, Ministry of Railways hereby excludes any warranty, express or implied, as to the quality, static/dynamic data accuracy including train timings, timeliness, completeness, performance, fitness for a particular purpose of the Site or any of its contents, including (but not limited) to any financial tools contained within the Site. Government of India, Ministry of Railways will not be liable for any damages (including, without limitation, damages for loss of business projects, or loss of profits) arising in contract, tort or otherwise from the use of or inability to use the Site, or any of its contents, or from any action taken (or refrained from being taken) as a result of using the Site or any such contents. Government of India, Ministry of Railways, makes no warranty that the contents of the Site are free from infection by viruses or anything else which has contaminating or destructive properties.

Certain links on the Site lead to resources located on servers maintained by third parties over whom Government of India, Ministry of Railways, has no control. Government of India, Ministry of Railways accepts no responsibility or liability for any of the material contained on those servers. Part of the Site contains advertising by third parties. Responsibility for ensuring that material submitted for inclusion on the Site complies with applicable International and National law is exclusively on the advertisers. Government of India, Ministry of Railways will not be responsible for any claim, error, omission or inaccuracy in advertising material.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>COMMERCIAL USE</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>The Railway related data available on this site should be not be used for commercial use.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>CHANGES TO THIS AGREEMENT</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We reserve the right to add to or change the terms of this Agreement. Any changes will be posted to http://www.indianrail.gov.in/disclaim.html and it is your responsibility as a user to refer to the terms on accessing this service. Changes could be made by us after the first posting to the Site and you will be deemed to have accepted any change if you continue to access The Site after that time.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>MATERIAL SUBMITTED BY USERS</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Certain elements of The Site will contain material submitted by users. Government of India, Ministry of Railways accepts no responsibility for the content or accuracy of such material.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>FORCE MAJEURE</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Ministry of Railways shall have no liability to you for any interruption or delay in access to the Site irrespective of the cause.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>INDIAN LAW</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>The Agreement will be governed by Indian Law. The Indian courts will have exclusive jurisdiction over any disputes arising under this agreement.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
