<POLICY modification_date="September 27, 2013" policy_url="http://www.greenmangaming.com/terms-and-conditions/" website_category="Games" website_index="074" website_url="greenmangaming.com">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>POLICY ON PRIVACY, DATA, COOKIES AND MARKETING COMMUNICATIONS</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Data</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We may ask you for certain information and you may submit personal data to the Service (such as your name, email address and contact details) when you subscribe or sign up to the Service. Green Man Gaming and Playfire user now have the ability to use either site with the same log in details. Some data is shared between the Playfire and Green Man Gaming services in order to enhance the user experience on both platforms. We may also record which parts of the Service and services you are interested in as well as user traffic patterns and site use. This information will be kept securely in accordance with an internal security policy and may be used to:process your Communications, your subscription to the Service and to enable your use of the Service and associated services; open and run your account and provide you with an up to date, efficient and reliable service; administer prize draws; and generally run the Service.

We also utilise device finger-printing technologies. We receive information from customers about devices that connect to Our websites, operated or controlled by customer and utilise this information to assist in the detection and prevention of fraudulent transactions. By subscribing and submitting your data you agree to this use.

We will only use information collected about you in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998. From time to time We also monitor and record telephone calls for training purposes and to improve the service to you.We do not collect sensitive information about you without your explicit consent.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Marketing Communications</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We give you a choice of whether or not you want Us or other reputable companies to contact you about future offers, events and new services or related activities that you may find useful. We will not sell or trade personal information to other companies but We would like to keep you informed of the developments on the Service and certain Games and We would like to share data with other reputable companies who may have interesting offers and information for you (inside or outside the EU). We will not send you any marketing emails or pass your information on to third parties unless you give your consent or you have given it already.
Cookies

Greenmangaming.com and playfire.com use cookies in order to improve your user experience by enabling that website to ‘remember' you, either for the duration of your visit (using a ‘session cookie') or for repeat visits (using a ‘persistent cookie'). Our cookies do lots of different jobs, like letting you navigate between pages efficiently, storing your preferences, and generally improving your experience of a website.

Cookies make the interaction between you and the website faster and easier - if a website doesn't use cookies, it will think you are a new visitor every time you move to a new page on the site. For example, when you enter your login details and move to another page it won't recognise you and it won't be able to keep you logged in. Greenmangaming.com and playfire.com also use cookies to enable Us to target advertising or marketing messages based for example, on your location and/or browsing habits. Cookies may be set by the greenmangaming.com and playfire.com (‘first party cookies') or they may be set by other websites who run content or services for Us (such as Google Analytics) on the page you are viewing (‘third party cookies').
What is in a cookie?

A cookie is a simple text file that is stored on your computer or mobile device by a website's server and only that server will be able to retrieve or read the contents of that cookie. Each cookie is unique to your web browser. It will contain some anonymous information such as a unique identifier and the site name and some digits and numbers. It allows a website to remember things like your preferences or what's in your shopping basket.
What to do if you don't want cookies to be set

Some people find the idea of a website storing information on their computer or mobile device a bit intrusive, particularly when this information is stored and used by a third party without them knowing. Although this is generally quite harmless you may not, for example, want to see advertising that has been targeted to your interests. If you prefer, it is possible to block some or all cookies, or even to delete cookies that have already been set; but you need to be aware that you might lose some functions of the website.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Cookies</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>If you wish to restrict or block web browser cookies which are set on your device then you can do this through your browser settings; the Help function within your browser should tell you how. Alternatively, you may wish to visit www.aboutcookies.org, which contains comprehensive information on how to do this on a wide variety of desktop browsers. We use ‘cookies' on the Service. If you do not wish for Us to use cookies when you use the Service please adjust your Internet browser settings to not accept cookies. Your computer's help file should tell you how to do this but please note that this may affect your ability to use the Service and Games.

By agreeing to these terms you are specifically allowing the Service to execute all cookies as are required for the Service to operate as efficiently as possible with the best user experience in mind. If you don't disable cookies the Service will ask for and store details including your name and email address and may automatically insert certain information on the subscription or Communications forms so that you can use the Service with less form filling.
Privacy

If you have any other concerns over privacy, this privacy policy or the Service please contact Us (as appropriate) as described below.
GENERAL

These terms and conditions are subject to your statutory and common law consumer rights and shall not limit any rights you might have that may not be excluded under applicable law nor shall it exclude or limit either GMGL's or Playfire's liability for death or personal injury resulting from its negligence nor any fraudulent representation.

All questions, comments or inquiries should be directed by email to helpdesk@greenmangaming.com or helpdesk@playfire.com (as appropriate) or by post to FOA Customer Service, Green Man Gaming Limited Hamilton House, Mabledon Place, Bloomsbury, London WC1H 9BB.

These terms and conditions constitute the entire agreement between you and Us and shall apply to the exclusion of all other terms and conditions or conditions of contract which you may propose.

Use of the word “including” in these terms and conditions means including without limitation. Failure to enforce any of these terms and conditions will not be deemed a waiver of any term or right.

If any part of these terms and conditions is found to be unenforceable, it will be construed as far as possible to reflect the intention and the remainder of the provisions will remain in full force and effect.

The Service is intended for and directed at the United Kingdom and no representation or warranty is made as to whether the Service complies with the regulatory regime and local laws of any other country.

Use of the Service and these terms and conditions are subject to the laws of England which shall exclusively govern the interpretation, application and effect of all the above permissions, exclusions, licenses and conditions of use and shall be construed in accordance with the laws of England and the parties submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the English courts.
Additional Terms

These terms and conditions include the terms and conditions of the Client Software end user license agreement available here http://www.greenmangaming.com/terms-and-conditions/ and the following terms and conditions of the Game EULA, which shall apply to the use of all Games unless provided otherwise, as detailed in the Game EULA.
GAME EULA

YOU SHOULD CAREFULLY READ THE FOLLOWING END USER LICENSE AGREEMENT (“EULA”) BEFORE PURCHASING, DOWNLOADING OR INSTALLING ANY GAME. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS EULA, YOU SHOULD NOT USE, PURCHASE, DOWNLOAD OR INSTALL GAMES

Games purchased through the Service are copyright works of the third party developer or publisher identified in the Game (“Publisher”) or its licensors.

Use of the Games is governed by the terms of this EULA unless you are presented with an alternative end user license agreement, in which case the terms of that end user license agreement shall apply. If you have already purchased or downloaded a Game before being presented with an alternative end user licence agreement and you do not accept (and have not accepted) its terms and conditions and have not made any use of the Game please notify Us using the contact information below and We may arrange for your purchase and use of the Game to be cancelled and your account credited or a refund given as appropriate.

Each Game is solely for use by end users according to the terms of this EULA. Any use, reproduction or redistribution of the Game not in accordance with the terms of this EULA is expressly prohibited. Reference to Game in this EULA shall include any online service which is made available through it, where and to the fullest extent that the content permits.

1- Limited Use License. You are granted and by installing the Game you accept, a limited, non-exclusive right and license to install and use one (1) copy of the Game for your personal, non-commercial use on a single computer subject to the terms of this EULA. 2- End User Rights and Obligations. The Game is licensed to you as a single product. Its component parts may not be separated for use on more than one computer. You should back-up to another secure location, on a regular basis, any data files concerning your use of the Game as neither GMGL nor the Publisher has liability for lost or corrupted data. You may make a single back-up copy of the Game for your own personal use in the event that the original copy is destroyed, lost or corrupted. You may also permanently transfer the Game on to another computer owned by you provided that you remove the Game from the computer on which it was originally installed. You may not, except as expressly provided by this EULA: - sell, distribute or otherwise transfer copies or reproductions of the Game to any third party in any way and may only sell or Trade-In a Game to GMGL; - in whole or in part reproduce, translate, reverse engineer, derive source code from, modify, adapt, merge, translate, disassemble, decompile, or create derivative works based on or of the Game, except where applicable law provides otherwise in which case the product and all end results of such acts shall belong to, vest in and be the exclusive property of the owner of the applicable rights in the Game; - remove, disable or circumvent any proprietary notices, labels or copy protection software contained on or within the Game; - exploit the Game or any of its parts for any commercial purpose including, but not limited to, use at a cyber or internet cafe or any other location-based site; - network the Game or otherwise install or use it (or permit its use) on more than one computer, console, handheld device or PDA at the same time nor use or permit use of the Game in a network, multi-user arrangement or remote access arrangement, including any online use otherwise than as part of an online service approved by Publisher; - use the Game for any illegal or immoral purposes; - export or re-export the Game or any copy or adaptation in violation of any applicable laws or regulations; - create data or executable programs which mimic data or functionality in the Game; - otherwise use, copy, transfer, distribute, rent, lease, loan, sub-license or deal in the Game or any part or interest in it except as expressly provided by this EULA or in any manner which is inconsistent with this EULA 3- Ownership. The Game is licensed, not sold. Your licence confers no title or ownership in the Game. All right, title, interest and ownership rights in the Game and any copyright, design right, database right, patents and any rights to inventions, know-how, trade and business names, trade secrets and trade marks (whether registered or unregistered) and any applications therefor and other intellectual property rights (“Intellectual Property Rights”), in or connected with the Game and each part thereof (including by way of example only any titles, code, themes, objects, characters, stories, catchphrases, concepts, artworks, animations, sounds, music, audio-visual effects and methods of operation) are owned by, belong to and vest in Publisher or its licensors. The Game is protected by copyright law, international copyright treaties and conventions and other laws. All rights are asserted and reserved. The Game may contain certain licensed materials and Publisher's licensors may act to protect their rights in the event of any breach of this EULA. All trade marks are the property of their respective owners. 4- Termination. The licence granted by this EULA will terminate automatically if you breach its terms and conditions. In that event, you must immediately destroy and erase the Game and all and any copies in your possession or control and stored on any media whatsoever and on GMGL's request certify that you have done so. You may terminate this EULA at any time by deleting and removing the Game from your personal computer and destroying your copy of the Game in your possession. 5- Liability

THIS EULA SHALL NOT LIMIT ANY RIGHTS YOU MIGHT HAVE AS A CONSUMER THAT MAY NOT BE EXCLUDED UNDER APPLICABLE LAW NOR SHALL IT EXCLUDE OR LIMIT ANY

LIABILITY FOR FRAUD OR DEATH OR PERSONAL INJURY ARISING CAUSED BY NEGLIGENCE OF GMGL OR ITS LICENSORS. EXCEPT AS SPECIFICALLY PROVIDED IN THIS EULA AND TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW:

YOU INSTALL AND USE THIS GAME AT YOUR OWN RISK ; THE GAME IS PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY OR GUARANTEE OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF SATISFACTORY QUALITY, MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE OR NONINFRINGEMENT;GMGL AND ITS LICENSORS DO NOT WARRANT THAT THE OPERATION OF THIS GAME WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR FREE OR THAT ERRORS CAN BE CORRECTED;GMGL AND ITS LICENSORS EXCLUDES ANY AND ALL LIABILITY FOR ALL REPRESENTATIONS (EXCEPT THOSE MADE FRAUDULENTLY), WARRANTIES, CONDITIONS AND OTHER TERMS

WHICH BUT FOR THIS NOTICE WOULD HAVE EFFECT;

GMGL AND ITS LICENSORS WILL NOT IN ANY EVENT BE LIABLE IN ANY WAY FOR ANY CONSEQUENTIAL LOSS OR DAMAGE RESULTING FROM THE USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE THE GAME, ERRORS OR DEFICIENCIES IN IT, DAMAGE TO PROPERTY, LOST DATA, LOSS OF GOODWILL, COMPUTER FAILURE OR MALFUNCTION, LOSS OF BUSINESS, LOSS OFINFORMATION OR LOST PROFIT, WHETHER CAUSED BY NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE, EVEN IF IT HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH LOSS;GMGL AND ITS LICENSORS WILL NOT BE HELD LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGE, INJURY OR LOSS IF CAUSED AS A RESULT OF YOUR NEGLIGENCE, ACCIDENT OR MISUSE, OR IF THE GAME HAS BEEN MODIFIED IN ANY MANNER (NOT BY GMGL OR ITS LICENSORS) AFTER IT HAS BEEN BOUGHT. THE LIABILITY OF GMGL AND ITS LICENSORS SHALL NOT EXCEED THE ACTUAL PRICE PAID FOR THE GAME. You agree to indemnify, defend and hold GMGL and its licensors, partners, affiliates, contractors, officers, directors, employees and agents harmless from any claims, costs and expenses (including legal expenses) arising directly or indirectly from your misuse of the Game or use otherwise than in accordance with the terms of this EULA. GMGL's licensors shall be third-party beneficiaries under this EULA and shall have the express right to enforce its provisions and to enjoy the benefits of its protections. 6- Severability In the event that any provision of this EULA shall be held by a court or other tribunal of competent jurisdiction to be unenforceable, such provision will be enforced to the maximum extent permissible and the remaining portions of this EULA shall remain in full force and effect. 7- Applicable Law. To the maximum extent permitted by the local law applicable in the country in which you obtain or use them, the Game, any applicable online service and this EULA are subject to English Law. In the event that English Law cannot apply in the country you obtained or use the Game local law will apply.
HEALTH AND SAFETY AND PRECAUTIONS

Games may contain flashing lights, realistic images and simulations.
PLEASE READ THIS NOTICE BEFORE YOU OR YOUR CHILD USE YOUR GAME(S)

Some people experience side effects such as motion sickness, epileptic seizures, momentary loss of consciousness dizziness, motion sickness or nausea when viewing certain types of flashing light or pattern including when playing video games. This may happen where a person has not previously suffered in this way and have no known symptoms or history of such side effects. If you or anyone considering using this Game has suffers in this way, has a condition which makes this possible or has experienced similar symptoms, please consult a doctor before using this Game. If you or they are already using the Game please stop and consult a doctor.

If you or any part of you feels tired, fatigue or discomfort whilst playing games please stop and rest. If it continues after you stop playing please consult a doctor. If you have suffered or suffer from an injury playing games can aggravate it. In that case please consult a doctor. Failure to follow this advice may result in long term injury.

PLEASE FOLLOW THESE PRECAUTIONS WHENEVER USING YOUR GAME(S): Please do not:

sit or stand too close to the TV screen / monitor but sit or stand a safe distance away;
use this Game or play games if you are sick, sleep, or feel tired, fatigue or discomfort;
play in a room that is not well-lit;
play for too long at any one time, please take a 10- to 15-minute break every hour. Notice to parents and carers:

Please observe children whilst they play games. Please ensure that you and they following the precautions described above. If you or they experience dizziness, altered vision, eye or muscle twitching, involuntary movements, loss of awareness, disorientation, or convulsions or any other side effects PLEASE STOP ALL USE IMMEDIATELY and consult a doctor.
08:46 27/09/2013</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
