<POLICY modification_date="July 01, 2011" policy_url="http://bulbapedia.bulbagarden.net/wiki/Bulbapedia:Privacy_policy" website_category="Games" website_index="030" website_url="bulbagarden.net">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>From Bulbapedia, the community-driven Pokémon encyclopedia.
Bulbagarden.net recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of all information provided by users of Bulbagarden.net. We created the following policy guidelines with a fundamental respect for our users' right to privacy.
Contents [hide]
1 General
2 Information collected by Bulbagarden.net
3 Use of information
3.1 Contests
3.2 Cookies &amp; Advertising</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>General</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Bulbagarden.net uses reasonable precautions to keep the personal information disclosed to us secure and to disclose such information only to responsible third parties after permission from the user.
Bulbagarden.net is not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of websites to which we may provide links or the websites of our affiliates or advertisers.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Information collected by Bulbagarden.net</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Bulbagarden.net collects information about users during their registration for our newsletter and during their participation in certain activities on our website, including contests. When users request pages from our server, our Web server automatically collects some information about the users, including their IP addresses. These addresses are used by computers on the network to send the requested pages to users.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Use of information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Bulbagarden.net does not reveal any personal information that users provide to us to any third party without their permission.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Contests</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>By entering Bulbagarden.net contests, users consent to the use of their name in the announcement of the winners on the Bulbagarden.net site and/or Newsletter, and use of their name and likeness for advertising and/or promotional and/or marketing purposes. Users' contact information may also be used by Bulbagarden.net to notify the user they have won and to confirm their mailing address.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Cookies &amp; Advertising</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Bulbagarden.net may use user entered information in combination with site usage information to help display advertisements relevant to the users interest and navigation patterns. Bulbagarden.net may use cookies to help in tracking these patterns but does not store or collect any personal data in combination with user supplied information. Cookies are small text files that contain a string of alphanumeric characters. You can remove cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's “help” file. For more information about cookies please visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org/cookies/.
Bulbagarden.net uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
