<POLICY modification_date="November 01, 2012" policy_url="http://om.yr.no/sporsmal/" website_category="News" website_index="070" website_url="yr.no">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>FAQ
yr.no on your mobile

You will find a simple version of yr.no is adapted for mobiles on  m.yr.no . Open web / wap application on your phone. Click "Well web address" (or similar) and enter "m.yr.no" (without the www in front). Search page you are looking for and make a bookmark of the page you come to.

We have our own appar for iPhone and Android .

Do you have another phone and want to install yr.no? There are several private individuals who have made ​​software for mobile phones that fetches weather forecasts from yr.no Check out  tillegg.yr.no to see if you find something that fits for you!

Have more questions? Send a message to us

How do I use "My Places"?

We receive many questions about the use and problems with "My Places". We have created a small article explaining the most here: How do I use "My Places"?

Sun, Moon and darkness

You can find information about sunrise and sunset at each place on yr.no (below the animated map).

There can be up to 5 minutes discrepancy between sunrise / sunset on yr.no and Almanac for Norway.

yr.no has its own symbol for the dark months north of the Arctic Circle. Places when mørketidssymbola displayed on yr.no .

Color-blind and long-term forecasts on yr.no

Long-term forecasts on yr.no (eg.  forecast for Bodo ) are marked with how certain the forecasts are.

The labels are made by a color (red, yellow and green). The colors have been selected for the colorblind will be able to see them, and tested in several color-blind. In addition, the shape of the markings slightly different for each category so that one can understand marking even if one can not distinguish red / green.

If you have trouble getting really see color codes you can keep calm mouse over each color code. Then comes a text that tells whether the forecasts are quite safe (green), uncertain (yellow) or very unsafe (red).

How much snow is 1 mm rain?

Broadly considered one could say that 1 mm precipitation will provide about 1 inch of snow.

Read more:  Why are snow forecasts in millimeters?

Meteorology academic questions
When will notice and observations to date?

There is information about when the forecasts are updated at the top of each item page. Keep the mouse over the dashed web link, you'll get accurate information about what data is updated when.

Note: Data are updated every hour or less often, we always uses the last observation (see time). Radar image is updated fourth quarter or more frequently.

Why the difference of the forecasts of "overview", "forecast" and "Weather"?

Weather and precipitation forecasts debt always an interval. In the top of the table says how far this interval. If we sign 2 mm precipitation interval, this means that between the time and the six påfylgjande lessons, will come 2 mm rainfall.

How long forecast is for varies in the different tables. This means that symbols can vary considerably too. About the time we notice announces sun, sun and rain in six hours, will the main page just stand light rain for all six lessons combined.

Wind

Hover your mouse over the arrows in the air tables, so you get up wind speed in m / s

Wind direction and wind speed are dependent on very local conditions. The meteorological models that underlie the forecasts on yr.no will in some cases lead to low wind speeds and crazy wind. Continuous efforts to improve the models. There is an extensive task. The new research and powerful computers are expected to contribute to future improvements!

The main reason for this problem is that the models have a simplified description of the terrain and fjords and lakes. Where there is very local control of wind will not models describe this well enough. In addition, this simplistic description also provides an over-run braking of the wind in complex terrain.

We recommend that you read the meteorologist's forecast in addition to looking at the graphic warnings. Often meteorologist know when the models wind warnings are not good, and she can correct for this in its notice. As you gain experience, you will also even be able to recognize situations where the wind will differ from the forecasts on yr.no for your location.

The forecast is wrong!

If you find mistakes in our forecasts, we set greatly appreciate if you contact us.

Be as detailed as possible when you write to us: KVAR lies instead we notified errors, how long has the error was and WHAT is it wrong? If you have several examples, it is very useful when we need to find out what has gone wrong.

Thank you for helping us to figure out the error!

Send feedback about forecasts on yr.no

There is no correlation between the symbol and watersheds in map

Sometimes it happens that vêrsymbola on the maps show rainfall without the precipitation area over the city, and to show symbols sun even though the map indicates the precipitation area.

This occurs because rainfall areas will be updated continuously, while the symbols show the weather that is most representative of a time period. This time period is always at least three hours outside the northern Europe. When the weather is changing may vêrsymbola and precipitation areas not match.

Lightning

Lyndata is unfortunately not publicly available in Norway, so we can not offer lynvarsel or observations.

Place, language and spelling
Wrong place / places as missing in Norway

All Norwegian place yr.no is set by the State Authority.

Many places in Norway has several approved. In these cases uses yr.no only one of skrivemåtane.

During the animated map you will find a box where you can check what is approved and not approved for the place name.

Read more about Norwegian place yr.no and how you can contact the State Authority

International conflicts / disputed area abroad

From time to get another yr.no questions about how we handles contentious area and international territorial disputes. We want to emphasize that yr.no not take a position on international conflicts, but that we keep to the decision of the Ministry of Foreign Affairs and the United Nations.

Read about how yr.no handles disputed area .

Wrong place / places that lacks outside Norway

yr.no uses Geonames database as the main source for place abroad.

You can even correct errors or add new places in Geonames, it is both clear and concise.

Please note that it may take several months between each time we update our place names from the Geonames (this is a very time-consuming process).

Go to geonames.org (you can correct any inaccuracies in itself)

Read about how yr.no handles contentious area and international conflicts .

English / Bokmål

All notice on yr.no is available in Norwegian, Norwegian, Sami and Kven and Norwegian.

The other texts on yr.no is a mixture of Nynorsk and Bokmål. yr.no is a public website, and follow the law on the target user in the public service. In concubine Act should we spend at least 25 percent of each language variant, and we have too little nynorsk today.

Places, XML, JavaScript, etc.
Can I get weather forecasts and other weather data free from you?

Yes! Read more on  yr.no / Places .

Gadgets, as well as Vista, Firefox, Opera, etc.

yr.no offers not own addition to Vista, Firefox, Opera, etc today, and it is unlikely that we come to develop these services yourself.

It contains several different such additions and gadgets on tillegg.yr.no , which is a website where anyone the can publish their software they have established.

If you are good at programming, you can get  free data from us and create your own applications. If you have made ​​a good service, it's nice if you told us about it so others can also enjoy what you have created.

Other questions
Search questions and answers
Search questions and answers
Use the field to search in questions / answers

Search
Can not find the answer to your question?  Contact us !

Last updated 29 November 2012 at 6:01 p.m.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
