<POLICY modification_date="" policy_url="http://static.zara.net/static//pdfs/ZARA/privacy-policy/privacy-policy-en_ZARA-20131125.pdf" website_category="Business" website_index="071" website_url="zara.com">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>Zara´s Privacy Statement
1. Whenever You use this website, you will be subject to the Privacy Statement in force at all times, and You should review that text in order to check that You are in agreement with it. The provision of your data is voluntary, however, please note that if You do not provide us with the required personal data, we may not be able to provide the information, products or services You need or process your request.
2. Personal data You provide will be kept in a file under the responsibility of ITX FASHION LIMITED ("ITX") for the purposes of:
1. the performance and enforcement of the purchase and sale contract over the products You have purchased, or of any other contract between You and us; and
2. attending to Your requests.
3. You have the right to access and correct your personal data and request information about our data protection policies and procedures. ITX FASHION LIMITED, with registered address at Hainault House, 5th Floor, 69-71 Stephen´s Green, Dublin 2, Ireland, being in charge of the file, undertakes to keep your personal information confidential and to ensure the exercise of your access, rectification, cancellation and objection rights by sending a letter to the above referred address or to the registered address of Inditex, S.A., as provided in the paragraph below or by e-mail to funcionlopd@inditex.com , for the attention of "Función LOPD".
4. To fulfill the purposes above, we are required to disclose the information that You have provided to us to other companies in the Inditex Group located in Spain (with activities, both online and in-store, related to the sectors of decoration, textiles, finished clothing products and home decoration, other complimentary sectors such as cosmetics and leather goods, as well as the development and support of e-commerce business) which ITX forms part, and Industria de Diseño Textil, S.A. (Inditex, S.A.), the holding company of the Inditex Group with registered address at Avenida de la Diputación, Edificio Inditex, 15142 Arteixo (A Coruña), and we understand that by providing information in this website or otherwise to us, You expressly authorize us to disclose and process your information as described.
5. We also intend to use your name, email address, address or phone number to send you commercial communications (both online and in-stores) about decoration, textile, finished fashion, homeware and furniture, cosmetics, leather goods, lingerie, underwear, accessories, fragrances products and services of Zara and/ or of any other brands/companies belonging to the Inditex Group, including those with activities related to the development and support of e-commerce business. Zara may share your personal data with any other companies within the Inditex Group who provide decoration, textile, finished fashion, homeware and furniture, cosmetics, leather goods, lingerie, underwear, accessories, fragrances products and services, as well as the development and support of e-commerce business for direct marketing purposes. Your consent is
required before we do so. You can withdraw your consent by writing to the above referred address/e-mail of ITX FASHION LIMITED. You can change your preference in respect of receiving such communications by logging into the MY ACCOUNT section of this website and editing your preferences. You can unsubscribe at the Newsletter section.
6. The user (You) hereby guarantees that the personal data provided is true and accurate and undertakes to notify any change or alteration to the same. Any loss or damage caused to the website or to the person responsible for the web-site or to any third person through the provision of erroneous, inexact or incomplete information on the registration forms will be the exclusive responsibility of the User.
7. Cookies: We use cookies in this website, small text files with information on your navigation in this site whose principal objective is to improve your experience in the website. You can find further information on the cookies that we use, their purpose and other information of interest in the section Information on cookies.
By accepting this privacy policy you consent to the use of the cookies used in this website and which are described on the previously indicated page.
You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows You to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if You select this setting You may be unable to access certain parts of the Website or unable to avail of any of our services. Unless You have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when You log on to our site.
Information on cookies
What is a cookie?
A cookie is a small text file that a website places in your PC, telephone or any other device, with information on your navigation in that website. The cookies are necessary to facilitate navigation and to make it friendlier and they do not damage your computer.
Although in this policy the general term cookies is used since it is the principal method of storing information that this website uses, the browser's "local storage" space is used for the same purposes as the cookies. In this regard, all the information included in this section is also applicable to this "local storage".
For what are cookies used in this website?
The cookies are an essential part of how our website functions. The principal objectives of our cookies are to improve your navigational experience. For example, the cookies help us to identify you (if you are registered in our website), to remember your preferences (language, country, etc.) during the navigation and in future visits, to manage the shopping cart, to allow you to carry out on-line purchases, etc.
The information collected in the cookies also allows us to improve the website, by means of estimates on the numbers and patterns of use, the adaptation of the website to the users' individual interests, the improved speed of the searches, etc.
For what are the cookies NOT used in this website?
We do not store sensitive information of personal identification such as your address, password, credit card data, etc., in the cookies that we use. Neither do we use the cookies to guide advertising to our users according to your navigation nor for other advertising aims, not ours or of third parties.
Who uses the information stored in the cookies?
The information stored in the cookies of our website is used exclusively by us, with the exception of that of Google Analytics, which are used and managed by Google and by us for statistical aims, and the Payment Operation Analysis cookie, which is generated exclusively when a purchase is made, and it is analyzed by an external company with the objective of offering sufficient guarantees on the payment operations performed.
Can the use of cookies be deactivated?
Yes, the cookies can be deactivated. However, if you select this configuration, you might not be able to access certain parts of our website, it may cause less efficient navigation and you cannot take advantage of some of our services.
If you prefer to restrict, block or erase the cookies from this website, you can do so by modifying your browser's configuration. Although the parameterization of each browser is different, the configuration of the cookies is usually done in the "Preferences" or "Tools" menu. For more details on the configuration of the cookies in your browser, consult its "Help" menu.
What specific cookies use this website and for what purposes?
Below is a table with the cookies used by this website along with the purpose of each of them:
Identification and authentication cookies
These cookies are used to identify the user during the session, avoiding the user having to repeat authentication processes in the website and accelerating some processes of the website.
TITLE OF THE COOKIES
TECHNICAL NAME OF THE COOKIES
PURPOSE
User identification
WC_AUTHENTICATION_&lt;userid&gt;, WC_USERACTIVITY_&lt;userid&gt;
They are used to identify and authenticate the user. They also contain technical data of the user's session, such as, for example, connection timeout, session identifier, etc.Â
HTTP Session
JSESSIONID, "Local storage"
It identifies the http session of the user. It is common in all the web applications to identify a user's petitions in a session.
Cookies for navigation
These cookies serve for the user's navigation during the session, remembering the selections made, the pages of our website already visited, etc.
TITLE OF THE COOKIES
TECHNICAL NAME OF THE COOKIES
PURPOSE
User selections
WC_GENERIC_ACTIVITYDATA, WC_PERSISTENT
They store the session values selected by the user such as the store, language, currency, etc. With WC_PERSISTENT various sets of identifiers can exist if the user visits more than one store (country).
Selected store
WC_ACTIVEPOINTER
It permits remembering the selected store (country) by the user during navigation and purchase.
Selected products
WC_filterManager
It permits remembering the filter established by the user in the grid of products during navigation and purchase.
Last category
WC_LastCat
It allows remembering the last category seen by the user.
Shopping cart
"Local storage"
They store information on the mini-shopping cart of purchases, as well as the identification information of the user associated with this shopping cart.
Session
WC_SESSION_ESTABLISHE
It allows identifying the start of the session for the
start
D
loading of the web page.
Protocols
socControl
It allows managing changes between secure (protocol) and insecure (http) domain.Â
Cookies for favorites
The cookies allow remembering certain user selections in the following accesses to the web page.
TITLE OF THE COOKIES
TECHNICAL NAME OF THE COOKIES
PURPOSE
Favorite stores
WC_favPhysicalShops
It allows the favorite stores of the user in subsequent accesses to the web page.Â
Last store
WC_ZaraStoreId
It allows the last store (country) visited by the user in subsequent accesses to the web page.
Last products
WC_lastVisitedProducts
This cookie permits remembering the last products seen by the user for subsequent accesses to the web page.
Cookies for navigation analysis
These cookies obtain generic information on the user's accesses to the website (not to its content) in order to provide us subsequently with aggregated information of these accesses for statistical purposes.
TITLE OF THE COOKIES
TECHNICAL NAME OF THE COOKIES
PURPOSE
Origin
WC_GASource
It is used to know the origin of a user upon reaching a page of this website, for example, if it comes from a page of product detail from a product grid, from the search engine or from an external website.
Google Analytics (third-party cookie)
__utma, __utmb, __utmc, __utmd, __utmv, __utmz
They allow monitoring the website by means of the Google Analytics tool, which is a service provided by Google for obtaining information of the accesses of the users to the websites. Some of the data saved for subsequent analyses are: number of times a user visits the website, dates of the first and last visit of the user, duration of the visits, from what page the user accessed the website,Â what search engine the user used to reach the website or what link he clicked on,
from what place of the world the user accesses, etc. The configuration of these cookies is predetermined by the service offered by Google, for which reason we suggest that you consult the privacy page of Google Analytics, http://www.google.com/intl/es/analytics/privacyoverview.html, to obtain further information on the cookies that it uses and how to disable them (in the understanding that we are not responsible for the content or the veracity of the third-party websites).
Cookies for purchase analysis
These cookies allow compiling information on the device from which the purchase is made in this website for the purpose of verifying that these operations offer sufficient guarantees for the clients. At no time do these cookies include sensitive information such as credit card data.
TITLE OF THE COOKIES
TECHNICAL NAME OF THE COOKIES
PURPOSE
Purchase device (third-party cookie)
thx_guid
It allows identifying solely the device (PC, telephone, etc.) from which the purchases are made in this website for its subsequent analysis with the purpose of being able to offer our clients sufficient guarantees in the purchase operations. The information contained in this cookie is collected by an external company in order to conduct these analyses.
NOTE: In the above table the information that is not stored exactly in a cookie but rather in the browser space called "local storage", but whose processing and purpose is similar to that of a cookie is identified as "local storage".
This list will be updated with the greatest speed possible as the website services change that are offered on this website. However, occasionally during this updating it could occur that the list no longer includes a cookie, although it always deals with cookies with identical aims as those that are recorded in this list.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
