<POLICY modification_date="August 01, 2013" policy_url="https://support.paddypower.com/app/answers/detail/a_id/9" website_category="Games" website_index="070" website_url="www.paddypower.com">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>Privacy &amp; Cookie Policy

Updated 16 August 2013</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Introduction &amp; Who We Are</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>1.1 The website www.paddypower.com and its associated Paddy Power branded websites (the "Websites"), the Mobile, Tablet and TV Betting Apps (including the Rollercasino brand at www.rollercasino.com and www.rollercasino.mobi and any other Paddy Power Apps all of which together are referred to as the "Betting Apps"), Paddy Power Text Betting ("Text Betting") and Paddy Power Dial-a-Bet ("Dial-a-Bet") are operated and controlled by Paddy Power Isle of Man Limited ("PPIOM") and Paddy Power Online Limited ("PPOL").  PPIOM and PPOL are wholly owned subsidiaries of Paddy Power plc., of Power Tower, Belfield Office Park, Beech Hill Road, Clonskeagh, Dublin 4,  Ireland.   Paddy Power plc.  and all entities within its group of companies shall be referred to herein as "Paddy Power".

1.2 Together, the Websites, the Betting Apps, Dial-a-Bet and Text Betting are referred to collectively herein as the "Paddy Power Services".  Together, Paddy Power Services and the Additional Gaming Services (as defined in the Paddy Power Remote Gambling Terms &amp; Conditions) are referred to collectively herein as the "Services".

1.3 This Privacy and Cookie Policy applies to the Services referred to above as well as other services and websites not expressly referred to that are provided by Paddy Power, including, without limitation, www.paddypowerpoker.com, www.paddypowercasino.com, www.paddypowerplayer.com, www.rollercasino.com and www.betdash.com (which websites are referred to together as the "Websites").

1.4 All customers who registered for any of the Services prior to 8 March 2010 are registered and transacting with PPIOM.  All customers that register for any of the Services on or after 8 March 2010 are registered (or will be registering, in the case of new customers) and transacting with PPOL.

1.5 This Privacy and Cookie Policy sets out the basis on which any personal information we collect from you or that you provide to us will be processed by us.  Paddy Power has created this Privacy and Cookie Policy in order to demonstrate our commitment to preserving the privacy of all visitors to our Websites and customers of our Services.  We are committed to ensuring that all Services and activities made available through our Websites are provided in a safe and secure environment.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Acceptance of Privacy and Cookie Policy</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>2.1 Your use of the Services will constitute acceptance of the then current Privacy and Cookie Policy, to include any amendments thereto.  Please read this policy carefully to ensure that you understand our views and practices regarding the capture, retention, processing and transfer (where applicable) of your information.  If you do not agree to accept and be bound by the Privacy and Cookie Policy, please discontinue your use of the Services.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Changes to Privacy and Cookie Policy</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>3.1 Paddy Power reserves the right to amend the Privacy and Cookie Policy at any time.  Any such revision will be binding and effective immediately on posting notification of such changes on the Website.  The date on which the then current Privacy and Cookie Policy came into force will be as stated at the top of this Privacy and Cookie Policy.  Please check this Privacy and Cookie Policy frequently for updates.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Information we may collect about you</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>4.1 We collect information about you during the account registration process for any of our Services.  This information may include, but is not limited to your name, postal address, e-mail address, phone number, credit/debit card details and any other mandatory details as might be requested from you for the purpose of registration and/or continued use of our Services.

4.2 We may also collect and process the following data about you during the course of  your use of our Services:
(a) if you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence;
(b) your entry details for a competition or promotion;
(c) details of your visits to our Services and the resources and webpages that you access including, without limitation, traffic data, location data and other communication data (including IP address).  We do not extract any personal information (e.g. email address or name) that may be in a web browser's user preference file;
(d) technical information relating to the device that you use to access our Services;
(e) information and communications on forums on the Websites, including chat rooms and message boards;
(f) information we collect using cookies stored on your device about how you use our Services and/or selected third party websites.  For more information on cookies please refer to section 8 below;
(g) where you communicate or share information with Us or other users of our Services through player forums, message boards, profile comments, in-game challenges and chat messaging with game operators or other users;
(h) your telephone conversations - either to place a bet or a customer service call - these may be recorded both to assist us in training and in quality management, and to allow for the speedy resolution of queries; and
(i) your betting, gaming, payments and other account transactions – these are routinely analysed so as to assist us in improving the Services we provide to you.

You acknowledge and consent to the recording and retention of such information for these purposes.

4.3 Our Services are not intended for individuals under the age of 18 and we do not knowingly record or retain any personal information from such individuals. In the event that we inadvertently gather personal information in relation to a minor, we will take reasonable measures to promptly close any relevant accounts and remove any records where possible, other than such information as will allow us to identify and prevent future access from such individuals.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>How we use your information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>5.1 The information that we collect is used by Us in order to process your transactions and requests and for any other purposes set out herein.  This processing includes, in certain circumstances, the transfer of your information to our third party data processors who assist with the performance of certain Services or elements thereof.  Your information may be processed in the following ways:

(a) for general account management and processing of your transactions via your banking service provider;
(b) for the provision of betting services;
(c) to help identify you;
(d) to verify your age and accuracy of your registration details, including disclosure of such information to third parties e.g. financial institutions and third party reference agencies;
(e) to serve appropriate and tailored marketing material and content via SMS, email, phone, push notification, post or otherwise, in accordance with your marketing preferences;
(f) to help diagnose system problems and to administer our Website;
(g) to gather broad demographic information about you, such as determining whether you are a user from outside the UK;
(h) to monitor and improve our Services;
(i) to carry out customer research, testing and analysis;
(j) to carry out risk management;
(k) to detect and report fraud, cheating and money laundering; and
(l) to enable us to comply with any legal or regulatory requirements.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Facebook In-Play App - Use, sharing and notification of your information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>6.1 As with any social network, please be aware that the Facebook In-Play App involves the sharing of certain data with the rest of the community in that network.

6.2 For users of the Facebook In-Play App we may also collect and process, as allowed by you through the Facebook App authentication process, certain additional information from Facebook, including;

(a) Your first and last name;
(b) Your profile picture or its URL;
(c) Your user ID number, which is linked to publicly available information as name and profile photo;
(d) The user ID numbers and other public data of your friends;
(e) The login email you provided to Facebook when you registered;
(f) Your physical location and that of your access devices;
(g) Your likes and your friends likes;
(h) Your gender; and
(i) Your date of birth.

6.3 For users of the Facebook In-Play App we may also share or notify your information, as authorised by you through the App and Facebook settings, through a number of features within the App and via auto-posting to your Facebook profile. The App may restrict the quantity of notifications that are posted on a daily basis so each In-Play activity may not automatically be posted to your profile. Notification types will include, but are not limited to:

(a) Bet placement (including those where a free bet is used);
(b) Bet win (including single and multiple bets;
(c) Challenges submitted, won and lost;
(d) New followers; and
(e) Player profile heat index changes.

6.4 We consider elements of the data outlined in 6.2 and 6.3 above to be public information, which may be accessed by the rest of the community, including your friends, followers or other users of the App. However, we also treat certain other information as private, which will never be visible or accessible to the rest of the community. This private information includes your account balance, bet stake amount, winning or loss amount for any bet.

6.5 Any user of the App can choose to follow you. Where someone chooses to follow you, you will receive an individual notification to this effect within the App. You do not have the ability to restrict or control which individuals are permitted to follow you. Your followers, friends and other users of the In-Play App will have the ability to access your In-Play profile and public information including details of challenges, awards, heat index, your position on leaderboards, a limited view of your betting history, competition standings and achievements.

6.6 If you do not wish to share certain data with the community and the existing control settings within the In-Play App or Facebook do not enable you to restrict that sharing, please discontinue your use of this service and we suggest instead that you use our other non-social networking Services such as www.paddypower.com.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Marketing Communications</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>7.1 As part of the initial account registration process you are provided with an opportunity to record your marketing preferences.  We endeavour at all times to respect these and not send you communications in contravention of your wishes.

7.2 Where you have agreed to receive such communications we may use your information and personal details to contact you with marketing messages by SMS, email, phone, post or otherwise.  We will do this during the period of your relationship with us and, unless specifically instructed otherwise by you, for a reasonable period of time after the relationship has ended in order to inform you about products, services, promotions and special offers which we feel may be of interest to you.  These marketing messages will provide you with information about our own products and services and information about products and services provided by our selected partners and third parties.

7.3 With your consent we may also send push notifications to your mobile device to provide game updates, communicate offers, promotions and other relevant messages. You can manage push notifications from your device's settings page for the relevant App.

7.4 You can opt out from receiving or opt in to receive such marketing communications in future by contacting our support team through one of the options available in our Help Centre.  You will also be able to opt out by following the respective unsubscribe or opt out mechanisms detailed in our electronic communications.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Cookies</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>8.1 Certain information about you, including personal information, may be collected through the use of cookies when you use our Services and/or visit selected third party sites.  Some of these cookies are essential for the Websites to operate and ensure that we provide the services you requested.  By using our Services you agree to the use of certain non-essential cookies unless you set your browser to reject them.

8.2 A cookie is a small text file that is stored on your computers hard drive or browser.  We use cookies and the information contained therein for a number of purposes including but not limited to:
• tracking the duration of visits and content accessed; and
• storing frequently used user information to personalise your online experience and ease the log-in process.

8.3 Set out below is an indicative list of the types of cookies we use:
Cookie type 	Purpose 	More information
Visitor ID Cookie 	An anonymous identifier used to recognise a visitor across visits. 	It may be used to identify repeat visits and analyse cross visit behaviour.
Tracking Cookie 	An account related ID used to recognise customers and maintain your session on site. 	It may be used to link site usage information with transactional information when analysing and optimising the user experience.
Customisation Cookie 	Used to customise your experience 	A unique ID used to recognise you as a returning visitor and customise your experience on our Websites.
Testing Cookies 	Anonymous cookie used to randomly serve variants of content and to maintain a visitor's view of that content. 	It may also be used to record a variants performance in achieving goals such as helping visitors to register
Analytics Cookies 	These are used to collect information about how visitors use our Websites. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the Websites. 	The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the Websites, where visitors have come to the Websites from and the pages they visited.

8.4 You may block cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies.  However, if you use your browser settings to block all cookies (including essential cookies) you may not be able to access all or parts of our Websites.  Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies as soon you visit our Site.  Further information on cookies and how websites use them can be obtained at www.cookiecentral.com

8.5 Please note: Due to certain technical constraints the Paddy Power site(s) cannot recognise any cookie preferences in Microsoft Internet Explorer 10. In order for your browser level cookie preferences to be detected please access our site(s) from an alternative browser.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Sharing and Transfer of Information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>9.1 Paddy Power may share customer information with trusted third parties in order to create a safer environment and to enhance the end-user experience.

9.2 In order to prevent fraud, cheating and money laundering we may disclose your information and betting and gaming history to third parties including, but not limited to, any relevant regulator, gaming and sporting bodies, financial institutions and law enforcement agencies or any other body that deals with the investigation of alleged offences.

9.3 We may disclose your personal information to third parties if some or all of our assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by us may be one of the transferred assets.

9.4 We may disclose your personal information to third parties if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation.

9.5 Paddy Power plc operates businesses in multiple jurisdictions some of which are not located in the European Economic Area (“EEA”).  Countries outside the EEA do not always have strong data protection laws.  We may from time to time transfer your data from one Paddy Power company to another one or to one of our authorised service providers for customer service, business management or for any of the purposes described herein.  We will ensure that each Paddy Power company and their service providers process your information under strict contractual instruction, in a secure manner and in accordance with this Privacy and Cookie Policy.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Security</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>10.1 Paddy Power recognises that online security is an area of vital importance for all our customers.  It is imperative that you should have full confidence that your personal details are secure before you register an account.  We employ security measures to protect your information from access by unauthorised persons and to prevent unlawful processing, accidental loss, destruction and damage.  Paddy Power uses at least 128 bit SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption when transmitting sensitive information across the internet, which is certified by Thawte.  This means that all personal and financial information sent to and from the Website are encrypted in accordance with good industry practice.

10.2 In order to protect both ourselves and our customers from identity theft we may verify the information you have provided with our banking institutions over secure lines.  Again this is carried out in accordance with our data protection obligations.

10.3 Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our websites, you are responsible for keeping the password, as well as any means to manage the password such as a registered email address, secure and confidential at all times.

10.4 As the security of all communications via the internet is not completely secure Paddy Power cannot guarantee the security of any information that you disclose online.  You accept the inherent security implications of using the internet and Paddy Power will accept no liability for any direct, consequential, incidental, indirect, or punitive losses or damages arising out of such an occurrence.

10.5 While Paddy Power follows best practice, including but not limited to implementing administrative, technical and physical measures to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft and misuse you should also take personal steps to protect the security of your data both physically and electronically by following common best practice procedures such as:
(a) running Anti-Virus software and keeping it up to date;
(b) applying operating system, web browser and other security updates;
(c) ensuring your PC or other device is not left unattended whilst logged into our Websites; and
(d) using strong passwords for all Services and logins.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Accuracy and Access to Information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>11.1 You are entitled and we require you to have any inaccurate information corrected so please ensure that you notify us of any updates, amendments and corrections to your information by logging into the ‘My Account' section of your online account and amending your ‘Contact Details' section or by contacting our support team through one of the options available in our Help Centre. .

11.2 You also have a right to request a copy of any personal information that we hold about you.  Should you wish to make such a request you should contact us in writing at: Paddy Power Plc, Power Tower, Belfield Office Park, Beech Hill Road, Clonskeagh, Dublin 4, Ireland marked “Data Access Request”.  You should include adequate information to identify yourself and such other relevant information that will reasonably assist us in fulfilling your request.  Your request will be dealt with as soon as possible.  We are entitled to charge an administration fee for processing such requests.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Retention and Disposal</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>12.1 We only keep your information for as long as is necessary for the purpose for which it was originally obtained.  Please note that we may be required in certain circumstances to retain your information indefinitely (for example under our procedures on responsible gambling and self-exclusion).

12.2 We will take all necessary steps to ensure that the privacy of information is maintained upon disposal.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>External links</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>13.1 The Websites contain links to other sites.  Paddy Power is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
