<POLICY modification_date="" policy_url="http://www.yoox.com/cms/legal/privacypolicy.asp" website_category="Shopping" website_index="059" website_url="yoox.com">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>Welcome to our web site ("yoox.com"). Please read our Privacy Policy carefully.

This Privacy Policy applies when you visit or surf our web site without purchasing any product, when you register with yoox.com, and when you use our services for purchasing products. If you haven't already done so, please also read the General Terms and Conditions of Use of yoox.com containing relevant information on privacy and on the security systems used by the web site.

yoox.com is managed by YOOX S.p.A. ("YOOX"), its registered office is located in Via Nannetti, 1 - 40069, Zola Predosa (Bologna), Italy, business register number, tax code and VAT number 02050461207, fully paid share capital of EUR 580,273.72.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>1. Our Policy</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Everyone has the right to protection of his/her personal data.

YOOX respects its users' right to be informed regarding the collection of and other operations involving their personal data. In using data, that may directly or indirectly identify you personally, you will apply the principle of strict necessity.

For this reason, we have designed yoox.com in such a way that the use of your personal data will be kept to a minimum and will not exceed the purposes for which your personal data was collected and/or processed; we do not process your personal data when we can provide you with services through the use of anonymous data (such as marketing research made for improving our services) or by other means which allow YOOX to identify you a part from when it is strictly necessary or upon request of the competent public authorities or the police (as, for example, in case of traffic data or your IP address).

YOOX determines the purposes and means for the processing your personal data, including security measures, as YOOX controls yoox.com users' personal data. This Privacy Policy provides you with all information needed to understand how we collect data which may identify yoox.com's users. For further information on our Privacy Policy, please contact us at our e-mail address privacy@yoox.com or at YOOX S.p.A., at our registered office located in Via Nannetti, 1 - 40069, Zola Predosa (Bologna), Italy.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>2. Who Processes Your Personal Data</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>YOOX controls the use of yoox.com users' personal data; YOOX autonomously determines the purposes and means of use, including security measures, for the protection of personal data. For organizational and operational purposes only, we have appointed certain entities that will also process personal data belonging to yoox.com's users, such purposes which are strictly connected to the performance of services on yoox.com, including the sale of products.

The above mentioned processors have been chosen by YOOX because of their experience in processing personal data and they provide sufficient guarantees in respect of compliance with data processing law (including the technical security measures governing the processing to be carried out). In processing the personal data of yoox.com's users, the processors shall act only on instructions from YOOX. We regularly ensure that our processors comply with our instructions and that they provide sufficient guarantees on their full compliance with the provisions on personal data processing.

Some of the processors of your personal data are: YOOX ASIA Ltd, a subsidiary of YOOX S.p.A., having an address at GFL, 2nd FL, 3rd FL 16th FL, Western Plaza, No. 3 San On Street and No. 2 Tin Hau Road, Tuen Mun, N.T., Hong Kong ("YOOX ASIA"). We provide YOOX ASIA, by electronic and papers means, with customers' address and other personal data for the purpose of performing the agreements entered into between Users (who browse and/or purchase products from this Site) and YOOX;
United Parcel Service, for purposes relevant to shipping and delivering products purchased on yoox.com;
BT Italia S.p.A. for purposes relevant to the housing of YOOX servers.

Please contact our Customer Care or send us an e-mail at privacy@yoox.com if you would like to receive a full list of our data processors.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>3. How Do We Use Personal Data and for What Purposes</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Your personal data is collected and processed by YOOX, both as users and registered customers, for purposes which are strictly connected to the use of the web site, its services and to the purchase of products on the web site. However, your personal data may also be used for other processing operations within the limits of such purposes.


In particular, your personal data shall be processed for the following purposes:

• when you register with our website we collect your personal data (for example, your personal details, user ID and password, e-mail address, gender, favorite designer) through the relevant registration form (MYOOX) and we process the data in order to provide you with your requested services in reserved access areas of yoox.com and in order to send you our YOOXNEWS, when specifically requested;
• when you require Customer Care services, we collect and process your personal data (for example, your user ID and password) for purposes strictly necessary to provide you with customer care services relevant to yoox.com services and to assist in the purchasing of products on yoox.com;
• when you are executing purchasing procedures for products sold on yoox.com, we collect and process your personal data (such as, for example, personal details, e-mail address, address, credit card numbers, bank code, tax code and telephone number) on your order form only for the purpose of selling the products ordered by you;
• payments, including anti-fraud checks for credit card payments; in this case, the data provided during the order process (first name, surname, address, credit card number, delivery address if different from billing address) will be sent to the supervisor responsible for anti-fraud control, ThreatMetrix Inc., located in the U.S., and will be processed strictly for that purpose (see also the section "Data supervisors");
• when you require technical assistance, we collect your personal data in order to provide you with information on net-surfing,  Internet browsing or viewing and downloading web pages;
• when creating your Dream Box, we process your personal data in order to customize our services for the purchase of products on yoox.com, and when it is specifically requested, we process your data to render your Dream Box searchable for other registered MYOOX users within your same country
• when you apply for the publication of your photograph and picture on yoox.com, we process your personal data (for example, your name, your image and your suggestions) only with your consent and as testimony to yoox.com services:

-when accessing the Friends service of MYOOX, your personal data will be processed in order to provide you with the services you have requested and, with your own consent, to make your personal data available to the other users of the Friends network that you have authorized.
- with regards to the Première Service, your personal data will be processed, with your own consent, in order to send you information regarding the availability of items you have indicated.

Your personal data is mostly processed by electronic means and in some circumstances by paper-based means, when, for example, the processing of your personal data is required in order to prevent fraud against yoox.com. Your personal data shall be stored in a way which allows YOOX to identify you for the period that is strictly necessary for the purposes for which the data was collected and subsequently processed and, in any case, in accordance with applicable law.

Please report any modification or amendment of your personal data to privacy@yoox.com in order to ensure that your personal data is always accurate and kept up-to-date and however adequate and not exceeding the purposes for which your personal data was collected and/or processed.

Your personal data shall not be disclosed to third parties for purposes which are not permitted by law or without your explicit consent. Your personal data may only be disclosed to third parties when it is necessary in order to process an order. For example, your personal data is disclosed to Banca Sella S.p.A. for the performance of electronic distance payment services, through credit/debit card, when you purchase a product on yoox.com. Moreover, your data may be disclosed to the police or to judicial authorities, according to law and upon a formal request by such entities, for example in the event YOOX needs to prevent fraud on yoox.com (anti-fraud services). Data processors will also have access to your personal data, as stated in paragraph 2, for the specific purposes stated in the same paragraph. In all the above circumstances, your consent for data processing is not required.

Your personal data contained in the Dream Box, provided that you have decided to activate the Dream Box service by your own consent, may be rendered accessible and visible to other registered users of MYOOX within your same country who use the search service Public Dream Boxes.

The data contained in the Dream Box that will be rendered visible to other users of this service are the following:

- your name and surname
- your birthday (day, month,) if entered
- any information entered by you in the blank field, with the purpose of simplifying the Public Dream Box searches (favourite designer, etc)
- the photo associated with your profile (if attached)
- your city (if entered)

Furthermore, any items you have placed in your Dream Box will also be visible to other users.

Your personal data contained in MYOOX, provided that you have decided to activate the FRIENDS service of MYOOX by your own consent, may be rendered accessible and visible to the other users of the FRIENDS network that you have indicated or authorized.

The data that will be rendered visible to other users of this service are the following:
- your name and surname
- your birthday (day, month), if entered
- any information entered by you in the blank field, with the purpose of simplifying the Public Dream Box searches (favourite designer, etc)
- the photo associated with your profile (if attached)
- your city (if entered)
- your e-mail address
- your preferred delivery address (that you have entered in the Address Book and indicated as the default address)

Furthermore, any items you have placed in your Dream Box will also be visible to other users

Your personal data may be disseminated to the public after receiving your approval and only for the supply of services on yoox.com, for example, in order to allow YOOX, upon your request, to post your photos and suggestions on yoox.com, as testimony of yoox.com.

Your personal data will not be transferred abroad to any countries, which do not ensure an adequate level of protection of individuals. Should the above be necessary in order to supply services or to execute a contract with YOOX for the purchase of products, the transfer of your personal data to such countries, shall be carried out only after the execution of specific contracts between YOOX and such entities, according to laws and applicable regulations.

We wish to inform you that YOOX shall process its users' personal data for purposes that are strictly connected to the supply of services on yoox.com, execution of contracts related to the sale and purchase of products on yoox.com and, after receiving your consent, in order to send to you information on new commercial initiatives which are strictly connected to the web site's activities and services.

YOOX shall process your personal data for direct marketing purposes, also by e-mail, only after receiving your consent.

YOOX may have access to third parties' personal data which was directly disclosed by its users to YOOX, for example when a user bought a product to be sent to a friend, when the user paying the purchase price of a product is different from the recipient of such product, or when a user wishes to recommend to a friend a service of yoox.com or the sale of a particular product.

In all of the above cases, please make sure you receive the consent of such individuals before disclosing their personal data to YOOX and make sure you informed such individuals about this Privacy Policy, since you will be the only person liable in connection with the disclosure of information and data relevant to such third parties (and with any other incompatible and unlawful use) if they have not provided you with their consent. We inform you that the consent of such third party individuals is not required if personal data belonging to the above individuals has been disclosed to YOOX for the execution of a sale and purchase contract with YOOX, on their exclusive behalf.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>4. What Happens if You Do Not Disclose Your Personal Data to YOOX</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Your personal data supplied to YOOX (in particular, your personal details, your e-mail address, your address, your credit card numbers and bank code and your telephone number), are necessary for the processing of your order for the purchase of products on yoox.com, to supply other services provided on the web site upon your request, or when your personal data needed to carry out obligations arising out of applicable laws or regulations.

The refusal to provide YOOX with some of your personal data necessary for performing the above purposes, may consequently prevent YOOX from processing your order for the purchase of products sold on yoox.com or from supplying other services provided on yoox.com, as for example Customer Care services, to send the YOOXNEWS, to use the Dream Box, to send a flower to a friend, to recommend a product to a friend, to post your photograph on the home page, or to carry out the obligations arising out of laws and other regulations. Failing to provide data may imply, in some cases, a legitimate and justified reason for YOOX's refusal to process your order for the purchase of products sold on yoox.com or to provide services on yoox.com.

Disclosure of further personal data to YOOX, other than that required in order to fulfill legal or contractual obligations, or in order to provide the services required, is, on the contrary, optional and does not have any effect on the use of the web site and of its services or on the purchase of products on yoox.com (as for example, in the event that we ask you the name of your favorite designer).

In some circumstances and if required, from time to time, we will duly inform you if personal data you are disclosing to YOOX is compulsory or optional. We will point out to you whether the disclosure of your data is compulsory or optional by marking with an appropriate font (*), the information that is compulsory or data which is needed required in order to provide the required services on yoox.com and for the purchase of products on yoox.com. Failing to disclose optional personal data will not imply any obligation or disadvantage to our users.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>5. To Whom Your Personal Data Will Be Disclosed</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Personal data will be disclosed to third party companies which provide, on behalf of YOOX, specific services as Data Processors or to other recipients of personal data collected by YOOX, which autonomously process your personal data only for the performance of a contract for the purchase of products on yoox.com (such as, for example, Banca Sella S.p.A.) and only when such purpose does not exceed the purposes for which your personal data was collected and subsequently processed and, in any case, according to applicable laws and regulations.

Personal data will not be disclosed to third parties or disseminated or transferred, without informing our users of such disclosure/dissemination/transfer and without their consent, when required by law.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>6. How Do We Collect Your Data on yoox.com</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>When you are using yoox.com, some personal data might be collected automatically (through the so-called "cookies"), for example, when we automatically collect users' IP addresses and other information regarding the users' data traffic or the users' preferences in the choice of services provided on this web site and of the products purchased through the provided services. This information and data are collected directly and automatically by the web site as part of its operational functions. This information and data are then processed in a collective and anonymous way for commercial purposes in order to optimize the services provided on yoox.com for the needs and preferences of the web site's users.

In other circumstances, YOOX directly collects personal data and information from its users when they register on-line with yoox.com or when they send purchase orders of products sold on the web site in order to finalize e-commerce transactions.

YOOX collects personal data on each individual who is interested in a job position with YOOX, in the specific area called Jobs, where each user may access and provide his/her data for recruitment purposes. YOOX will process such data only for the above purposes, according to applicable laws. In this latter case and under no circumstances YOOX will disclose personal data to third parties.

Moreover, we collect personal data in the Press Room area in order to process requests for information from journalists and from media and press agencies and in order to send the Press Letter, upon a specific request and after the performance of yoox.com's registration process.

YOOX reserves the right to eliminate all MYOOX accounts and their relevant information in the case of content that is illicit or damaging to YOOX's image and/or of their products or third parties; data that promotes illegal or defamatory activities; pornographic content; content that induces violence or promotes racial, sexual, or religious discrimination. Finally, we collect personal data of third parties interested in starting business relationships with YOOX only for such purposes.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>7. Security Measures</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We have adopted security measures to protect personal data against accidental or unlawful destruction, accidental loss, alteration, unauthorized disclosure or access, and against all other unlawful forms of data processing, as provided in our Privacy Policy.

Nevertheless, YOOX cannot guarantee that the security measures adopted for the protection of the web site and for data and information transmission on yoox.com will prevent or exclude any risk of unauthorized access or of loss of data. It is advisable that your computer is provided with software devices for the protection of network data transmission/receipt (such as updated antivirus systems), and that your Internet services provider has taken appropriate measures for the security of network data transmission (such as, for example, firewalls and anti-spam filtering).</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>8. Cookies</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>yoox.com uses automatic systems of data collection, such as cookies. A cookie is a device transmitted to the hard disk of an Internet user; it does not contain intelligible information but it allows linking between an Internet user to his/her personal information provided by the user on yoox.com. Cookies are disseminated by our servers and no one may gain access to the information contained therein. Only YOOX processes information collected by cookies, in a collective and anonymous way, in order to optimize its services and its web site for the needs and preferences of its users.

We have provided cookies in connection to functions such as browsing the catalogue, purchasing products on-line and supplying "MYOOX" services.

As you know, each Internet browser allows the deletion of cookies after each session. Your Internet browser contains instructions on how to carry out these procedures of deletion. Please access the information on your Internet browser if you wish to delete cookies.

The acceptance of automatic procedures of collection of data and the use of cookies are necessary for the use of the web site and its services, including the purchase of products. If you have started the procedure of deleting cookies, YOOX cannot ensure that all web pages of yoox.com will be displayed or that certain services will be supplied such as, for example, storage or display on the web pages of products you chose when you were finalizing the on-line purchasing processes.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>9. Opt-in/Opt out</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>YOOX processes your personal data only after receiving your consent, freely expressed, in order to send you advertising material and direct marketing or other commercial communications which do not fall within the services provided by YOOX, also via e-mail, upon the user's request (such as, for example, the transmission of the YOOXNEWS or publication of your photo on yoox.com).

Each time your consent is required, we will inform you in advance and we will give you the option to either provide or refuse your consent for the use of your personal data, including your e-mail address, for the above purposes, by ticking the appropriate boxes.

We wish to inform you that law provides that your consent is not necessary and that YOOX may process your personal data without your consent when such processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which YOOX is subject; or such processing is necessary for processing an order with its users (such as, for example, if you purchased products on yoox.com or if you asked to use specific services through our web site).

In any case, we wish to inform you that YOOX ensures its users that, even when prior consent is not necessary, users may exercise, at any time, their right not to receive future communications connected to particular services upon request, such as for example the YOOXNEWS.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>10. Your Right to Access Personal Data and Further Rights</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>You are entitled to obtain, at any time, confirmation from YOOX as to whether or not data relating to you is being processed, whether the data is not yet registered, and the communication in intelligible form of the data undergoing processing.

Moreover, you are entitled to receive from YOOX information on the source of your personal data; the purposes and way of processing your personal data; the logic involved in any electronic data processing; details of the data controller and of the data processors and the names of subjects and categories of subjects to whom your personal data may be disclosed or who may access your personal data like, for example, the names of data processors. You can easily find all of the above information in our Privacy Policy.

You are entitled to obtain at any time from YOOX:

a) the updating, rectification or, when you have an interest in, the integration of your personal data;
b) the deletion, the transformation into an anonymous form or blocking of your personal data, (unlawful processed), including data which does not need to be stored for the purposes for which it has been collected and subsequently processed;
c) the confirmation that the operations under letters a) and b) have been reported, (together with the contents of the same), to whom the data was disclosed or disseminated, except when it becomes impossible or if it means exceeding the protection of the relevant right.

You are entitled to object, in all or in part:

a) for legitimate reasons, to the processing of your personal data, even if it is related to the purposes for which it was collected;
b) to the processing of your personal data for advertising or direct marketing purposes or in order to carry out marketing researches or commercial communications.

You may freely and at any time exercise your rights, provided that you do so in compliance with applicable laws, by sending your request to YOOX at the following e-mail address privacy@yoox.com. We will reply to you in order to satisfy your request.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>11. Links to Other Web Sites</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>yoox.com contains links to other web sites which may have no connection with yoox.com or with YOOX.

YOOX does not control or monitor such web sites or their web content. YOOX shall not be held liable for the web content of such sites and for the rules adopted by them in respect of your privacy and the processing of your personal data while you are visiting those web sites. Please, pay attention when you connect to these web sites through the links provided on yoox.com and read  their terms and conditions of use and their privacy policy carefully. yoox.com's Privacy Policy does not apply to the web sites managed by third parties.
yoox.com provides links to other web sites exclusively to help its users in their searches and net-surfing activities and to allow links to other web sites on the Internet. When YOOX provides links to other web sites, YOOX does not recommend the use of these web sites and does not provide any guarantees to their web content or to the services and products supplied and sold by these web sites to Internet users.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>12. Contacts</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>If you wish to receive further information on how YOOX processes your personal data, please send an e-mail to the following e-mail address privacy@yoox.com.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>13. Governing Law</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>This Privacy Policy is governed by Italian law and, in particular, by the Italian Personal Data Protection Code (legislative decree no. 196 of 30 June 2003) which governs the processing of personal data - also held overseas - carried out by anyone who is domiciled or has registered offices in Italy.

The Italian Personal Data Protection Code guarantees that processing of personal data will be carried out in compliance with fundamental rights and freedom of individuals, as well as of their dignity, with particular reference to confidentiality, identity and to the right to personal data protection.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>14. Companies of the Yoox Group</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>YOOX operates on the Internet through yoox.com and in non-EU Countries through foreign subsidiaries that are part of the YOOX Group.

Your personal data will not be disclosed to the above companies without your consent.
These companies usually adopt their privacy policies when providing their services to their users and when selling their products on yoox.com. Such privacy policies are, in any case, consistent with this Privacy Policy since Italian Data Protection Code applies in the case of processing of personal data carried out by anyone who is located in a non-EU Country using processing equipment (whether or not electronically based) located in the Italian territory, except when they such equipment is used only for the data transit on the Italian territory. For these purposes, companies of Yoox Group appointed YOOX as their data protection representative within the Italian territory for the application of Italian laws on data processing, as provided by the Italian Data Protection Code.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>15. Modification and Updating of yoox.com Privacy Policy</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>YOOX may amend or simply update all or part of yoox.com's Privacy Policy, in consideration of amendments to legal provisions or regulations which govern data protection and protect your rights. The amendments and the updating of yoox.com Privacy Policy shall be notified to our users on yoox.com's homepage as soon as such amendments or updates have been introduced and shall be binding as soon as they are published on the web site in this section. Therefore, you are requested to regularly access this section in order to check the publication of the most recent and updated YOOX Privacy Policy.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
