<POLICY modification_date="" policy_url="http://www.hrs.de/web3/showCmsPage.do;jsessionid=D9D0D0E61541FD23205DC60C14D0918A.57-4?clientId=ZGVfX05FWFQ-&amp;cid=57-4&amp;pageId=legals" website_category="Recreation" website_index="093" website_url="hrs.de">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>Privacy + Security

Privacy Policy

We at HRS - Hotel Reservation Service committed to protecting your privacy and security very seriously. Here we would like to explain what information we collect, what we use it and how we protect your data.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>General information about data protection and purpose of storage</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>What data is collected?

Booking
When you make a reservation booked through HRS, we collect the necessary arrangements for the reservation information from you, particularly your name, your telephone number, your e-mail address ("Contact") and the date of your arrival and departure, your hotel and type of room booked ("reservation data").

Contact
About the Contact field can report general inquiries. To address these requests, we collect your contact information. After processing your request we will delete that data.

MyHRS
Under MyHRS you can register as a user of our site with your contact information. This registration has among others the advantage that you do not have to retype your data anew for each booking. You have the option to terminate the registration at any time, by sending an email to:

datenschutz@hrs.de

We will then delete your contact information. Under MyHRS You also have the option to e-mail about travel tips, new features on the site, special offers, etc. to be kept up to date. You can also subscribe to a newsletter. It is up to you, this kind of customer care to choose and at any time to stop again.

Connection information
in the course of using the website of the HRS in this communication transmitted and accumulated usage data are collected such as IP address. We use the resulting usage data only for the prevention of abuse and interference as well as to optimize our range.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Who will my data be shared</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>When you make a booking with HRS, booking details are passed on to the hotel you've selected to make your reservation to be made. In addition, your data will not be passed to third parties. Under no circumstances your contact HRS sell or lend.
Due to legal regulations, judicial or administrative orders, we are in exceptional cases be obliged to return data to the relevant authority or court. This happens only in the context of our legal obligations.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Privacy Statement</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>How secure is the data transfer to HRS?

All data that you provide to HRS available are encrypted with at least 128 bit SSL (Secure Socket Layer) method and transmitted. Unless your browser supports stronger encryption, the data with up to 256-bit encrypted. When SSL is a proven and world related encryption system, which allows your browser automatically encrypt your data before returning it to us.

How secure is my data on the HRS database?

For our database and our web server, we use high HRS safety standards in order to ensure effective protection against the loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and deletion of your data.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Cookies</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Cookies - What are they?

Cookies are small data files that are stored by your browser on the hard drive of your computer. They simplify your booking by, frequently accessed data are displayed automatically for you at a repeat visit our websites. You can set your browser to not store any cookies on your computer. You might be able then but some features of our range not perceive. The basic functions "Search &amp; Book" however, are also possible without cookies.

Website Analysis

We also employ a cookie analysis software Omniture SiteCatalyst Adobe Systems GmbH. The software writes a cookie with a random, unique ID on your system. The cookie can be assigned at any time of a natural person. Details measuring method of Omniture SiteCatalyst, you can also see on the product page:

Omniture</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Social Media</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Facebook
We have on our website on the "Like" button from the company Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA ("Facebook") involved. If you access this page, your browser automatically establishes a connection to the servers of Facebook and Facebook, the corresponding information.

If you have a Facebook account, while on our Facebook page are logged in Facebook or save cookies on your computer, Facebook can assign your visit to our site to your Facebook profile. Click the "Like Me" button or to enter a comment, it will be stored by Facebook and displayed in your Facebook profile. If you do not want that Facebook collects this information from you, please login before you visit the HRS website at Facebook from or delete the Facebook cookies.

Information on the purpose and scope of data collection and the further processing and use of data by Facebook, and your settings options for protecting your privacy please visit the privacy policy of Facebook.

Google+ and Youtube
we have on our side the "Google+" button and the "Youtube" button from the company Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA ("Google") involved. If you access this page, your browser automatically establishes a connection to Google's servers and Google, the corresponding information.

If you have a Google account, while on our site are logged into Google or Google cookies stored on your computer, Google can assign your visit to our site to your Google profile. Click the "Google+" button or to enter a comment, it will be stored by Google and displayed in your Google profile. If you do not want Google will store this information from you, please login before you visit the HRS website at Google from or delete the Google cookie.

Information on the purpose and scope of data collection and the further processing and use of data by Google as well as your settings options for protecting your privacy please visit the privacy policy of Google.

Twitter
We have included on our side the "Twitter" button from the company Twitter, Inc., 1355 Market St, Suite 900, San Francisco, CA 94103, USA ("Twitter"). If you access this page, your browser automatically establishes a connection to the servers of Twitter and Twitter, the corresponding information.

If you have a Twitter account, while visiting our page at Twitter are logged or save Twitter cookies on your computer, Twitter can assign your visit to our site your Twitter profile. Click the "Twitter" button or to enter a comment, it will be stored by Twitter and displayed in your Twitter profile. If you do not want Twitter saves the information from you, please login before you visit the HRS website at twitter from the twitter or delete cookies.

Information on the purpose and scope of data collection and the further processing and use of data through Twitter and your settings options for protecting your privacy please visit the privacy policy of Twitter.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Ask</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>You can always get information about the data you have stored with us. You have the right to correct, delete and block (incorrect) data. Your contact details please right under MyHRS. The deletion of data, however, there may be contractual and / or legal requirements, in particular, preclude those relating to accounting and billing. For questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at:

datenschutz@hrs.de</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
