<POLICY modification_date="August 12, 2013" policy_url="http://www.behance.net/misc/privacy" website_category="Business" website_index="038" website_url="behance.net">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>Privacy Policy

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------


Effective date: August 12, 2013

Behance Inc. (“Behance”) is an online platform where creative professionals can showcase their work and discover the creative work of others.  Behance is hosted exclusively in the United States and is operated from the Behance offices in New York, NY.  Behance may be accessed directly on the web at www.behance.net  or, for Adobe Creative Cloud (“Creative Cloud”) subscribers, from various points available inside of Creative Cloud.

Behance is a wholly-owned subsidiary of Adobe Systems Incorporated, and any information you provide to Behance will be shared within the Adobe family of companies.  Adobe's privacy practices are described here.  Behance follows Adobe's privacy practices.  In addition, privacy-related information specific to Behance is provided below.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>How Does Behance Use Geographic Information It Collects At Registration, And How Can I Change It</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Behance requires that users provide geographic information (city, state and country) when registering.  This information lets users search for artists or creative work by geographic region.   It also helps Behance to make your web experience more geographically relevant.   If you move, you can update your geographic information by going to the “My Profile” tab.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>How Can I Opt-Out Of, Or Customize Messages Behance SendsTo Me</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>You can opt-out or customize the type of messages you receive from Behance by visiting the “Notifications” tab under “Account Settings”, or by clicking on the unsubscribe link included at the bottom of Behance marketing emails.  You may also set your marketing preferences for other Adobe products and services here.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>How Does Behance Share My Information If I Join A Custom Creative Network</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Behance allows organizations to set up private galleries hosted by Behance called Custom Creative Networks.  If you choose to join a Custom Creative Network, Behance will share with the Custom Creative Network your name, email address, country, date you joined Behance, the number of projects you have published, your Behance URL, and if applicable, your school status, school/organization email address, degree program and year of graduation.  By joining a Custom Creative Network you will be subject to that organization's privacy policy, in addition to the policies outlined on, or linked to from, this page.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>How Can I Review, Update or Delete My Personal Information On Behance</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>You may review and update your personal information by visiting the “Account Settings” tab.  If you wish to delete your Behance account, you can go to the “Privacy” tab under “Account Settings” and click “Delete” (please note, this process is irreversible and we can't restore your account afterwards).  You can also delete your account by submitting a request to http://behancenetwork.zendesk.com/tickets/new.   Additionally, you can edit or update other information in your Behance profile by visiting the “My Profile” tab.   You can also edit your personal Behance URL on the “My Profile” tab, but you are only permitted to do so once.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
