<POLICY modification_date="June 01, 2013" policy_url="http://www.laterooms.com/en/static/TermsOfUse.mvc#s4" website_category="Recreation" website_index="090" website_url="laterooms.com">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>LateRooms.com privacy policy

We understand that making purchases online involves your trust. Retaining your trust is a responsibility that we take very seriously. We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information.

By disclosing your personal information to us by using our website or over the telephone, you consent to the collection, storage and processing of your personal information as stated in this policy.

The personal information that we collect from you shall be obtained, processed and transmitted in compliance with applicable data protection legislation. Since our servers are located in the United Kingdom, the personal information that we collect from you shall be obtained, processed and transmitted in compliance with European Directives 95/46 and 2002/58, as well as any other such legislation that replaces, substitutes, complements and develops it such as the Data Protection Act 1998 from the United Kingdom.

"Personal Information" means information that relates to a living individual who can be identified from that information or from that information together with other information which is held by or is likely to be held by us.

Back to the top</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>What personal information do we collect</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal information:

information that you provide by filling in any booking forms or other forms on our website or which you give us over the telephone, including your name, (home or office) address, date of birth, (business or private) email address, (mobile, home or office) telephone number, credit card details (i.e. credit card type and number, CVC code, expiration date, credit card holder name) and to the extent available, reservation preferences and smoking preferences;
information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website including where you have clicked on any of our advertising links or banners, (including your IP address, geographical location, browser/platform type and version, Internet Service Provider (ISP) and (for users of our service through a mobile device) Unique Device Identifier, operating system, referral source/exit pages, length of visit, page views, website navigation, date/time stamp information and details like the number and location of (mouse) clicks on a given page, mouse movements, scrolling activity and the (search) words you use and the text you type while being on and using our website);
information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us;
information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our website services, email notifications and/or newsletters; and
any other information that you choose to send to us.

We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them.

Back to the top</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Information about other people</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>If you provide information to us about any person other than yourself, you must ensure that they understand how their information will be used and that you are authorised to disclose it to us, and consent its use on their behalf, before doing so.

Back to the top</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Cookies and Web Beacons</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>A cookie consists of information sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.

We use both "session" cookies and "short-term" cookies on the website. We will use the session cookies for such purposes as to keep track of you whilst you navigate the website. We will use the short-term cookies for such purposes as to enable our website to recognise you when you visit.

Session cookies will be deleted from your computer when you close your browser. Short-term cookies will remain stored on your computer for a period of 30 days.

In addition to this, we use web analytics services provided by Google, Inc ("Google") and WT EMEA Acquisition Ltd ("Webtrends"). Google and Webtrends use cookies, to help analyse how visitors use our website. The information generated by the cookie about the use of our website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google and Webtrends on servers in the United States. Google and Webtrends will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of our website, compiling reports on website activity for us and providing other services relating to website activity and Internet usage. Google and Webtrends may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's or Webtrends behalf. Google and Webtrends will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google or Webtrends.

We also work with advertising partners to serve ads that we believe are most likely to be of interest to you, based on information about your visit to this and other websites (this information is anonymous in that it does not include your name, street address, e-mail address or telephone number). In order to do this, our advertising partners may need to place a cookie (a small text file) on your computer. For more information about this type of online behavioural advertising, about cookies, and about how to turn this feature off, please visit www.youronlinechoices.com.

Most browsers allow you to reject all cookies, whilst some browsers allow you to reject just third party cookies. For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking "Tools", "Internet Options", "Privacy", and selecting "Block all cookies" using the sliding selector. Blocking all cookies will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites, including this one. More information about cookies can be found at www.allaboutcookies.org

Below is a detailed list of the cookies that we use on this website, including those cookies that are essential for the website to operate.
Strictly Necessary Cookies
Cookie Name 	Cookie Type 	Purpose and Further Information
Lateroomsprofile 	Short

This cookie notes customer data such as your preferred language/currency/country, and it is vital for the website to work.
Search 	Short (7 days)

This cookie enables us to store your search preferences so that the website remembers what you are searching for, such as number of nights, children, adults, arrival date, etc. and it is vital for the website to work.
Functionality cookies
Cookie Name 	Cookie Type 	Purpose and Further Information
ASP.NET_SessionId 	Session

This cookie retains your current session so that you can return to the website if you encounter a browser issue and will still be able to make a booking.
Performance Cookies
Third Party 	Cookie Type 	Purpose and Further Information
Partner Cookies 	Persistent (longer than 30 days)

These cookies are used to identify which partner has referred a user when they have arrived on the website via a link from another site. This cookie is placed by the partner site prior to arriving on the website. This enables us to identify referral customers and remunerate partners and is vital to the functioning of the affiliate referral program.
Webtrends 	Persistent (longer than 30 days)

These cookies monitor the traffic volumes to the website to allow us to understand how the website is working and fix any problems. This ensures that the website is fully functional and optimised to create the best possible user experience.

To opt-out of receiving these cookies please see Webtrends' privacy policy at: http://www.webtrends.com/privacy-policy.
Google 	Persistent (longer than 30 days)

These cookies monitor the traffic volumes to the website to allow us to understand how the website is working and fix any problems. This ensures that the website is fully functional and optimised to create the best possible user experience.

To opt-out of receiving these cookies please see Google's privacy policy at: http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html or visit http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
Tealeaf 	Persistent (longer than 30 days)

These are cookies that are used to analyse a user's actions across our website during single and multiple visits so we can understand how you are using the website. This provides us with information to ensure the best possible user experience.
Maxymiser 	Persistent (longer than 30 days)

These are cookies that are used to analyse a user's actions and behaviours on our website through conversion optimisation solutions so we can understand how you are using the website. This provides us with information to ensure the best possible user experience.
Targeting Cookies
Third Party 	Cookie Type 	Purpose and Further Information
Criteo 	Persistent (longer than 30 days)

These third party cookies allow us to deliver adverts to you (after you have left LateRooms.com) that show the best hotel deals for the locations you have been searching for. This means that you will be shown deals that you may have missed without having to search the site again. This is called online behavioural advertising, a common online advertising practice and does not collect any personal data.

To opt-out of receiving these cookies please follow this link: http://www.criteo.com/en/privacy-policy/opt-out.
Efficient Frontier 	Short (7 days)

These third party cookies allow us to monitor the effectiveness of our search marketing campaigns on Google, Yahoo and MSN. This means we can make the adverts more useful to you by providing you with content that is timely and relevant.

To opt-out of receiving these cookies please follow this link: http://www.efrontier.com/optout-page.
AddThis 	Persistent (longer than 30 days)

These are cookies are used to enable sharing of content and they also measure content impacts across various social network streams.

To opt-out of receiving these cookies please see AddThis' privacy policy at http://www.addthis.com/privacy.
Banners 	Variable, but some will be persistent (longer than 30 days)

These third party cookies allow us to monitor the effectiveness of our online banner marketing campaigns on Doubleclick (Google), Yahoo, Xaxis, Yahoo, MSN and Flashtalking amongst others. This means we can make the adverts more useful to you by providing you with content that is timely and relevant. We also use these cookies to ensure we are not serving a high volume of ads to you.

To opt-out of receiving these cookies please follow these links:

http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/index.aspx
http://info.yahoo.com/privacy/uk/yahoo/cookies
http://www.flashtalking.com/intelligent.html (follow the link in the bottom right)
http://www.xaxis.com/uk (follow the link in the bottom right)
http://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/fullnotice.mspx

You can also opt-out of receiving other third party marketing cookies (not used by LateRooms.com) by following this link: http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad-choices.

Some of our Website pages and HTML-formatted e-mail newsletters may use web beacons in conjunction with cookies to compile aggregate statistics about website usage. A Web beacon is an electronic image, called a single-pixel (1x1) or clear GIF and are used like cookies to recognize certain types of information on your computer, such as your cookie number, time and date of a page view, and a description of the page where the web beacon is placed.

Back to the top</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Using your personal information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Personal information submitted to us via this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.

We may use your personal information to:



manage and administer the website;
improve your browsing experience by personalising the website;
enable your use of the services available on the website including providing you with login in details so you may access details of your bookings;
manage, administer, mediate and contract the services offered by us via the website and/or our call centre;
manage, administer, mediate and contract your bookings made through the website and/or our call-centre;
send you general (non-marketing) commercial communications including communications about any important changes to the website and/or surveys we may ask you to complete;
send you email notifications which you have specifically requested including email nofitications confirming your bookings made via the website and/or our call centre;
contact you by electronic means (e-mail or SMS) with information such as special offers for goods and services similar to those which were the subject of a previous sale to you, unless you have opted out of receiving such information (you can inform us at any time if you do not wish to receive such marketing communications by simply clicking on the unsubscribe link);
send to you our newsletter and other marketing communications relating to new services, our business or the businesses of carefully-selected third parties which we think may be of interest to you by post or, where you have specifically agreed or subscribed to this, by email or similar technology (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications by simply clicking on the unsubscribe link);
provide third parties with statistical information about our users' but this information will not be used to identify any individual user;
deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the website, your bookings and/or the services offered by us or our suppliers;
to analyse and improve the services offered on our website and to provide you with the most user-friendly navigation experience. We may also use and disclose information in aggregate for marketing and strategic development purposes;
send you an email inviting you to leave a guest review on the website following your stay; and
deliver marketing and advertising to you that show services and deals that we think you will be interested in including via targeted advertising on third party websites and/or platforms.



Where you submit personal information for publication on our website, we will publish and otherwise use that information in accordance with the license you grant to us.

We may monitor, record, store and use any telephone email or other communication with you for monitoring purposes, in order to check any instructions given to us by you, for staff training purposes, for crime prevention and to improve the quality of our customer service.

We will not provide your personal information to any third parties for the purpose of direct marketing by such third party unless you have provided your express consent by activating the "opt-in" option on the website. In such cases, we shall only transfer to the third party adequate, relevant and not excessive personal data (name, address and email addresses) so you will be able to receive direct marketing material from such third party. You can inform us at any time if you no longer wish for your details to be disclosed to such third party and we will no longer disclose your information. The relevant third party will show their contact information in their marketing material and we have no control over such third party marketing material, therefore we disclaim any kind of liability that may arise from such third party marketing material.

You expressly agree to such uses of personal information.

Back to the top</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Disclosures</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We may disclose information about you to any of our employees, officers, agents, suppliers, partners or subcontractors insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes as set out in this privacy policy or whom we have appointed to process information on our behalf or manage aspects of our website. Please note we must disclose information about you to the relevant suppliers of your travel arrangements.

In addition, we may disclose your personal information:



to the extent that we are required to do so by law;
in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;
in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk);
to the purchaser (or prospective purchaser) of any business or asset which we are (or are contemplating) selling; and
to any person who we reasonably believe may apply to a court or other competent authority for disclosure of that personal information where, in our reasonable opinion, such court or authority would be reasonably likely to order disclosure of that personal information.



Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties.

You expressly agree to such disclosures of personal information.

Back to the top</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>International data transfers</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Information that we collect may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which we and/or our suppliers operate in order to enable us to use the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

Information which you provide may be transferred to countries which do not have data protection laws equivalent to those in force in the European Economic Area (EEA), in particular where your booking destination is outside the EEA. Please note, if we cannot pass this information to the relevant accommodation and/or service providers, whether in the EEA or not, we cannot provide the services to you.

Information may be transferred to companies contracted by us to perform services in connection with this website who are based outside the EEA including in the United States, where such organisations have signed up to the US Safe Harbour Principles and/or contracts providing an adequate level of protection have been signed.

In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website as a review will be published on the internet and may be available, via the internet, around the world. We cannot prevent the use or misuse of such information by others.

You expressly agree to such transfers of personal information.

Back to the top</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Security of your personal information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Please note that, in accordance with European personal data protection laws, we will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

Of course, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet.

You are responsible for keeping your password and user details confidential. We will not ask you for your password (except when you log in to the website).

Back to the top</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Policy amendments</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes. Your continued use of the website shall constitute your agreement and acceptance of the changes to this policy.

Back to the top</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Your rights</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you. Provision of such information will be subject to:



the payment of a fee (currently fixed at £10.00); and
the supply of appropriate evidence of your identity (for this purpose, we will usually accept a photocopy of your passport certified by a solicitor or bank plus an original copy of a utility bill showing your current address).



We may withhold such personal information to the extent permitted by law.

You may instruct us not to process your personal information for marketing purposes by email at any time. In practice, you will usually either expressly agree in advance to our use of your personal information for marketing purposes, or we will provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of the use of your personal information for marketing purposes.

Back to the top</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Third party websites</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites including use of cookies on such third party websites and you should prefer to the third party's privacy policy for more information.

Back to the top</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Updating information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Please let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated.

Back to the top</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Contact</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal information, please contact us here or by post to Late Rooms Ltd, The Peninsula Building, 2 Cheetham Hill Road, Manchester, M4 4EW.

Back to the top</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Data controller</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>The data controller responsible in respect of the information collected on this website is Late Rooms Limited, whose registered office address is TUI Travel House, Crawley Business Quarter, Fleming Way, Crawley, West Sussex, RH10 9QL.

Our data protection registration number is Z8168511.

Updated June 2013</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
