<POLICY modification_date="February 15, 2013" policy_url="http://www.videogamer.com/legal.html" website_category="Games" website_index="095" website_url="videogamer.com">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>Log In / Join ▼


Platforms
News
Videos
Reviews
Games
Gamercards
Features
Downloads
Cheats
Podcast
YouTube
Forum


VideoGamer.com Legal Notices
Copyright Notice
Disclaimer; Limitation of Liability
Privacy Policy

Pro-G Media, operator of VideoGamer.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for all of our Internet-based services.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Personal info</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>The following types of personal data, may be stored by us if you choose to sign-up to the website or connect via Facebook:
Full name
E-mail address
IP address
Browser software information
Date of Birth (Optional)
Your social/gaming network username or ID (Optional. May include Facebook, Twitter, Google Plus, PSN, Xbox Live or Steam)</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Tracking technologies</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We use third party analytical tools to help us to understand how you and other users consume the information on our website. Most of these tools use JavaScript to log page views and other such statistical information about your visit to the site. This data is entirely anonymous, we do not store or use any personally identifiable data about you during this process.

We collect this data to enable us to improve the user experience across the site.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>How we use your info</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>If you create an account with us, your personal information is used to personalise your experience on the website and give you the ability to interact with us and other users. We use your IP address and browser information to help diagnose problems with our server and to gather broad demographic information.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>When we share your info</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We do not generally share personally identifiable information (such as name, address, email or phone) with other companies except in these limited circumstances:
You provide your express consent,
when we have a good faith belief it is required by law,
when we have a good faith belief it is necessary to protect our rights or property, or
to any successor or purchaser in a merger, acquisition, liquidation, dissolution or sale of assets. Your consent will not be required for disclosure in these cases, but we will attempt to notify you, to the extent permitted by law to do so.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>How we store your info</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Personal information is stored on a secure database server, sensitive information such as a password is encrypted and non-reversible.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Cookies</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Information gathered through the use of cookies is not related to any personally identifiable details. Many browsers are set to accept cookies. You may prefer to set your browser to refuse cookies. It is possible, however, that some areas of the site will not function properly if you do so. Definition of a cookie.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Accessing or removing your data</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>At any point you may request a copy of the personal data we stored about you, you may also request for such data to be entirely removed from our database by contacting us.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Changes</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>This privacy policy was last updated on 15/02/2013. Our privacy policy may change from time to time. If we make any material changes to our policies, we will place a prominent notice on our website or application. If the change materially affects registered users, we will send a notice to you by email or private message via the site.
Contact us

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy please direct them to privacy@pro-g.co.uk.
Terms of Use
Categories
Copyright Notice
Disclaimer; Limitation of Liability
Privacy Policy
Terms

Popular Games
There are currently not enough games with scores.
All Updates
News
Reviews
Features
All games
Cheats &amp; FAQs
All videos
Trailers
Gameplay Clips
Extended Plays
Most Popular Games
The Legend of Zelda: A...
TMNT: Out of the Shadows
TMNT: Out of the Shadows
TMNT: Out of the Shadows
Top Games
Grand Theft Auto 5
Battlefield 4
FIFA 14
Assassin's Creed 4: Bl...
Call of Duty: Ghosts
Network Sites




© 2004-2013
Policy Info</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Contact us</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Terms
Staff</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
