<POLICY modification_date="April 11, 2002" policy_url="http://www.gearslutz.com/board/terms/" website_category="Recreation" website_index="091" website_url="gearslutz.com">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>GEARSLUTZ.COM

Terms of Use &amp; Privacy Policy</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Disclaimer</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>This internet site provides information of a technical nature and is designed for reference purposes only.  Please review the Terms of Use below before using this site. Your use of the site indicates your agreement to be bound by the Terms of Use.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Terms of Use</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Please read this agreement carefully before accessing or using this site. By accessing or using the site, you agree to be bound by this agreement. The information and services on this site are provided by Gearslutz.com and its suppliers, subject to your agreement to the terms and conditions below.

Gearslutz.com can edit or delete messages as we see fit, it is our sole discretion. This is for your benefit and is to ensure the forums stay friendly, fun and supportive. If you feel unable to accept this rule, then we politely request that you find what you seek on forums elsewhere.

Posting to our discussion forums and entering into our chat room will be taken as acceptance of these rules. You should ensure that you are aware of your legal responsibilities when using our forums. Please note that contravention of these rules will lead to the removal of your message.

This forum is intended for members who have an interest in recording equipment. It is intended for those seeking advice and support in relation to all recording matters.
IMPORTANT NOTE: It is not a place to air personal grievances you may have and under no circumstances should information about another person be divulged.
1.         Do not flame or personally insult another user. Please do not use Gearslutz.com discussion forums or chat rooms to harass, threaten or attack anyone, or behave in any way that would cause annoyance or distress to other users. Please be tactful when posting in a forum or chat room where extra sensitivity is required.

2.         Commercial messages and messages from businesses or organizations are discouraged. These forums and chat rooms are for use by our members and non members  - they are not to be aggressively used as a medium for marketing or selling to our users

3.         You may not insult or defame Gearslutz.com, including any of its employees, moderators or freelancers. You may not post the contents (in part or whole) of any email that you may receive from any Gearslutz.com employee or moderator without our prior permission.

4.         Do not labour a point after a thread concerning the same point has been removed or has run it's course

5.         Do not post messages more than once. This is also known as 'flooding'. Duplicate messages are very frustrating.

6.         Do not behave in any way that disrupts the flow of an ongoing discussion or that spoils the atmosphere within the forum or chat room.

7.         Do not impersonate another person.

8.         Do not post chain letters, promote pyramid schemes or recruit members for any 'network marketing' businesses.

9.         Do not collect or distribute personal data concerning other Gearslutz.com members without first obtaining the consent of Gearslutz.com and the members concerned.

10.       Do not use the forums or chat rooms to make complaints about Gearslutz.com. If you are unsatisfied about something, please consider other forum/ chat users, and email us directly

11.       Do not recruit our members to join another website forum or chat group, whether personal or otherwise. Adding a link to a specific personal website that is utterly relevant to both your posting and the forum topic is permitted on infrequent occasions. If you have a suggestion for a new forum, please contact the site admin. If you are approached to join another group/site as a result of your Gearslutz.com membership/posts on our forums, please advise us.

12.       We encourage the exchange of information on the forums and adding an appropriate link to your posting links is invited. However, obvious promotion of, or inappropriate links to, other known commercial websites, or any forum or chat groups are not permitted and may be removed. If you are unsure whether a link or posting is allowed, Please ask us.
- we consider an 'appropriate link' as one that is utterly relevant to both the posting and the forum topic.
- we consider a 'commercial' site to be one which is funded or supported in any way by a profit making business.
-  'Any forum or chat group' means anywhere on the web, regardless of topic, please see rule above.

13.       We encourage a healthy exchange of opinions and disagreements are allowed! By all means challenge an opinion – but please do it respectfully. Name calling, insults and foul and abusive language will not be tolerated. This includes the use of offensive nicknames and usernames.

14.       Be sure you want to give information, which is personal before you post a message. Remember that anybody can read it. That said, we respectfully ask that you use a proper name when posting to the forums, and keep with that name when posting. If there is someone already posting with the same name, please alter your name to avoid confusion.

15.       This is a UK site. Please make your postings in English so they are understood by other members and our moderators. We apologize but we can't allow members to post in a language other than English.

16.       Gearslutz.com aims to bring the best of our community to a larger audience. We may do this by quoting your discussion board messages in newsletters, throughout Gearslutz.com, in books, newspaper columns, radio and TV programmes. When using your comments, we will identify you only by your Gearslutz.com member name. We promise to be sensitive in this effort. We will not republish anything that we think could be deemed personally endangering, inflammatory or embarrassing to you without your consent.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Safety Guidelines</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>All members are responsible for the safety of their personal information. We recommend that members do not disclose their name, address, email address, telephone number or other personal information online. No Gearslutz.com employees or Gearslutz.com discussion forum moderators will ever request such details online.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Legalities</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>All members are reminded that they may be held legally accountable for what they say or do online. In particular, members may be held liable for any defamatory comments, threats and untrue statements or other illegal and fraudulent claims made by them.

Unfortunately, Gearslutz.com cannot guarantee the prompt editing or removal of any content. Neither Gearslutz.com nor its third party contractors are liable for the content of any material accessed via the internet, any adverse treatment of any information placed by a member anywhere on the internet, or any loss or damage that a member may suffer as a result.

We do not endorse opinions expressed by members of Gearslutz.com on its discussion forums, in its chat rooms or anywhere on the site where members can add their own content.

Gearslutz.com reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to remove material from Gearslutz.com discussion forums and member content areas at any time

Gearslutz.com discussion forums, member content areas, and chat rooms consist of information posted by third parties. As a result, Gearslutz.com accepts no liability in respect to the accuracy or truthfulness of any advice, information or data posted online or any responsibility for the consequences of a member acting in reliance on such information.

Please also be aware of our disclaimer.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>To protect other Gearslutz.com members</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>If members fail to observe the above Conditions of use at any time, Gearslutz.com reserves the right to exclude the member from the Gearslutz.com community (including forums, chat rooms and member area) depending on the nature and severity of the breach.

We reserve the right to deny access to Gearslutz.com's community, including discussion forums and chat rooms, to members who repeatedly breach these Conditions of use.
Gearslutz.com reserves the right to change these Conditions of use at any time and will post details of the changes online.

Members accepting the Conditions of use agree that Gearslutz.com may release their information (both present and past) where Gearslutz.com believes that a member has breached the Conditions of use or used Gearslutz.com's discussion forums or chat rooms to commit unlawful acts. Gearslutz.com also reserves the right to disclose a member's personal information where required to do so by law and where Gearslutz.com deems it appropriate in response to complaints of a substantial nature.

Use of our community services, including discussion forums, chat rooms and member areas will be taken as acceptance of these rules. Please note that any contravention of these rules may lead to the removal of your message/content.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Disclaimer of Liability</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>To the extent permissible by law, Gearslutz.com assumes no responsibility for information published on this site and disclaims all liability in respect of such information. Gearslutz.com is not liable for any injury and/or damage to persons or property as a result of any actual or alleged libelous statements, infringements of intellectual property or privacy rights, or product liability, whether resulting from negligence or otherwise, including without limitation, from any use or operation of any ideas, instructions, procedures, products or methods contained in the material published on the site. Gearslutz.com does not warrant that the information published on the site is accurate or free from error. Information published within the site is intended solely for the purpose of providing general information. Gearslutz.com's failure to insist upon strict enforcement of any provision of this agreement shall not be construed as a waiver of any provision or right.

This agreement will be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of England and Wales, and the parties hereby submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the English Courts.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Visitors and members' contributions to the website</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We are pleased to receive your contributions to the website.  We point out that the website is international and is accessible throughout the world and that by contributing in any way to the website, as above, you are consenting to the publication of your contribution on Gearslutz.com.  Gearslutz.com reserves the right to edit any contributions where necessary.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Chat Rooms/Discussion Forums</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>The chat room service is intended to facilitate communication between members and non members, and the views expressed do not necessarily reflect those of Gearslutz.com. The posting of defamatory comment or material that infringes the rights of others has no place in such discussions, and will not be permitted. Although Gearslutz.com is not responsible for comments included in this area, it reserves the right to review postings and delete them if they are not appropriate and the user's right to access the chat room may be rescinded. Users should also be aware that such activities may subject them to civil actions or criminal penalties.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Featured Products</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Any advertising on Gearslutz.com does not constitute a guarantee or endorsement of the quality or value of any products or of the claims made for them by the manufacturer. Users are advised to verify product information with the manufacturer.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Copyright and Limited Reproduction Notices</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>This website and its contents are (c) Gearslutz.com April 11th 2002 or its Licensors. All rights reserved. Reproduction of all or any substantial part of the contents in any form is prohibited except that individual users may print or save portions of the site for their own personal use. This license does not permit users to incorporate the material or any substantial part of it in any other work or publication, whether in hard copy or electronic or any other form. In particular (but without limitation) no substantial part of the website may be distributed or copied for any commercial purpose. No substantial part of the website may be reproduced on or transmitted to or stored in any other website or other electronic retrieval system.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Indemnification</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>You agree to indemnify, defend and hold harmless Gearslutz.com, its affiliates and suppliers from any liability, loss, claim and expense (including reasonable legal fees) directly or indirectly related to (i) your breach of this agreement, and (ii) your posting of material to this site.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Disclaimer of warranty</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>To the maximum extent permitted by law, Gearslutz.com and its suppliers disclaim all express and implied warranties with regard to the information, services, and materials contained on this site, including without limitation any implied warranties of care and skill, satisfactory quality, fitness for a particular purpose. All such information, services, and materials are provided "as is" and "as available" without warranty of any kind.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Privacy Policy</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We do not retain any credit card details for any transactions.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Returns policy</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We require two working days notice for any ad campaign cancellations. Refunds will be issued on a daily pro rata basis for any cancelled campaigns.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
