<POLICY modification_date="" policy_url="http://www.mckinley.com/privacy-policy" website_category="Regional" website_index="061" website_url="mckinley.com">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>Privacy Policy and Legal Statement
McKinley is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. We provide certain services and opportunities for users of our Web site.

In order to provide services to you and to develop a better site, we may ask you to submit some personal information. Please read the following to learn more.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Personal Information Collected</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We collect information:

When you register an account to apply for housing online at http://www.mckinley.com/apply. This includes your email address and password.
When you complete an online application (http://www.mckinley.com/apply) for housing we require personal information in order to conduct a full background and credit check. This includes your full name, date of birth, current address, ssn, phone number, email, emergency contact information, current and past housing information, and current and past employment information.
When you submit a request for more information about our communities, we collect your name, phone, and email.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Uses of personal information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>The information you provide us on http://www.mckinley.com/apply, with your authorization (via electronic signature) is used to conduct a full background and credit check for housing at our communities.
By sending a request for more information, we use this information to contact you to find the best housing solution.
We use the information you provide us to administer your account for technical issues.


We do not sell, rent, or otherwise provide personally identifiable information to third parties without your consent except where it is necessary to carry out your instructions (to conduct background and/or credit checks for example).

To modify or delete this personal information or opt-out, please send an email to live@mckinley.com with your request.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Information Gathered</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>When you request information or complete a contact form, McKinley is collecting information from you. This information is necessary to tailor our subsequent communications with you, to fulfill your information request and to contact you about McKinley.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Information Sharing</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>McKinley will not sell, rent, or share your personal information with others, unless we have your permission or are required by law. We will not share aggregate data with other parties.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Cookies</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>A cookie is a small data file that certain websites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you've visited, but the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself.  A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites.

McKinley may use cookies to identify what pages are being used and which ones aren't. This helps us analyze the website traffic and improve our site. No other company has access to McKinley's cookies.

McKinley wants to be sure you understand that accepting a cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any personal information about you, other than the data you chose to share with us. If you are uncomfortable with cookie technology, you may adjust your browser accordingly.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Changes to this Privacy Policy</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>McKinley may amend this policy occasionally. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information, we will notify you.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Feedback</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or our use of personal information on this site, please contact us.

Legal Policy

Please read these terms and conditions of use carefully.

By downloading any materials from this website, you indicate your acceptance of these terms and conditions. If you do not accept these terms and conditions, then do not download any materials from this website. McKinley reserves the right to change these terms from time to time at its sole discretion. In the case of any violation of these terms, McKinley reserves the right to seek all remedies available by law and in equity for such violations. These terms apply to the McKinley website, both now and in the future.

Copyright
McKinley owns all content and materials on this site. The materials are copyrighted and protected by the copyright laws of the United States and, throughout the world, by the copyright law of each jurisdiction reflecting pertinent treaties and conventions.

EXCEPT AS SPECIFICALLY PERMITTED BELOW, YOU MAY NOT COPY, ADAPT, MODIFY, DISPLAY, PERFOM, OR OTHERWISE USE THE MATERIALS (INCLUDING USE OF THESE MATERIALS ON ANY OTHER WEBSITE OR NETWORKED COMPUTER ENVIRONMENT) WITHOUT THE PRIOR WRITTEN PERMISSION OF MCKINLEY. Your use of the materials is conditioned on your maintaining all copyright, trademark and other proprietary rights notices appearing on the materials. Any unauthorized use of any of the materials on this site may violate the copyright, trademark and other similar laws.

McKinley authorizes you to view, copy, print, and distribute McKinley material from this site, as long as:
The material is used for information only
The material is used for noncommercial purposes only
Copies of any material include McKinleys copyright notice

No Warranty
Although McKinley attempts to provide accurate information on this website, some information may be incorrect or outdated. Therefore, McKinley assumes no responsibility for the accuracy of information on this website. McKinley may change the information on the website, or the products mentioned, at any time without notice.

LIMITATION OF LIABILITY
MCKINLEY IS NOT LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF THE USE, OR THE INABILITY TO USE, THE MATERIAL ON THIS SITE. THIS INCLUDES, BUT IS NOT LIMITED TO, THE LOSS OF DATA OR LOSS OF PROFIT, EVEN IF MCKINLEY WAS ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.

Links to other websites
This website may contain links to other web sites. These links are provided to you as a convenience, and McKinley is not responsible for the content of any linked website. A link to any other website does not imply that McKinley endorses or accepts any responsibility for the content or use of such a website. In no event shall any reference to any third party or third-party product or service be construed as an approval or endorsement by McKinley of that third party or of any product or service provided by a third party.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
