<POLICY modification_date="December 19, 2012" policy_url="http://www.mcafee.com/common/privacy/english/index.htm" website_category="Society" website_index="004" website_url="siteadvisor.com">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>Privacy Notice
This Notice provides information about data we use for security purposes and our
commitment to using the personal data we collect in a respectful fashion.
Go here for our complete notice.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>McAfee Privacy Notice</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>McAfee and its family of companies (“McAfee”, “we”, “us”) are wholly owned
subsidiaries of Intel Incorporated.  We care deeply about your privacy and security
and your safety is a significant part of our essential mission.  We appreciate your
decision to trust us with helping to protect your digital life from theft, disruption,
and unauthorized access to your personal information and systems.
This privacy notice is designed to inform you about how your personal information
is collected, managed, and used to:
-  Safeguard devices and data
-  Manage our relationship with you
-  Improve security products and services to predict future vulnerabilities
-  Protect data
By collecting and processing data, we can help to predict threats and protect
you, your devices and your information. McAfee is committed to becoming as
transparent as possible to help you understand how your data is processed, why it
takes data to protect data, and our commitment to using the personal data we
collect for the purposes discussed in this Notice.  Every time you turn on a device,
connect to a network or open a file, you face significant risk from hackers,
spammers, malware, spyware and other forms of unauthorized access to your data.
This is why it is important to use security products and services such as McAfee's.

To defend against these threats and the thousands of new threats that emerge each
day, McAfee technologies may:

  Analyze data sent to your devices for signs of risk or suspicious activity in
order to take corrective action
  Assess the reputation of the sending device to determine whether access
should be allowed or if the transaction should be continued;
  Adapt responses to new threats based on intelligence from our global
network. .

Please read about our privacy practices and let us know if you have any questions.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Scope</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>This Privacy Notice applies to personal information we obtain from individuals
interacting with McAfee and its websites, products, services, and applications.  This
Notice does not apply to personal information we obtain in our capacity as an
employer.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Notice</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We provide access to our Privacy Notice by:
  Linking to it throughout our websites
  Referencing it in our terms of use and end user license agreements
  Incorporating it into our contracts and other legal agreements as necessary</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>The Information we collect</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>McAfee collects some information that is personal (i.e., information that identifies an
individual either alone or in combination with other data).  McAfee also collects
non-personal information that does not, on its own, identify an individual person.
When non-personal information is combined with other information so that it does
identify an individual person, we treat that combination as personally identifiable
information.
McAfee collects personal information when you or someone acting on your behalf
provides it to us. We also collect information when you obtain or use McAfee
products, services or when you communicate with a device using McAfee's services.
The following are examples of the type of personal information that may be
collected, directly from you (or someone acting on your behalf)
  Contact information (including name, email address, mailing address,
telephone and fax number)
  Payment information (including payment card and bank account
information);
  Shipping, billing and other information provided in connection with the
purchase or shipment of McAfee products and services;
  Information about transactions with us (such as purchase history) and use of
our products and services;
  Information provided by you through McAfee-related communication
channels such as forums, technical support, and customer service;
  Username, password and other information used to verify identity; and
  Photographs or other biometrics when submitted
The following are examples of the type of information that may be collected by
McAfee, from your web browser or from interactions with our products and
services:
  Details about your computers, devices, applications and networks (including
IP address, browser characteristics, device ID and characteristics, device
operating system information and system language preferences);
  activities on our websites and usage patterns of products and services;
referring URLs, dates and times of website visits, and clickstream data such
as information commonly recorded in web server logs;  and
  details about Internet or network usage (such as the URLs or domain names
of websites you visit, information about applications that attempt to access
your network, or traffic data);
  data about files and communications, such as potential malware or spam
(which may include computer files, emails and attachments, email addresses,
metadata and traffic data related to files and communications, or portions or
hashes -- a hash file is a file that has been converted into a numerical string
by a mathematical algorithm -- of any of this information); this may include
similar  information from third parties interacting with you;
  other information used in the operation of our products and services (such as
information regarding the number of checked, suspicious, infected or
unwanted files or emails; the number of malware infections); and
  Information that may be included in a virus or malware sample or a file you
consider to be suspicious that you submit to McAfee for review.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>IP Addresses</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>An Internet Protocol address (IP address) is a numerical label assigned to
each device (e.g., computer, printer, server) participating in a computer network
that uses the Internet Protocol for communication.  It is how devices such as
computers find each other on the network.
Where it is sometimes possible that IP addresses can be associated with a single
individual's system, they most often are associated with a group of systems, one
system shared by many users or a gateway into a group of systems or devices.
For instance, IP addresses included in an email communication are typically
associated with the respective email service provider and not with your device.
McAfee security products and services, like those of many security companies,
depend on IP addresses to protect your information, your devices and your
privacy. For example, we may detect that a system or a group of systems
associated with a particular IP address has been compromised and is sending
malware or spam to some of our users.

Even without identifying who owns a compromised system or who
compromised it, we can assign a score to that IP address to reflect the
heightened threat it poses.  Our products and services can then divert your
traffic away from this IP address or block this IP address from sending malware
to your McAfee-protected device before your device is a victim of an attack.
The use of IP addresses and other machine data is critical to the ability to keep
security protections current, relevant and effective as cyber threats and attacks
evolve over time.
McAfee protects the collection of IP addresses – regardless of whether they are
associated with any particular individual's system or a group of systems.  We do
not use IP addresses that our security tools gather for marketing purposes such
as online behavioral advertising or to push marketing messages.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Cookies</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>McAfee uses “cookies” to remember user preferences and to maximize the
performance of our website and services.  Additionally, cookies help us to identify
returning users so, for example, we don't need to ask them to enter their email and
password on every visit.
Please note the information gathered by cookies is necessary to provide some
McAfee services, including certain subscriptions. We do not provide those services
to users who do not give their consent to the data processing carried out through
cookies or whose browsers are set to reject all cookies.  For example, when you
purchase a subscription to an online technology, a cookie is set that identifies the
version of the protective software and when it expires.  We use this information to
alert you that a newer version is available or if your subscription is going to
terminate and, thus, leave your system open to attack.
Cookies may also be used to control the type and/or frequency of ads, promotions,
or other marketing messages the customer views. These ads may be placed by third-
party advertising companies which are our vendors  McAfee also uses “web
beacons” (small transparent image files) to count visitors to our sites and analyze
how visitors use our sites. The information collected is generally anonymized and is
not used to identify any particular user.
As is common on the Internet, McAfee maintains log files of the traffic that visits our
sites. For example, our servers may automatically record the information you or
your browser send when you visit a website. These log files may include
information such as your requests, IP address, browser type, browser language, the
date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify
your system.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Use of the Personal Information we collect</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>McAfee uses the information it collects in ways that serve your security and
privacy needs, including the following:
  Provide threat prediction and protection products and services;
  Provide security advisories, information and product updates;
  Conduct research and analysis (for example, market and consumer research,
security research and analysis, and trend analysis);
  Analyze users' behavior when using McAfee products and services to
customize users' preferences;
  Establish and manage McAfee accounts;
  Collect and process payments and complete transactions;
  Provide customer support, manage subscriptions and respond to requests,
questions and comments;
  Communicate about, and administer participation in, special events,
programs, surveys, contests, sweepstakes, and other offers and promotions;
  Enable posting on our blogs and other communications;
  Customize, measure, and improve our websites properties and advertising;
  Analyze and develop new products, services and websites;
  Perform accounting, auditing, billing, reconciliation and collection activities;
  Prevent detect, identify, investigate, and protect against potential or actual
claims, liabilities, prohibited behavior,  and criminal activity;
  Comply with and enforce applicable legal requirements, agreements and
policies; and
  Perform other activities consistent with this Notice.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Products and Services Data Processing</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>If you use one of our products or services, software will operate in the background
of your computer system or device environment to perform specific security and
privacy protections including:
  Spam protection
  Virus protection
  Intrusion protection
  Threat Prevention and Prediction
  Home Network Defense
  Data Encryption
  Mobile Device Lockdown</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Product Updating and Reporting</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Our products and services may also process certain data to provide updates and
reports.  These update functions may check your system to see whether files
relating to the services need to be refreshed or modernized.

For example, products and services may transmit report files to McAfee. These files
contain information, including  the number of checked, suspicious, infected or
unwanted files or emails, the number of infections, the date and hash values of the
detected infections and the number of false negatives/false positives. The purpose
of these reports is to analyze the frequency of particular infections or the prevalence
of threats. McAfee will also adapt the product where necessary to user preferences
based on actual use of the product.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Personal Information We Share</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We may share personal information with:
  Other members of the McAfee family of companies for the purposes
described in this Privacy Notice, such as to (i) provide services and joint
content (such as registration, sales, and customer support); (ii) help detect
and prevent potentially illegal acts and violations of our policies; and (iii)
guide our decisions about our products, services and communications.
  Service providers and authorized partners who perform services for us (such
as data storage, sales, fraud investigations and bill collection) based on our
instructions.  These third parties are not authorized by us to use or disclose
personal information except as necessary to perform services on our behalf
or comply with legal requirements.
  Third parties with your consent.  For example, co-marketing with a business
partner or sharing limited information as necessary with security research
analysts;
  Other business entities legally related to McAfee, such as our parent
company, Intel, Inc. or any third party that may take over all or part of
McAfee's functions in the future (provided that such party agrees to use such
personal information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice).
Should a further combination occur, we will require that the new combined
entity follow this Privacy Notice with respect to your personal information.
We may also disclose personal information (i) if we are required to do so by law
or legal process ; (ii) in response to requests by government agencies, such as
law enforcement authorities or other authorized third-parties; (iii) as may be
required for purposes of national security; or (iv) when we believe disclosure is
necessary and appropriate to prevent physical, financial or other harm, injury or
loss or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity
or exposure to legal liability.
McAfee will not disclose your personal information to non-affiliate third parties
for their own marketing purposes unless you have provided consent.

McAfee family companies may share personal information with each other and use
it in a manner that is consistent with this Notice. We may also combine it with other
information to provide and improve our products, services, content and advertising.
Where we share this personal information with a third party with a contractual
relationship with us (such as a provider of services to McAfee) these entities must
comply with standards at least as stringent as McAfee's processing standards and
are limited to those standards unless you wish to create your own independent
relationship with that provider.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>California Shine the Light Law</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>McAfee does not share your personal information with third parties for their own
marketing use without your permission.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Security</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We use administrative, organizational, technical and physical safeguards to protect
the personal information we maintain and ensure it is used according to this Notice.
Our security controls are designed to restrict access to the information to
authorized personnel only.  We regularly test our website for security
vulnerabilities.    When you make a payment on our website using your credit card,
we use SSL encryption in the transmission to McAfee of the credit card number.  We
require Service Providers maintain at least the same level of security we expect of
ourselves.
McAfee complies with the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard that
requires merchants to implement security measures for credit card information.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>How you can manage and control your personal information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We offer certain choices about how we communicate with our users and what
personal information we obtain about them.  Many McAfee products allow users to
make choices about the personal information collected.
  You may choose not to receive marketing email communications from us by
clicking on the unsubscribe link or other instructions in our marketing
emails, visiting the My Account section on our website or contacting us as
specified in the “How to Contact Us” section below.
  Many McAfee products contain settings that allow users or administrators to
control how the products collect information.  Please refer to the relevant
product manual or contact us through the appropriate technical support channel
for assistance.
  To remove your personal information from a McAfee website testimonial, please
contact customer service.
If you chose to no longer receive marketing information, McAfee may still
legitimately communicate with you regarding such things as security updates,
product functionality, responses to service requests or other transaction related
communications.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>How you can access and correct inaccuracies</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>If you wish to contact us in relation to any personal information you may request
access to such information so that we can correct or amend the information by
contacting us as indicated below.  In certain circumstances we may be required to
retain data we have about you (such as for tax or other business purposes or if
required by law or by authorities).</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Data Retention</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>The time periods for which we retain your personal information depend on the
purposes for which we use it.  McAfee will keep your personal information for as
long as you are a registered subscriber or user of our products and, thereafter, for
no longer than is reasonably necessary for internal reporting and reconciliation
purposes pursuant to legal requirements and to provide you with any feedback or
information you might request or require.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Storage of the information we collect from you</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>The information we collect may be stored in servers in the United States and
wherever McAfee and its service providers have facilities, as well as your web
browser (see section on cookies above).</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Children's Privacy</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>McAfee complies with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of the United
States of America where it applies to our information protection activities. McAfee
does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.
If we learn we have collected personal information on a child under the age of 13
without proper consent, we will delete that data from our systems.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Data Transfer</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We may transfer the personal information we obtain to countries other than the
country in which the information originally was collected.  Those countries may not
have as comprehensive data protection laws as the country from which McAfee
initially obtained the information.  When we transfer the information to other
countries, we will protect that information as described in this Privacy Notice.

If you are located in the European Economic Area or Switzerland, we comply with
applicable legal requirements providing adequate protection for the transfer of
personal information to countries outside of the EEA or Switzerland.  McAfee is
certified under the Safe Harbor privacy framework as set forth by the U.S.
Department of Commerce, the European Commission and Switzerland regarding the
collection, storage, use, transfer and other processing of personal data transferred
from the European Economic Area or Switzerland to the U.S.  Click here to view our
Safe Harbor Certification</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Updating the Privacy Notice</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We may update this Notice at any time by posting additions or modifications on this
web page.  If at any point we decide to use personal information in a manner
materially different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users
by email or via a prominent notice on our website, and where necessary we will
seek the prior consent of our users.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Links to Other Websites</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Our websites may contain links to other websites for your convenience and
information.  These websites may be operated by companies not affiliated with
McAfee.  Linked websites may have their own privacy policies or notices, which we
strongly suggest you review if you visit any linked websites.  We are not responsible
for the content of any websites that are not affiliated with McAfee, any use of those
websites, or the privacy practices of those websites.
In certain circumstances, where the information of third parties is collected by us by
virtue of the third-party's interaction with you (such as the information of those
individuals who send communications to your computer), we rely on you to provide
the relevant third parties with any requisite notice and to obtain any requisite
consent.
Your agreement to our Privacy Notice
You expressly consent to McAfee's processing of information as described in this
Privacy Notice when you:
  Provide information to us through our websites;
  Buy or license our products or services and accept the terms of user or end-
user license; or
  Sign a contract with McAfee for products and services.
In addition, through these uses and interactions with McAfee Products, Services or
Websites, you specifically consent to our collection of personal information by
automated means, such as cookies or the intended functionality of a product or
service, and to our subsequent processing of the information in accordance with this
Privacy Notice and to the storage and transfer of the information to locations
wherever McAfee and its service providers have facilities.


Contact Us
If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Notice, or would like to
update information we have about you or your preferences, please contact us by:
  Emailing the Privacy Program Office of McAfee, Inc.
at privacy@mcafee.com;
  Calling us at 972-963-7902;
  Writing to us at:
Privacy Program Office - McAfee, Inc.
2821 Mission College Blvd.
Santa Clara, CA 95054
If you do not receive a response, contact the Consumer Privacy Response Team of
McAfee, Inc. by emailing consumer_privacy_response_team@mcafee.com or by
writing to Consumer Privacy Response Team, 5000 Headquarters Drive, Plano,
Texas 75024.
If you are located in the European Economic Area, please write to:
Privacy Program Office - McAfee Security S.A.R.L.
26, Boulevard Royal
2449 Luxembourg, Luxembourg
In addition to McAfee, Inc., the McAfee entity with which you have a business
relationship is responsible for ensuring your personal information is collected and
processed according to this Notice.
For the U.S., Mexico, Central America, South America, and the Caribbean, this is:
McAfee, Inc., 2821 Mission College Blvd., Santa Clara, California 95054
For Canada, Europe, the Middle East, Africa, Asia, and the Pacific Rim, this is: McAfee
Security S.A.R.L., 26, Boulevard Royal, 2449 Luxembourg, Luxembourg
For Japan, this is:   McAfee Co., Ltd., Shibuya Mark City West Building 12-1,
Dogenzaka 1-Chrome, Shibuya-ku, Tokyo 150-0043, Japan


Last Modified December 19, 2012.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
