<POLICY modification_date="December 31, 2013" policy_url="http://www.consumerreports.org/cro/2012/10/privacy-policy-highlights/index.htm" website_category="Home" website_index="043" website_url="consumerreports.org">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>Privacy Policy Highlights
Last updated: December 2013
Effective Date: December 31, 2013

We want consumers to be informed of our privacy practices. The following applies to the entire Consumer Reports family of information products, programs and services and covers how we collect and use the information we receive from all marketing and distribution channels. For more information, please read our complete Privacy Policy.  Please note that the Consumers Union Privacy Policy applies to information provided or collected in connection with our consumer advocacy programs and campaigns and their associated websites.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Information We Collect</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>In all marketing channels we do collect information you choose to submit to us, for example, when you subscribe directly to one of our publications or online services, place an order, or participate in a contest.
We may obtain additional information about you, such as updated address, payment card, demographic or lifestyle information, from other sources.
You can visit us online without telling us who you are or giving us personal information.
We use common Internet technologies, such as cookies and web beacons, on our Web sites, mobile products and in our e-mails.
Additional details</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Uses of information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We use the information you submit to provide the products and services you request. Our products and services may include the presentation of personalized content.
We use your information to inform you of other products, programs or services offered by Consumer Reports.
Additional details</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Sharing Your Personally Identifiable Information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Information about those participants in our consumer advocacy campaigns who have consented to receive communications regarding our advocacy activities, may be rented or shared with our affiliate, Consumers Union Action Fund, Inc., a 501(c)(4) nonprofit consumer advocacy organization.
We may also share information about donors to Consumer Reports Foundation or Consumers Union with Consumers Union Action Fund, Inc.
If you become a new customer of Consumer Reports on or after January 3, 2013 and later make a donation directly to our organization, we may provide that information to our affiliates, including Consumers Union Action Fund, Inc. and Consumer Media LLC, operator of The Consumerist website.  We may also exchange, rent or otherwise provide information from such donors (including full name, address and donation information but excluding email address, telephone numbers and any financial account information) with other organizations.
We may share information about you with vendors we have hired to provide services on our behalf.
We may share information about you with companies that provide online content to Consumer Reports, if those companies host that content on our behalf.
We will not share your e-mail address with other companies for offers of their products and services, including companies that provide content on behalf of Consumer Reports.
We may share your name and postal address with selected other companies for direct-mail offers of their products and services.
Additional details</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Your privacy choices</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>You may unsubscribe from our e-mail newsletters and promotions.
You may direct us not to share your name and address with other companies for offers of their products and services. If you would like to do so, click here for information.
Click here to change your fundraising solicitation preferences and/or opt out of donor information sharing with unaffiliated third parties.
You may direct us not to send you direct mail promotional materials or call you about Consumer Reports products, programs and services.
You may decline participation in our surveys, including our Annual Questionnaire.
You may also turn off cookies in your browser.
We provide you with the ability to access and edit your personal account information.
Additional details</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Important information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We encourage you to read our full Privacy Policy.
We take steps to protect the information you provide us against unauthorized users. Learn more.
Our products and services are for a general audience and intended for adults only. We do not knowingly request personal information from children.
Personal information you provide will be maintained in the United States. Some personal information provided by users may be transferred to, processed and stored temporarily by our service providers in other countries.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>How to contact us</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Questions about our Consumer Reports Privacy Policy or about Consumer Reports' handling of your information may be sent to:

Consumer Reports Customer Relations
Attn: Privacy
101 Truman Avenue
Yonkers, NY 10703

Consumers Union is an expert, independent, nonprofit organization whose mission is to work for a fair, just, and safe marketplace for all consumers and to empower consumers to protect themselves. To maintain its independence and impartiality, CU accepts no outside advertising and no free samples and employs several hundred mystery shoppers and technical experts to buy and test the products it evaluates.

Learn more.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
