<POLICY modification_date="April 30, 2013" policy_url="http://www.williamhill.us/privacy-policy" website_category="Games" website_index="013" website_url="williamhill.com">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>Privacy Policy
WILLIAM HILL'S PRIVACY POLICY

LAST UPDATED:  April 30, 2013</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>OUR COMMITMENT TO YOUR PRIVACY</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Your privacy is important to American Wagering, Inc.  (together, with its subsidiaries and affiliated companies, referred to as “William Hill,” “us,” “our,” or “we”) therefore we have developed a Privacy Policy that covers how we collect, use, disclose, transfer and store your information.  Please take a moment to familiarize yourself with our privacy practices so you can make an informed decision as to whether to use our “Services” (as defined in our Terms of Service).</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>APPLICATION AND SCOPE OF THIS POLICY</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>This Privacy Policy applies only to William Hill.  It does not apply to the practices of companies we do not own or control, or to people that we do not employ.  Though our website may contain links to other websites we are not responsible for, nor does our privacy policy apply to, those websites operated by third parties.  This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is subject to our Terms of Service.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>WHY WE COLLECT INFORMATION</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We collect information in order to:

•Enable us to set up, operate and manage your remote wagering account so that you can make full use of our Services;

•Verify your location, age and identity when you are using your remote wagering account;

•Comply with relevant regulations regarding your registration;

•Enable us to receive questions and comments from you so we can provide technical assistance;

•Keep you informed of future events, offers and promotions.

We also collect, use, share, transfer and store information as set forth below.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Through our website, kiosks, your wireless device utilizing the William Hill Mobile Sports App,  our Ticket Writers, and the remote account wagering registration process we collect Personal and Non-Personal Information (as defined below).

PERSONAL INFORMATION is data that can be used to uniquely identify or contact a single person.

•Registration Information.  When you register for or use our Services and download the William Hill Mobile Sports App, we may collect “Personal Information” from you, such as your name, date of birth, mailing address, email address, mobile phone number, wireless carrier, telephone number, and fax number through which you can be identified.  We may also ask you for Personal Information such as your credit or debit card number, financial account number, driver's license number, state identification card number, Social Security number, passport number, naturalization number, and/or the beneficiary of your William Hill money bearing account (i.e., your William Hill remote wagering account), which when combined with your name is then deemed “Confidential Personal Information“.

NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION is information about you or your activities through which you cannot be personally identified.  In situations where it is possible to do so, Non-Personal Information may be linked to Personal Information.  Non-Personal Information includes:

•Profile Information. When using our Services you may provide other information such as interests and hobbies, age, gender, relationship status, purchase information, favorite sports type and team preference, fan affiliation and wagering activity.  We call this “Profile Information.”

•Location Information. To provide our Services to you, we collect and use information related to the actual geographic location of your wireless device; we obtain this information from your wireless carrier, certain third-party service providers, or directly from the wireless device you used to register for our Services.

•Cookies and other technologies. When you use our Services we may send and access one or more cookies (a small amount of data which often includes an anonymous unique identifier which is sent to your browser from a website or computer and stored on your hardware).  We use cookies to remember personal information when you use our website, online services, and applications.  We may use this information during your subsequent visits.  Please review your web browser “Help” file to learn how to modify your cookie settings.

•Log File Information. When you use our Services, our servers automatically gather and store certain information about your usage. These server logs may include information such as a wireless device identification number and device identifier, web requests, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, search terms, ratings, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, features used in our Services, our wireless application(s), alerts received, advertisements delivered, the amount of time spent on particular screens, the dates and times of your requests, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>HOW WE USE INFORMATION</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Except for Confidential Personal Information, we may use Personal Information and Non-Personal Information for our own marketing purposes, including notifying you of special promotions, offers and events specifically tailored to you and your special interests via mail, email, telephone, text message, and other means.  Confidential Personal Information will not be used for our own marketing purposes without your express consent.

•With your consent, we use your Confidential Personal Information, Personal Information, and Non-Personal Information to enable us to set up, operate, and manage your remote wagering account, and to provide to you, and maintain, all of the features (including text invitations to private contests or tournaments, alerts to changes in the odds or close of betting session for a game, injury reports, or winning a game, a contest or a tournament, and updates to the William Hill Mobile Sports App) and functionality of our Services.

•With your consent, we also use your location information to determine whether (i) you are in a jurisdiction where our Services are lawful, (ii) your wireless device matches your account while you are in the William Hill Services approved jurisdiction, (iii) which of our Services alerts are relevant to you.  We reserve the right to use your anonymous location information for other purposes.

•We may also use your Personal Information and Non-Personal Information (such as location and anonymous log file information) to track and analyze your user preferences and trends to improve the quality and design of our Services and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services.

•We may further use cookies and log file information to: (i) remember information so you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you use or visit our Services, (ii) provide custom and personalized content, advertisements, and information, (iii) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns, and (iv) monitor aggregate usage metrics.

•We may also use a third-party data source to verify your mobile phone number is on a wireless provider we support.  If you have a supported mobile phone number and device, then we may send a text message to your phone in order to verify your custody of that handset.  If your carrier or handset is not supported, then we may store your mobile phone number and may send a one-time text message to you when our Services become available on your wireless provider or handset.

•We may use your email address or mobile number from time-to-time to send you messages from us such as privacy or security related notices, notifying you of major updates to our Services, or for other customer service purposes.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>WHEN WE SHARE INFORMATION</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>•Except for Confidential Personal Information, we may share Personal Information and Non-Personal Information with our parent, subsidiaries and affiliated companies, or other businesses or persons to: (i) the extent necessary to permit validation of your identity, completion of a purchase or credit transaction, processing and recording of a betting transaction, or other legitimate non-marketing business purposes, (ii) provide certain features, (iii) serve relevant advertisements in support of our Services, and (iv) process such information on our behalf.  We require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with this Privacy Policy and use appropriate confidentiality and security measures, and we use reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information.

•We may disclose aggregate, anonymous log file and usage information in reports to interested third parties to assist those parties in understanding the usage patterns and performance results of certain advertisements, content, services, promotions, or features. For example, we may provide aggregate level reports to an advertising partner for the purpose of showing delivery and performance statistics of a specific advertising campaign.

•We may release Personal Information, including Confidential Personal Information, and Non-Personal Information if required to do so by law, or if we in good faith believe that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws or respond to a court order, subpoena, or search warrant.

•We may also disclose Confidential Personal Information, Personal Information, and Non-Personal Information about you if we determine, in good faith, that disclosure  is reasonably necessary to: enforce our Terms of Service; take precautions against liability; protect users from or to investigate, prevent or take action regarding fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful uses or activities; investigate and defend ourselves against any third-party claims or allegations; assist government enforcement agencies; protect the security or integrity of our Services; or protect our rights, property, or personal safety or those of our users, or others.

•We may share or sell your anonymous location information to third parties.

•We may transfer information about you if we are acquired by or merged with another company.  In this event we will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>HOW YOU CAN UPDATE YOUR ACCOUNT INFORMATION</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>You may update your account information at any time by contacting us at contact@williamhill.us.  To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps to verify your identity before making changes.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>OUR COMMITMENT TO DATA SECURITY</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and to protect personal information about you, we have put in place commercially reasonable physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations.  We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information that we receive on your behalf to operate our Services or that you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.  We also cannot guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.

If we learn of a security systems breach we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps and/or post a notice on our website if a security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing.

We will retain your Personal Information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>OUR COMMITMENT TO THE PRIVACY OF CHILDREN AND ADULTS UNDER 21</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We do not knowingly collect or maintain personal information from anyone under 21 years of age.  If we learn that we have collected the personal information of someone under 21 years of age we will take the appropriate steps to protect this information.  If you are a parent or guardian and discover that your child has submitted personal information, you may alert us at contact@williamhill.us.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>INTERNATIONAL VISITORS</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Our Services are based in the United States. You may not utilize the William Hill Mobile Sports App outside of Nevada.  If you are using any other services from the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, then please note that you are transferring your personal data to the United States and by providing your personal data you consent to that transfer.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>THIRD-PARTY ADVERTISERS AND AD-SERVING COMPANIES</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Third-party advertisers or ad network companies may sometimes deliver (“or serve”) advertisements, that may appear on our website, directly to users.  These companies may automatically receive your IP address or other information about your wireless device or personal computer when serving advertisements. These third parties may also download cookies to your computer, or use other technologies such as JavaScript and “web beacons” (also known as “1×1 gifs”) to measure the effectiveness of the advertisements served and to personalize advertising content.  Doing this allows the advertiser or ad network to recognize your computer or wireless device each time they send you an advertisement in order to measure the effectiveness of the ad and to personalize advertising content.  These companies may compile information about the sites or services visited when seeing advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked.  We do not access or have control of the cookies that these third-party advertisers or ad networks may place.  Likewise, third party advertisers and ad networks do not have access to your personal information stored with us unless you choose to share it with them. This Privacy Policy does not cover the use of tracking technologies or personal data by any such third-party advertisers or ad networks.  We encourage you to learn about the privacy practices of those third parties.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>IN THE EVENT OF MERGER, SALE, OR BANKRUPTCY</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>In the event that we are acquired by or merge with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected from our users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control so that our Services can continue operations.  In the unlikely event of a bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>This Privacy Policy describes our current practices and may be revised from time to time without further notice to you.  Our policy indicates when it was “Last Updated.”  Thus, please visit our website and review this Privacy Policy periodically to learn of any changes.  Your continued use of our Services after the posting of any changes constitutes your binding acceptance of such changes.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>HOW TO CONTACT US</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy please email us at legal@williamhill.us or contact us at:

William Hill
Legal Department – Privacy Policy Issues
6325 S. Rainbow Blvd., Suite 100
Las Vegas, NV  89118</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>YOUR CONSENT TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>By using our Services (including, the William Hill Mobile Sports App), you consent to:  (1) receive text messages, (including advertisements), data, emails and information sent through other data channels; (2) pay carrier data, messaging, and other fees resulting from your usage of our Services; and (3) the collection, use, disclosure, transfer, and storage of your Personal and Non-Personal Information (including location information related to your wireless device) as described in this Privacy Policy.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
