<POLICY modification_date="" policy_url="http://www.hopkinsmedicine.org/Privacy/" website_category="Health" website_index="062" website_url="hopkinsmedicine.org">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Privacy Policy and Disclaimer</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>All health and health-related information contained within this Johns Hopkins Medicine Web site is intended to be general in nature and should not be used as a substitute for a visit with a health care professional. The advice is intended to offer only a general basis for individuals to discuss their medical condition with their health care provider. Your health care provider should be consulted regarding matters concerning the medical condition, treatment and needs of you and your family.

Although every effort is made to ensure that the material within this Johns Hopkins Medicine Web site is accurate and timely, it is provided for the convenience of the Web site user and should not be considered official. Users of this Web site are advised to refer to and rely upon the official version of information when making significant decisions, including decisions related to employment opportunities at Hopkins.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>See Also</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Privacy Information
Patient Privacy Information</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Stored Information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Please be aware most information transmitted over the Internet is not secure; thus, confidentiality cannot be guaranteed.

Of the information we learn about you from your visit to Johns Hopkins Medicine Web sites, we store the following: the IP address from which you access the Internet, the date and time, the Internet address of the Web site from which you linked directly to our site, the name of the file or the words you searched, and the browser used to access our site. This information is used to measure the number of visitors to the various sections of our site and identify system performance or problem areas. We also use this information to help us improve features of the site and to make the site more useful.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Personally Provided Information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>If you choose to provide us with personal information by sending an email, or by filling out a form with your personal information and submitting it through our Web site, we use that information to respond to your message and to help us provide you with information or material that you request. We do not give, share, sell, or transfer any personal information to a third party unless required by law.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Links to Other Sites</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Please note that some pages within this Web site, for the convenience of users, are linked to Web sites not managed by Johns Hopkins Medicine. Neither The Johns Hopkins University nor The Johns Hopkins Health System review, control or take responsibility for the content of those Web sites.

Links from this Web site to Web sites not managed by Johns Hopkins Medicine do not imply endorsement or credibility of the service, information or product offered through the linked sites

Some Johns Hopkins Medicine Web sites provide links to other internet sites that provide health information. Once you link to another site, you are subject to the privacy policy of the new site.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
