<POLICY modification_date="" policy_url="http://www.pinkbike.com/about/legal/#privacy-policy" website_category="Kids_and_Teens" website_index="092" website_url="pinkbike.com">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>Privacy Policy</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Visitors</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Pinkbike does not collect information from not logged in visitors interacting with the site. A cookie and ip address may be tracked to allow technology to better the visitor experience during a session. Session data is cleared when a browser is closed.

Visitors may recieve third-party advertising. See point 5</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Members</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Pinkbike offers the ability to register as a member of the website allowing a richer community experience. Members use their email address and other personal information in the process.
Your email address is NEVER shown to visitors or other members of the community
Age, gender, and IP information may be used as an identifier during thrid-party advertising.
Pinkbike never shares your email address with any third party.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Uploaded Material</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>As a member of Pinkbike you may upload your videos and photos.
Your uploaded material is viewable by all visitors and members.
You may, at any time, delete or remove your uploaded material
You may, only upload material that is your own, or you have the copyright to.
Pinkbike adheres to the 1998 DMCA Safe Harbor Provisions. admin@pinkbike.com</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>News Letter</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Pinkbike may send out an opt-out news letters to members.
Members can opt out from newsletter communication.
We hate junk mail. In 8 years of operation we have not yet sent out a newsletter.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Third-party Advertisers, Links to Other Sites</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Pinkbike allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within the Pinkbike Site. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the Pinkbike Site. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see.

Pinkbike does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. However, please note that if an advertiser asks Pinkbike to show an advertisement to a certain audience (for example, men aged 18-34) or audience segment (for example, men aged 18-24 who have viewed certain channels of content) and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach. The advertiser may also use information regarding your use of the Pinkbike Site, such as the number of times you viewed an ad (but not any personally identifiable information), to determine which ads to deliver to you.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
