<POLICY modification_date="" policy_url="http://www.funtrivia.com/privacypolicy.html" website_category="Games" website_index="088" website_url="funtrivia.com">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>FunTrivia.com Privacy Policy


Return to Homepage</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Overview</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>This Privacy Statement discloses our policies regarding information we obtain from you and how we limit and protect the uses to which that information is put.

We are committed to building users' trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the principles of disclosure and informed consent. Accordingly, we wish to notify you about:

What information is collected from you through the FunTrivia.com site.

How that information may be used, including with whom it may be shared.

Choices you have about collection, use and distribution of your information.

How you can access, update or delete your information.

These policies apply only to the Site, which consists solely of those web pages we control. You should determine what privacy policies apply to other web sites before providing information to them.

If you have questions or concerns regarding these policies, or any other aspect of the Site or your use of it, please contact us by clicking here.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>What Information We Collect and How We Collect It</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Through your use of the Site, we may obtain various types of basic contact and user information from you such as your IP (or Internet) address, your user name, email address, and password. While we store this information in our database and endeavour to protect that data, we can offer no warranties or guarantees. Any data you submit to FunTrivia is ultimately submitted at your own risk.

Player user names are displayed all over the site to identify players. Players should not use personally identifying information in their user names.

We use player email addresses to contact a player if a password is forgotten, send "daily trivia" when specifically requested by the player, and to send yearly website updates which can be unsubscribed from. We also request that a user provide their email address in our feedback section, so that we can respond to their problem. Private tournaments ask for email addresses so that we can likewise contact players if they forget their passwords, and so that we can send out monthly tournament emails (which can be unsubscribed from). Finally, FunTrivia Forums require an email for similar contact purposes.

We use player IP addresses to help track down cheating, and to provide us a way to prevent players from accessing the website for abuse, spam, illegal activities, account infractions, etc. Private tournament administrators have access to player IP addresses. Finally, we display in the email the IP address of the player who sends an email from a form on our website to external email addresses, to prevent/track spammers. For example, if someone abuses our "I have forgotten my password" form to send unwanted emails to another user, we can use that IP information to determine where the abuse is originating from.

Player city, state, and country is public and appears in user profiles. It is used to display regional scoreboards and statistics for some of our trivia games. Players are free to leave this information blank.

Player hobbies and info fields appear in user profiles. This information is all public and available to search engines. Players are asked to carefully consider what they write in these sections, for personal security.

The FunTrivia Forums is a separate piece of software, and has its own fields (most optional) for information such as home town, etc. Players should assume that everything except their email address is public information.

FunTrivia does not store important information such as credit card numbers, bank information, or social security numbers on its servers. All billing is handled, managed, and tracked entirely by 3rd parties such as Paypal.com (for our gold membership), and we do not store that information ourselves.

We also collect and store http logs, statistics, usage logs, and other information about the online activities of our visitors, primarily for error and abuse tracing. This information is never offered to 3rd parties, unless required by law.

We obtain information in several ways. Some is required as part of the registration process. Additional information is gathered through "cookies", which deposit special codes on your computer.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>FunTrivia Private Tournaments</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>The administator of a private tournament is able to see the IP addresses of all participants in his/her tournament, so that he can track down cheating and lock-out abusive users within the game.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>FunTrivia Message Boards</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Players should assume that all information they input to FunTrivia message boards, forums, and chat boards is publicly accessible. Search engines such as Google regularly pick up content from these boards, so players should assume that their posts will eventually be indexed.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>User Fun Trivia Mailboxes</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>FunTrivia player mailboxes carry no guarantee of privacy and should not be used for sensitive or personal discussions. Our messaging system was designed and intended for discussions related to quizzes, corrections and non-sensitive discussion. This privacy warning is reiterated on the "send message" screen. Most volunteer editors have access to user messages in order to handle corrections, quiz notes, etc, and site administrators have access to read / monitor messages for abuse, spam, etc. Sensitive or personal discussions should be conducted outside of the FunTrivia.com website via email. Our editors and administors retain the right to delete any message.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Team Message Boards</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Team message boards are publicly accessible. Participants should not assume any additional level of privacy on these boards.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>How We Use Your Information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We generally use your information only to operate the Site and make your experience more efficient, effective and enjoyable.

As a general practice, we do not sell, rent or otherwise give user submitted information to any other party, except in limited circumstances such as compliance with law or with your permission, as noted below. Thus, we would not sell your name, email address or other personal information to mass marketers. If FunTrivia is acquired or becomes part of another organization, we retain the right to trasfer all exclusive control over that data to our new operating entity.

Most uses we make of your information are for site administration of your use of the site, such as processing and tracking of orders, diagnosing problems with our server, identification, security and billing. We may also use this information to contact you for operational purposes, such as tracking of orders, and notifying you of product updates or new products or editions.

We sometimes share aggregated data with some of our partners. However, none of this information identifies you in any way without your consent. For example, we may share data that shows that a certain percentage of our users buy a certain product, but there would be no identification of specific users.

Only if you consent, will we share personal, identifiable data about you to third parties. For example, on particular pages where we ask for personal information, we may explicitly tell you that the data we ask for may by shared with third parties.

There are circumstances where we may need to provide individual information to others. For example, we may disclose information if we in good faith believe it is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who is violating our Conditions of Use of the Site, breaking the law, causing injury to or interference with others or otherwise violating the rights of others. We may also disclose information to the extent we believe in good faith it is required by law or for administrative and other purposes we deem necessary to maintain, service and improve our products and service. In all such circumstances, we will limit what information we disclose to the extent we believe it to be appropriate.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Choices Regarding Collection, Use and Distribution of Information - Opting Out and Corrections</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We may send you emails or other promotions our vendors or we offer that we believe may be of special interest to you. Only FunTrivia (or our agents who are required to comply with these policies) will send you these materials. If you do not wish to receive these materials, you may either modify your account preferences to opt out from such promotions, send an unsubscribe email by the means indicated in the materials or tell us when we collect information from you.

You also have choices concerning cookies. Your Internet browser allows you to accept all cookies, be notified when a cookie is sent or reject all cookies. However, if you reject cookies, we may not be able to customize the content we show you or otherwise learn your preferences. There may also be services that require the use of cookies. This may negatively affect your Site experience. In addition, we may place advertising on the Site that originates from outside advertisers or other third parties. In some cases, if you click on these advertisements, a cookie may be sent to your computer. We do not control these cookies.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Changes In Policies; Terms and Conditions</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We may change these policies from time to time. If any such changes materially and adversely affect the use of your information, we will generally refer to such changes on the Site for a period of time, although our failure to do so will not affect the applicability of such changes. Accordingly, we recommend that you check back to review these policies from time to time, particularly if you have not visited the Site for some time. These policies are also subject to our Terms of Use, which are incorporated herein by reference, and we also recommend that you review those from time to time.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Third Party Cookies</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
