<POLICY modification_date="December 16, 2013" policy_url="http://www.patient.co.uk/privacy-policy" website_category="Health" website_index="023" website_url="patient.co.uk">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>Privacy Policy</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Website Operator</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>This Website is run by Patient.co.uk.

Patient.co.uk is a brand name of Egton Medical Information Systems Limited, a company registered in England with company number 2117205 with registered offices at Rawdon House, Green Lane, Yeadon, Leeds, LS19 7BY.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Website Principles</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Patient.co.uk operates by the following principles:

We do our best to protect your personal details and other information about your account. We are constantly reviewing our processes and procedures to protect your personal information from unauthorised access and use, accidental loss and/or destruction.
We will respect your privacy. You should receive marketing emails only from Patient.co.uk. It will be made clear to you where you have these choices, for example, tick boxes will let you decide whether you wish to receive marketing or newsletters. We may, however, email you occasionally with information or queries about your registration, your subscription account, your Website activity or postings, for example, with reminders, confirmations, warnings or copyright requests.
Sometimes we use other organisations to process your personal information on our behalf. Such processing shall comply with appropriate security measures. We may also independently audit these service providers to ensure that they meet our standards. We may use service providers to help us run the Website or services available on the Website, some of whom may be based outside the EEA.
We explicitly ask when we need information that personally identifies you ("Personal Information"). For example, when you register with the Patient.co.uk discussion forums you are asked for an e-mail address, password and nickname.
We may use technology to track the patterns of behaviour of visitors to our site. This can include using a "cookie" which would be stored on your browser. You can modify your browser to prevent this happening. The information collected in this way can be used to identify you unless you modify your browser settings. For more information on cookies and to learn how to change your settings, read our cookie policy.
If at any time you believe that Patient.co.uk has not adhered to these principles, please notify us by e-mail to the webmaster, and we will use all commercially reasonable efforts to determine and correct the problem promptly.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
