<POLICY modification_date="December 09, 2013" policy_url="http://www.indeed.co.in/legal#privacy" website_category="Business" website_index="009" website_url="indeed.com">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>Privacy Policy

Effective Date: December 9, 2013

Indeed has created this Privacy Policy in order to disclose its use of personal data you give to Indeed when you access or use Indeed's online and/or mobile services, web sites, and software provided on or in connection with the services or web sites (collectively, the “Website”). This Privacy Policy is effective as of December 9, 2013. You may contact Indeed, Inc. at 7501 N. Capital of Texas Hwy, Building B, Austin, TX 78731, USA and Indeed Ireland Operations Limited, First Floor, Block B, Riverside IV, Sir John Rogerson's Quay, Dublin 2, Ireland. Or you can reach either company via our Website contact form.

This Privacy Policy covers only data collected through the Website and not any other data collection or processing, including, without limitation, data collection practices of other web pages to which we link or data that we or our subsidiaries collect offline or through web sites, products, or services that do not display a direct link to this Privacy Policy. Occasionally, we may refer to this Privacy Policy in notices and consent requests related to special-purpose web pages, for example, if we invite you to submit ideas to improve the Website; under such circumstances, this Privacy Policy applies as modified in the particular notice or consent request (e.g., with respect to types of data collected or purposes of collection).</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Information Collected and Utilized</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>When you request information, subscribe for a service, register as a user, participate in a survey, post a rating or review, post a question or answer, post a resume, upload content or otherwise actively send us data on our Website, we usually collect data including, but not limited to, user name, password, first and last name, email address, street address, gender, occupation, interests, messages you send to users and any other data included in a submitted profile or resume. In connection with chargeable services, we will also collect payment information (e.g., credit card number and related verification information). In each such instance, you will know what data we collect through the Website, because you actively submit it.

As part of the standard operation of the Website, Indeed will automatically collect information from your computer or mobile device, including, but not limited to, your browser type, operating system, IP address and the domain name from which you accessed the site, and if you are accessing our site with your mobile device, type of mobile device. In addition we may record actions taken on the Website including, but not limited to, date and times of use, clicks, page views, the amount of time you spend on each page, and search queries. Indeed reserves the right to match your IP address or other information with other information about you in any way permitted by applicable law. Indeed will store this information on its equipment or the equipment of third parties that it has a relationship with for that purpose.

If you access or use the Website on your mobile telephone or other mobile device, including tablets, we collect mobile device identifiers, including MAC Address, and IP Address. Indeed may create and assign to your device an identifier that is similar to an account number. We may collect the name you have associated with your device, device type, telephone number, country, and any other information you choose to provide, such as user name, geo-location or e-mail address. We may also access your contacts to enable you to invite friends to join you in the Website.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Uses of Information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>When you submit information to Indeed, this information will be used for the purposes set forth in Paragraphs 2 and 3 of this Privacy Policy. Indeed uses this information and information generated when you use our Website, including but not limited to your resume, your posted reviews, searches, clicks, taps, web sites and web pages you visit through our mobile software (including third party web sites and web pages), job applications, messages and postings to provide our services and features to you, to provide your information to employers that may be interested in contacting you, to provide employer information to you and to measure and improve those services and features, and to provide you with customer support. If you are located in the USA, Indeed may also share your personal information, such as your email address, with third party websites and/or social networking sites in order to show you targeted advertisements and other content that has been customized for you. If you would like to opt-out of receiving advertisements, please send an email to opt-out @ indeed.com. (remove spaces when sending email)

Indeed may also use the information to prevent potentially illegal activities and activities that are detrimental to you or other users. Indeed may investigate and disclose information from or about you or your use of Indeed if we have a good faith belief that such investigation or disclosure is (a) reasonably necessary to comply with legal process and law enforcement instructions and orders; (b) helpful to prevent, investigate, or identify possible wrongdoing in connection with the use of the Website; or (c) protects our rights, reputation, property, safety, or that of the public. We may use a variety of methods to detect and address anomalous activity and screen content to prevent abuse such as spam. These efforts may on occasion result in a temporary or permanent suspension or termination of some functions for some users.

We may use other companies, including other members of the Indeed corporate group and third parties, to perform services necessary to our operations. In the course of providing these services, those companies may have access to your personal information and such information may be transferred overseas. By contractual agreement, those companies must treat your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. However, we will not be liable (to the fullest extent permitted by law) for any damages that may result from the misuse of your personal information by these companies. Indeed may use your IP address and mobile device information to help diagnose problems with Indeed's service and to administer Indeed's site. Your IP address and mobile device information may also be used to help identify you, your location, and your online profile and to gather broad demographic information (such as country of origin). Indeed may maintain (as permitted by applicable law) your data following your termination of your relationship with Indeed. Indeed may delete your user data as permitted by applicable law. If you provide credit, debit or other payment card and related details to us in order to make a payment, Indeed will use those details only for the purpose of processing the payment. Indeed may also aggregate your data with other data, for the purposes set forth above.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Contact and Resume Information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>When you give Indeed contact information (such as your name and email address) and demographic information, you agree that Indeed may utilize this information as set forth herein. You agree that Indeed may, as part of its services to you, communicate with you, or initiate communication with you on behalf of a 3rd party, through your Indeed account or through other means made available through your contact information such as email, phone, or postal mail. If and to the extent permitted by applicable law, Indeed, or its designated third party partners, may also use your contact information to (i) send you job alerts; (ii) create an account; (iii) send you information about Indeed; and, (iv) if you are located in the USA, send you promotional material from some of Indeed's partners. Indeed may use demographic and/or profile data to tailor your experience on Indeed's site, show you content that Indeed thinks you may be interested in, and display content according to your preferences. Your personal information gets placed on the Indeed Website when you upload or edit a resume. To the extent you upload a resume or edit it, and subject to your Privacy Settings, you are making the resume, your name and other personal information that you place on your resume available to third parties who may be interested in you as an employee, search engines, or to the general public by posting your personal information on the internet. This may be crawled by, and displayed through, search engines when someone searches for your name. This means that third parties can view the personal information contained in your resume and you may receive unsolicited contact from parties unaffiliated with Indeed and for whom Indeed has no responsibility. If you do not want your personal information posted on the Website, you should not upload it. You may opt-out of this feature by editing your Privacy Settings; however, Indeed does not warrant how often third-party search engines will update their caches, which may contain old public resume information. Indeed reserves the right to charge third parties a fee for accessing your information as part of Indeed's services. At your direction, Indeed may also send your resume to third parties if you choose to apply for a job listing.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Consent</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Indeed offers any user the choice to utilize the Indeed website. If you create a resume on, upload your resume to or apply to a job through or otherwise use the Indeed website, you are specifically consenting to the use of any personal information you have provided to Indeed as set forth herein and in the Terms of Service.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Security</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>The Website has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under Indeed's control. Indeed uses SSL encryption, access control policies, anti-virus programs and firewalls to protect information under our control. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. In addition, please note that emails, messages sent via your web browser, and other similar means of communication with other users are not encrypted. We strongly advise you not to communicate any confidential information through these means. Therefore, while we strive to protect your information, we cannot guarantee its security.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Cookies</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>“Cookies” are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Please see our cookie policy for further information regarding Indeed's use of Cookies.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Links</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Indeed may create links to other web sites. When you click on links on Indeed you may leave our Website. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites, and we encourage you to read their privacy statements.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Amendments</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Indeed may amend this Privacy Policy at any time. If Indeed is going to use personally identifiable information collected through Indeed's site in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection Indeed will notify users via email and/or by posting a notice on Indeed's Website for 30 days prior to such use or by other means as required by law.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Assignment</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>If there is a change of ownership or control in Indeed's business (whether by merger, sale, or otherwise) or if there is an asset sale, the user information, including your personal information, could be disclosed as part of such a process and / or sold as part of that transaction and your personally identifying information potentially could be used by the purchaser. However, if that business materially changes this statement or the information-handling practices as described in this Privacy Policy, you will be notified by email and/or through a notice posted on the website, and you may opt-out of the use of your existing information in a new manner. This Privacy Policy inures to the benefit of any successors or assigns of Indeed or the assets of Indeed.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Safe Harbor for EU Residents</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Indeed Inc. complies with the US-EU/Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Economic Area member countries and Switzerland. If you are located in the European Economic Area or Switzerland, Indeed Ireland is the data controller responsible for your information. Indeed Inc. receives data from Indeed Ireland as a data processor and has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view our certification page, please visit http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/ and see our General Safe Harbor Notice.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Accessing Personal Data for EU Residents</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Residents of the European Economic Area and Switzerland have a right of access to their data. If you wish to access such data, please send a certified letter to the above address with a copy of your passport or national identity card (for identity verification purposes) and the same will be provided to you. There may be a charge for such a request (which will not be higher than applicable law permits). European Economic Area and Switzerland residents also have a right, if their personal data is inaccurate, of rectification, erasure or blocking of such inaccurate personal data. You may edit your resume free of charge (if there is an inaccuracy or otherwise), by following procedures set forth on the Indeed Website. If your personal data is inaccurate, you may alternatively request Indeed to rectify, erase or block the data by sending a certified letter, with a copy of your passport or national identity card (for identity verification purposes), to the above address with the exact nature of the requested action.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
