<POLICY modification_date="May 05, 2010" policy_url="http://www.oracle.com/us/legal/privacy/privacy-policy/index.html" website_category="Computers" website_index="095" website_url="java.com">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>Oracle's Privacy Policy

Oracle Corporation and our subsidiaries and affiliates ("Oracle" or "we") respect your preferences concerning the treatment of personal information that we may collect from your use of the Oracle.com Web sites and your interactions with Oracle off-line. This policy lets you know how we collect and use your personal information, and how you can control its use. This policy describes the broadest potential use of personal information throughout the Oracle Web sites and in offline transactions; however, we may make far less use of your personal information.

Because Oracle lines of business and offerings collect and use personal information in different ways, Oracle has established separate privacy policies that govern those different activities. The following privacy policies are specifically tailored to the relevant line of business or offering, and are separate and distinct from the activities governed by this privacy policy:

The services privacy policy addresses customer data to which we may be provided access in order to perform consulting, product support, outsourcing and other services.
The recruiting privacy policy addresses information we may collect in connection with Oracle's employment recruiting efforts.
The Exchange.Oracle.com privacy policy addresses information shared in an online commercial trading community.
The Profit Magazine and Oracle Magazine privacy policy addresses information we collect from subscribers to these publications.
The Oracle.com Web sites provide links to non-Oracle sites we believe may be of interest to you. Those sites are beyond our control. You are advised to check the privacy policies and terms of use of any non-Oracle sites before providing your personal information to them.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>TRUSTe Certification and Safe Harbor</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>TRUSTe European Safe Harbor certification
TRUSTe Certification: Oracle is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. If you have questions about this policy, please fill out an inquiry form. If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact TRUSTe or fax Watchdog Complaints at 415.520.3420, or send postal mail to: Watchdog Complaints, TRUSTe, 55 2nd Street, 2nd Floor, San Francisco, CA USA 94105.

If you are faxing or mailing TRUSTe to register a complaint, you must include the following information: our company name (Oracle); the nature of the alleged privacy violation, including details about how your data was collected and what causes you to believe a violation occurred; the resolution you are requesting; your contact information; and whether you give permission to TRUSTe to share the particulars of your complaint, including your name, with us.

The TRUSTe Click to Verify seal applies to Oracle Web sites and offline privacy practices, services privacy policy, and recruiting privacy policy. It does not cover personal information that may be collected through software downloaded from the Oracle Web sites or in connection with Exchange.Oracle.com or Oracle publications.

Safe Harbor: Oracle is a global corporation, with operations in over 80 countries, and has developed global data practices designed to assure your personal data is appropriately protected. Oracle's privacy practices, including the practices addressed in this policy and those applicable to its services businesses, are self-certified to the United States/European Union Safe Harbor Program. and the United States/Swiss Safe Harbor Program as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union and Switzerland respectively. For more information about Safe Harbor or to access Oracle's certification statement, see Safe Harbor Program. TRUSTe acts as Oracle's third-party dispute resolution provider, as required by the Safe Harbor Program. If you have a complaint concerning Oracle's Safe Harbor compliance, please use the TRUSTe complaint process described above.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Types of Information We Collect and How We Collect It</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Personal Information: This policy covers the following personal information that Oracle collects through your use of the Oracle Web sites and in connection with off-line communications. Specifically, Oracle may collect this information from offline and online registrations and forms, communications and interactions, and sales inquiries and transactions. Oracle also may use third-party sources, such as opt-in lists, as specified in Section 4 below.

Contact information, such as name, physical address, telephone number(s), email address, and company. The majority of the information collected under this category is business contact information and when this information is collected in forms on our web site, it is collected and/or transmitted using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.
Transactional information, including information about the products and services you purchase or download or about which you make an inquiry.
User preferences, such as product requirements, areas of industry interest, newsletters, community choices and other information you select in the customer profile when registering on Oracle.com or indicated by your use of the Oracle Web sites.
Financial/credit card and payment information.
Event and conference participation information, such as lectures, classes or booths attended or visited during an event or conference hosted or attended by Oracle. If we use electronic tracking technologies at an event, we will provide notice in the event registration materials and/or correspondence.
We may supplement information you provide with information received from third parties.

Electronic Communications Protocols and Cookies: In addition to the information specified above, Oracle may collect information about your use of the Oracle.com Web sites through electronic communications protocols and cookies. As is true when you visit most Web sites, Oracle may automatically receive information from you as part of the communication connection itself, which often consists of network routing information (where you came from), equipment information (browser type), your IP address, and date and time. Oracle also uses cookies, embedded URLs and embedded pixels to capture additional information.

Cookies: Oracle's server will query your browser to see if there are "cookies" previously set by the Oracle Web sites. A cookie is a small piece of information sent by a Web server to store on a Web browser so it can later be read back from that browser. Cookies on the Web sites may collect a unique identifier, user preferences and profile information and membership information. Oracle also uses cookies to collect general usage and volume statistical information that does not include personally identifiable information. Some cookies may remain on the user's computer after they leave the Web site, and the majority are set to expire within 30 – 365 days. Your browser may provide you with information and control over cookies. You can set your browser to alert you when a cookie is being used, and accept or reject the cookie. You can also set your browser to refuse all cookies or accept only cookies returned to the originating servers. Users can generally disable the cookie feature on their browser without affecting their ability to use the site, except in some cases where cookies are used as an essential security feature necessary for transaction completion. Cookies, however, are important to the proper functioning of a site and disabling them may degrade your experience and interfere with Web site features and customizations.

Flash Cookies: We also use flash cookies, also known as "local shared objects," on our sites that employ Flash technology. Flash cookies are small files similar to browser cookies and are used to remember the site's settings to personalize the look and feel of the site. Like normal cookies, Flash cookies are represented as small files on your computer. One method of preventing Flash cookies from being placed is to adjust your preferences in the Macromedia Website Privacy Settings Panel at macromedia.com.

Embedded URLs: Oracle also uses a tracking technique that employs embedded URLs to allow use of the site without cookies. Embedded URLs allow limited information to follow you as you navigate the site, but is not associated with personal information and is not used beyond the session.

Embedded Pixels: On the Web site, Oracle may use embedded pixel technologies on selected pages for the purposes of identifying unique user visits to the Oracle Web sites as opposed to aggregate hits. In addition, embedded pixels or other technologies may be used in emails to provide information on when the email was opened to track marketing campaign responsiveness; information collected using these technologies may be associated with the recipient's email address.

Third-Party Cookies: Oracle has engaged one or more third-party service providers to track and analyze usage and volume statistical information from visitors to the Web site. The service provider(s) set cookies on behalf of Oracle. Oracle also uses other third-party cookies to track the performance of Oracle advertisements on their Web sites.

Oracle may re-associate the information provided by the technologies directly above with personal information.

Widgets: Our Web site includes Widgets, which are interactive mini-programs that run on our site to provide specific services from another company (for example, links to bookmarked sites). Personal information, such as your email address, may be collected through the Widget. Cookies may also be set by the Widget to enable it to function properly. Information collected or used by a Widget, including cookie settings and preferences, is governed by the privacy policy of the company that created it.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Use and Sharing of Personal Information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Oracle uses (and, where specified, shares) your personal information for the following purposes:

To engage in transactions. Oracle may use personal information such as name, physical address, telephone number, email address, and company to engage in transactions with you, including contacting you about your order.

To process transactions. Oracle may use financial/credit card and payment information to process your order. Oracle may need to share some of this information with delivery services, credit card clearing houses and other third parties to complete the transaction.

To provide support or other services. Oracle may use your personal information to provide you support or other services you have ordered, as well as product updates, product patches and fixes and other similar communications.

To tailor marketing to your needs and respond to your requests. Oracle may use your personal information to notify you about new product releases and service developments. Oracle also may use your personal information to respond directly to your requests for information, including registrations for newsletters or other specific requests, or pass your contact information to the appropriate Oracle distributor or reseller for further follow-up related to your interests. In addition, if you consent, Oracle may share your contact information with other selected partners that offer complementary products or services. Please review the specific partner's privacy policy regarding any further interactions with them.

To provide online forums and social networks. Some services available on the Web sites permit you to participate in interactive discussions, post comments, opportunities or other content to a bulletin board or exchange, or otherwise engage in networking activities. Some of these services are moderated; all may be accessed for technical reasons. Oracle does not control the content that users post to these forums or social networks. You should carefully consider whether you wish to submit personal information to these forums or social networks and should tailor any content you submit appropriately and in accordance with the relevant terms of use. In addition, you should review any additional terms and conditions that may govern your use of these services, including terms related to use, sharing your personal information and receiving communications; any such terms will be clearly identified on the relevant site.

To post Testimonials. We post testimonials on our web site which may contain personal information. Prior to posting the testimonial, we obtain the customer's consent to post their name along with their testimonial.

To administer product downloads. Oracle may contact you if you download products to confirm certain information about your order (for example, that you did not experience problems in the download process), discuss the downloaded products or provide marketing or sales information about related products and services. Oracle also may use this information to confirm compliance with licensing and other terms of use and may share it with your company.

To select content, improve quality, and facilitate use of the Web Sites. Oracle may use your personal information, including the information gathered as a result of site navigation and electronic protocols and cookies (including third-party cookies), to help create and personalize Web site content, facilitate your use of the Web sites (for example, to facilitate navigation and the login process, avoid duplicate data entry, enhance security, keep track of shopping cart additions and preserve order information between sessions), improve Web site quality, track marketing campaign responsiveness, and evaluate page response rates.

To provide various Oracle communities, such as partners, with relevant product alerts and updates. If you sign up for an Oracle community (for example, Oracle Partner Network, Oracle Technology Network, Oracle.com), Oracle also will provide you information in which you have expressed an interest related to new product releases, alerts, updates, prices, terms, special offers and associated campaigns.

To power joint sales or product promotions. Oracle and its partners may engage in joint sales or product promotions. Such promotions will always reference the partners involved. Both Oracle and the partner(s) will have access to that information, and either Oracle or our partners may provide you the sales or product promotion information. We recommend you review the privacy policies of these partners to address your particular needs and concerns.

To contact a referral/"tell a friend". If you elect to use our referral service to inform a friend about our site, we will ask you for the friend's name and email address. Oracle will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. Oracle uses this personal information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. The friend may contact Oracle through our inquiry form to be removed from the referral program.

To communicate with you about a conference or event. We or our partners may communicate with you about a conference or event hosted or co-sponsored by Oracle or one of our partners. This may include information about the event's content, event logistics, payment, updates, and any additional meetings, special demonstrations or other customer facilitation that we may provide related to an event for which you have registered. Oracle may contact you after the event about the event and related products and services and may share information about your attendance with your company. Oracle also will permit designated partners or conference sponsors to send you up to two communications through the services of a third-party bonded warehouse. Please note that our partners or conference sponsors may directly request your personal information at their conference booths or presentations; providing your information is optional, and you should review their privacy policies to address your particular needs and concerns.

To comply with legal requirements. Oracle may be required to disclose your personal information in order to comply with legally mandated reporting, disclosure or other legal process requirements. Oracle will use reasonable efforts to limit the personal information it provides for these purposes.

Please note that your personal information may be transferred, accessed and stored globally as necessary for the uses stated above in accordance with this policy. While Oracle may share your personal information with agents and contractors in order to perform the functions listed above, including credit card clearing services, order fulfillment, and event, campaign and web site management, we require that they treat your personal information, and limit its use, in accordance with the standards specified in this policy.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Registration, Customization, Preferences, and Opt-Out</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Oracle allows you to establish an online registration profile for marketing communications at Oracle.com. You may use the profile to customize and control your preferences for receiving electronic information, including opting into (or out of) communities, newsletters and general interest areas. You can return to the registration profile at any time to change your elections or modify your profile at https://myprofile.oracle.com/. Please login as usual and follow the prompts to "update my profile."

Opting Out. Oracle.com enables you to opt out of marketing communications. You may opt out of email marketing by modifying your online profile as described above or by using our general unsubscribe automated link that is included in Oracle marketing emails. You can find details on how to automatically unsubscribe from email communications, as well as how to submit requests to opt-out from phone and postal marketing, on our Oracle.com Account Help page. If you have any problems using any of these opt-out mechanisms, please fill out an inquiry form.

Some non-marketing communications are not subject to general opt-out, such as communications related to product download, sales transactions, software updates and other support related information, patches and fixes, quality assurance surveys, conferences or events for which you have registered, and disclosures to comply with legal requirements, as well as communications with partners, including product alerts, updates, marketing and sales materials and other notices related to partner status.

Oracle enables you to opt-out of cookies that are not required to enable core site functionality. You may access or change your cookie preferences at any time by clicking here. If you have any problems using this cookie preference mechanism, please fill out an inquiry form.

Information-Sharing Choices. Oracle only shares personal information with selected companies after providing users the ability to either opt out of or opt into the sharing. There are limitations to opting out of such sharing in the case of (1) joint sale or joint events where the data goes to both Oracle and the other party at the same time; (2) where the customer has requested follow-up which involves Oracle partners; and (3) where third parties are required to accomplish the transaction or perform the service.

Third-Party Permission-Based Lists. On occasion, Oracle may use third-party lists to send communications about Oracle products and services. These lists, which are maintained by third parties, include users eligible under applicable law to receive emails from other companies such as Oracle. When we use such lists, the communications will include mechanisms to opt out of Oracle marketing communications and the third-party lists. If you have trouble opting out, or if you wish to make us aware of any issues related to a third-party mailing, you may contact us directly through our inquiry form.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Access and Profile Updates</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>You have the ability to update your Oracle.com profile and related personal information at any time. To change this information, please login at https://myprofile.oracle.com/ and follow the prompts to "update my profile." If you have questions about your account or are having trouble accessing your account, you can get answers to Frequently Asked Questions (FAQs) and request help with your account. If you have privacy concerns about your personal information, please contact us through our inquiry form. You may also write to us at the following address:

10 Van de Graaff Drive
Burlington, Massachusetts 01803
Attn: Chief Privacy Officer

While the majority of questions and issues related to access can be handled quickly, complex requests may take more research and time. In such cases, issues will be addressed, or you will be contacted regarding the nature of the problem and appropriate next steps, within thirty days.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Advertising</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Oracle uses some third parties to administer a limited set of Oracle advertisements on its Web sites. No personal information is provided to the advertisers as part of this process, but aggregate profile information, such as user community, may be used in the selection of advertising to make sure that it has relevance to the user. On some banner ads, an embedded pixel may be present, and while it does not associate with a cookie or other personal profile information, it may return session connection information that allows advertisers to better determine how many individual users have clicked on the ad banner.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Security</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>The security of your personal information is very important to Oracle. We have in place physical, administrative and technical safeguards designed to protect your personal information from unauthorized access. In addition, Oracle uses standard security protocols and mechanisms to exchange the transmission of sensitive data such as credit card details. When you enter sensitive information such as your credit card number on our site, we encrypt it using secure socket layer (SSL) technology.

In the event that your personal information is acquired, or is reasonably believed to have been acquired, by an unauthorized person and applicable law requires notification, Oracle will notify you of the breach by email, fax, or U.S. mail. Oracle will give you notice promptly, consistent with the reasonable needs of law enforcement and/or Oracle to determine the scope of the breach and to investigate and restore the integrity of the data system.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Compliance Issues</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Oracle has appointed a Chief Privacy Officer. If you believe your personal information has been used in a way that is not consistent with this policy or your specified preferences, or if you have further questions related to this policy, please contact the Chief Privacy Officer by filling out an inquiry form. Written inquiries may be addressed to Chief Privacy Officer, Oracle Corporation, 10 Van de Graaff Drive, Burlington, Massachusetts 01803, United States of America.

Under California Civil Code Section 1798.83 (also known as S.B. 27), if you are a California resident and your business relationship with Oracle is primarily for personal, family, or household purposes, you may request certain data regarding Oracle's disclosure, if any, of personal information to third parties for the third-parties' direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please fill out an inquiry form; you may make such a request up to once per calendar year. If applicable, we will provide you, by email, a list of the categories of personal information disclosed to third parties for their direct marketing purposes during the immediately preceding calendar year, along with the third parties' names and addresses. Please note that not all personal information sharing is covered by S.B. 27's requirements.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Policy Updates</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We may update this policy from time to time. We will post a prominent notice in this section of this policy notifying users when it is updated. If we are going to use your personal information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify you via email, and you will have a choice as to whether or not we use your personal information in this different manner.

We appreciate your comments on Oracle's privacy practices: please contact us through the privacy inquiry form.

Last Updated: May 5, 2010. See the prior version of this policy.

Corporate Headquarters</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Corporate Headquarters</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>500 Oracle Parkway
Redwood Shores, CA
94065, USA
Tel: +1.650.506.7000
Fax: +1.650.506.7200</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
