<POLICY modification_date="" policy_url="http://www.oxforddictionaries.com/words/privacy-policy-and-legal-notice" website_category="Reference" website_index="054" website_url="oxforddictionaries.com">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>Privacy Policy

This privacy policy is specific to this website ("Website") and overrides any other privacy policies appearing elsewhere on Oxford University Press websites.

Oxford University Press ("OUP", "we", "us" or "our") is committed to protecting your privacy online. This privacy policy explains how we will do this. We will review this privacy policy in the light of comments we receive so please check the latest version. If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us by emailing us at oxfordonline@oup.com if you are in the Americas or onlinesubscriptions@oup.com if you are outside the Americas.

By using the Website, you are accepting the practices described in this statement.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>What kind of information do we collect and how do we use it</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>When you visit the Website, OUP may collect information and statistics that contain your identifying information. The information collected may include information relating to your behaviour and navigation on the Website. This information allows us to carry out internal research on our users' interests, demographics and behaviour so that we can better understand, and in turn, provide better information, products and services to you and other customers.

If you subscribe to or ask for further information about the Website, we ask for your name, email address, postal address, and other relevant personal information. Personal information submitted in this way is added to our access control database, hosted by a third party hosting company, and to our customer databases at OUP's and/or our affiliates' premises. This information will be updated if you inform us of any changes.

If you are a subscriber (which may be you as an individual or an institution to which you are affiliated) (including a subscriber on a trial basis), your personal information will be used to enable us to verify that you are a subscriber and to deliver any restricted content on the Website to you.

If you sign up to receive newsletters, we will ask you for your email address and your name and this information will be added to our customer databases.

We may use information in our customer databases to send you information about us, our affiliates, our products and services, and our affiliates' products and services that we think may be of interest to you electronically or otherwise.

We request personal information (such as your name, email address and other contact details) from you when you contact us with subscription management queries, technical problems, to comment on the Website, or when you ask for information about how to use the products and/or services made available on the Website. Personal information submitted by you via the "contact us" page will not be added to our customer databases and we request it simply so that we can respond to you about your query. Statistics regarding the types of queries submitted to us via the "contact us" page may be collated by us in aggregate form so that we can effectively monitor the Website and improve levels of service.

If you have asked for information or subscribed to restricted content on the Website in the past and no longer subscribe to such service and do not wish us to store information about you, please contact us and we will remove your details from our customer databases. We need to store information about current subscribers in order to fulfil our contractual requirements to you and grant you access to restricted content on the Website.

You may notify us either in writing or by telephone, fax or email that you object to being contacted or being contacted in a particular stated way. If you use more than one email address to communicate with us, please notify us of each email account you use.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>When do we share information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

We share your information within OUP. We also share your information with our affiliates, licensors and suppliers, which assist us in making the Website available to you (e.g. our hosting supplier).

If we believe that your use of the Website is unlawful or damaging to others, we reserve the right to disclose the information we have obtained through the Website about you to third parties to the extent that it is reasonably necessary in our opinion to prevent, remedy or take action in relation to such conduct.

We may also disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation; in order to enforce or apply any agreements or licences with you; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of OUP, our employees, affiliates, licensors, suppliers, and/or our customers. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

If any part of our business (including those of our affiliates) is sold or integrated with another business, your details may be disclosed to our advisers and any prospective purchasers and their advisers.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Use of cookies</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>OUP uses "cookies" and other technologies on the Website. The terms and conditions governing OUP's use of "cookies" and such other technologies on the Website are set out in OUP's Cookie Policy.

By using the Website, you are agreeing to be bound by the terms of our Cookie Policy.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Security</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Some of your personal information is stored at a data centre managed by our third party hosting company. The data centre managed by our third party hosting company is specifically designed to be physically secure and to admit authorised personnel only, who are contractually bound to keep all of our data confidential.

Access to our customer databases is only given on a 'need to know basis'.

The information that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area. It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us, our affiliates or for one of our suppliers. However, we have taken the steps outlined above to try to improve the security of your information. By using the Website, you consent to these transfers.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Updating Your Details</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>If any of the information that you have provided to OUP changes e.g. if you change your e-mail address, please let us know the correct details by sending an e-mail to at oxfordonline@oup.com if you are in the Americas or onlinesubscriptions@oup.com if you are outside the Americas.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Changes to our Privacy Policy</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We reserve the right to make changes to this privacy policy. Any changes we may make to this privacy policy will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail.

Governing Law

You agree that this privacy policy shall be exclusively governed in accordance with the laws of and the courts in England and Wales.

Legal Notice



This legal notice is specific to this website ("Website") and overrides any other legal notices appearing elsewhere on Oxford University Press websites. By using the Website, you are agreeing to the practices set out in this statement.

You may access certain parts of the Website without registering or providing OUP with your details.

As the information on the Website may be incomplete, out of date or inaccurate and may contain technical inaccuracies or typographical errors, Oxford University Press ("OUP", "we", "us" or "our") reserve the right to update the Website at our sole discretion. Thus, such information may be changed or updated without notice.

We reserve the right to make changes to this legal notice. Any changes we may make to this legal notice will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, we will also notify you by e-mail. Certain provisions of this legal notice may be superseded by expressly designated legal notices or terms located on particular pages of the Website.

Usernames and Passwords

Where you have registered on the Website and have been provided with a username and password, you agree not to make available your username and/or password to anyone. If there has been a disclosure of your username and/or password, you agree to notify us promptly of such disclosure so that OUP can take appropriate security measures and to provide you with a new username and password.

Subscribers

Under the licence to access restricted content on the Website accepted by a subscriber (which may be you as an individual or an institution to which you are affiliated) you are permitted to:

1.  search, view, retrieve, and display portions of restricted content;
2.  electronically save portions of restricted content; and/or
3.  print out single copies of portions of restricted content

In each case, subject to any specific restrictions which appear on particular pages of the Website. Under the licence accepted by the subscriber, you may not:

1.  remove or alter the copyright notices or other means of identification or disclaimers as they appear on the Website;
2.  systematically make printed or electronic copies of multiple extracts of restricted content for any purpose;
3.  display or distribute any restricted content on any electronic network, including without limitation on the Internet and the World Wide Web (other than the institution's secure network, where the subscriber is an institution);
4.  permit anyone to access or use restricted content (other than other users authorised by the institution, where the subscriber is an institution); and/or
5.  use any content on the Website whether restricted content or otherwise  for any commercial use.

If you sign up to receive newsletters or subscribe to our web feed you may only use the material sent to you for non-commercial use. You may not:

1.  remove or alter the copyright notices or other means of identification or disclaimers as they appear in the material sent to you;
2.  systematically make printed or electronic copies of multiple extracts of the material for any purpose;
3.  display or distribute any part of the material on any electronic network, including without limitation the Internet and the World Wide Web;
4.  permit anyone to access or use the material; and/or
5.  use all or any part of the material for any commercial use.

ClickandBuy customers

If you have purchased a subscription for the Website through ClickandBuy, your subscription contract will be with ClickandBuy and NOT with Oxford University Press, however, your use of the Website will still be subject to the privacy policy on the Website and this legal notice.

Your card will be automatically charged each month until you cancel your subscription.

Intellectual Property Rights

We and/or our licensors are the owners of all intellectual property rights in the Website, and the Website and the materials on the Website are protected by intellectual property laws around the world including copyright and trade mark laws. Subject to the terms of this legal notice and any other licence agreements between you and OUP, all such rights are reserved and no materials may otherwise be copied, modified, published, broadcast or otherwise distributed without our prior written permission. OUP, Oxford and/or any other names of products or services provided by Oxford University Press and referred to on the Website are either trademarks or registered trademarks of Oxford University Press.

Notwithstanding the foregoing and where applicable, copyright in each illustration that appears on the Website is owned by the rights holder(s) named in ‘Picture Details' window for that illustration. All rights are reserved. No illustration from the Website may be copied, modified, published or broadcast or otherwise distributed.

Disclaimer

Oxford University Press makes no warranties or representations of any kind concerning the accuracy or suitability of the information contained on the Website for any purpose. All such information is provided "as is" and with a specific disclaimer of any warranties of merchantability, fitness for purpose, title and/or non-infringement. Oxford University Press makes no warranties or representations of any kind that the services provided by this Website will be uninterrupted, error-free or that the Website or the server that hosts the Website are free from viruses or other forms of harmful computer code.

You are solely responsible for your choice in selecting this Website product.

In no event shall Oxford University Press, its employees or agents be liable for any direct, indirect or consequential damages, loss of opportunity, loss of data, loss of goodwill, loss of anticipated savings or loss of profits resulting from the use of the Website even if OUP has been advised of such loss.

Without prejudice to the foregoing paragraph, OUP's liability arising out of or in connection with your use of the Website and/or this legal notice whether in contract, tort, misrepresentation, under statute or otherwise will not exceed the price you paid for your subscription to access this Website.

Neither party's liability for personal injury or death caused by negligence or for fraud is excluded or limited.

The exclusion and limitation set out in this legal notice only applies to the extent permitted by law and is without prejudice to any express provisions to the contrary in any written licence or subscription agreement which you have with Oxford University Press in respect of the use of any online service provided via the Website.

Links

Links to other websites are provided by OUP in good faith and for information only. OUP disclaims any responsibility for the materials contained in any website linked to the Website.
In addition, a link to a non-OUP website does not mean that OUP endorses or accepts any responsibility for the content, or the use, of such website or the products and/or services offered on such website. It is up to you to take precautions to ensure that whatever you select for your use is free of such items as viruses, worms, trojans and other items of a destructive nature.

Service Access

While we endeavour to ensure that the Website is normally available 24 hours a day, we shall not be liable if for any reason the Website is unavailable at any time or for any period.

Access to the Website may be suspended temporarily and without notice in the case of system failure, maintenance or repair or for reasons beyond our control.

You are prohibited from posting or transmitting to or from the Website any material:

that is threatening, defamatory, obscene, indecent, seditious, offensive, pornographic, abusive, liable to incite racial hatred, discriminatory, menacing, scandalous, inflammatory, blasphemous, in breach of confidence, in breach of privacy or which may cause annoyance or inconvenience;
for which you have not obtained all necessary licences and/or approvals;
which constitutes or encourages conduct that would be considered a criminal offence, give rise to civil liability, or otherwise be contrary to the law of or infringe the rights of any third party, in any country in the world; or
which is technically harmful (including, without limitation, computer viruses, logic bombs, Trojan horses, worms, harmful components, corrupted data or other malicious software or harmful data).

You may not misuse the Website (including, without limitation, by hacking).

Global Nature of Websites

You recognise the global nature of the Website and thus, agree to comply with all applicable local laws in your jurisdiction when using the Website.

Information we publish on the Website may contain references or cross-references to our services and/or products offered that are not announced or available in your country.  Such references do not imply that we intend to announce such services and/or products in your country.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Governing Law</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>You agree that this legal notice shall be exclusively governed in accordance with the laws of and the courts in England and Wales. Notwithstanding the foregoing, nothing in this legal notice will preclude OUP from applying to any court to bring an action for the infringement of its intellectual property rights.

Queries

If you have any concerns about material which appears on the Website, please contact oxfordonline@oup.com if you are in the Americas or onlinesubscriptions@oup.com if you are outside the Americas.

Note on proprietary status

Oxford Dictionaries Pro and Oxford Dictionaries Online include some words which have or are asserted to have proprietary status as trade marks or otherwise. Their inclusion does not imply that they have acquired for legal purposes a non-proprietary or general significance nor any other judgement concerning their legal status. In cases where the editorial staff have some evidence that a word has proprietary status this is indicated in the entry for that word but no judgement concerning the legal status of such words is made or implied thereby.

Thank you for visiting the Website.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
