<POLICY modification_date="September 24, 2009" policy_url="http://www.xmarks.com/about/privacy" website_category="Home" website_index="061" website_url="forum.gsmhosting.com">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>This document outlines what information we collect from our users and how we use that information. Our goal in creating this policy is to be transparent so that you can make informed decisions. We urge you to read it, as by installing our Add-on or visiting our website, you are accepting the practices described here. If you have questions, please visit Customer Support. Capitalized terms that are not defined in this Privacy Policy are defined in our Terms of Service.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>What information does Xmarks receive</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Through your use of Xmarks, we receive the following types of information:

Information you give us: When you create a web account with us, we receive and store information from you, such as your username, password, and email address (your "Registration Information"). We also receive and store any information that you post or disclose on our website, or in any email that you send to us.
Information generated when you visit our website: Each time you visit our website, we receive and store information associated with that visit, such as the date and time of the visit, your computer's IP address, which pages on our site you view, which browser you are using, any cookies associated with our site, etc.
Information generated by the Xmarks Add-on: If you use an Xmarks Add-on, it will contact our servers periodically or in response to certain actions you take in your browser. Each of those contacts generates the same kind of information generated when you visit our website, as described above. Additionally, the Add-on will transmit whatever data is necessary to provide particular features of the Add-on and to monitor their use. For example, to synchronize your bookmarks, the Add-on transmits your bookmarks to our servers. To provide the Smarter Search feature, the Add-on transmits the search query you entered and any search results you receive.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>What about cookies</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We use cookies in a variety of ways to improve your experience using our site (for example by keeping you logged in as you browse our site) and to analyze in aggregate usage of our site. Additionally, our advertising partners may use cookies to analyze your behavior across websites to facilitate the display of ads that are more relevant to you and your interests.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>How does Xmarks use the information it receives</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We use the information we receive from our users to provide our users with various services and otherwise operate our business as follows:

Registration Information: We use your Registration Information (as defined above), to ensure that only authorized people can access your account. The Xmarks Add-on uses your Registration Information to log you in automatically to synchronize your bookmarks and passwords. We also use your Registration Information to confirm your identity when you log in manually to our website. We may use your Registration Information to contact you to provide technical support, or, unless you opt out, to contact you regarding Xmarks services or products.
Synchronized Passwords: If you use the Xmarks Add-on to synchronize your passwords, we keep an encrypted copy of your passwords on our servers. Because your passwords are encrypted with a PIN that you choose and we never see, we cannot view your passwords. We will never decrypt your passwords other than to provide synchronization services on a computer you are using, and we keep your encrypted passwords on our servers only to allow you to synchronize those passwords.
Synchronized Bookmarks: If you use the Xmarks Add-on to synchronize your bookmarks, we keep a copy of your bookmarks on our servers. We use this data to provide you with backup and synchronization services. Unless you opt out, we anonymize, aggregate, and analyze the bookmarks of our users in order to provide a range of Search and Discovery services like Smarter Search, Suggested Tags, and Top Sites.
Usage Data: When you use our website or various features in the Xmarks Add-on, we collect usage data which we analyze in aggregate to learn how our site and features are being used so we can tune and improve them. On occasion, we may examine usage data from an individual user as required to solve technical problems.
Other Data: We use other data that the Xmarks Add-on sends us to provide specific in-browser features. For example, in Firefox when you open the bookmark dialog, we use the web address that the Add-on sends to provide you with a list of Suggested Tags.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Does Xmarks share the information it receives</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>As a normal part of our business, we share information only in the ways described below:

Registration Information: We will never lease, rent, or sell your email address. If you contribute User Content (as described in the Terms of Service) to a public area of our website, we may share your chosen username as the author of that content.
Synchronized Passwords: We will never share your synchronized passwords.
Synchronized Bookmarks: We may share information about our users' bookmarks in anonymous, aggregate form only with our users, subsidiaries, and affiliates. In doing so, we protect your privacy in two ways. First, we share only anonymous, aggregate data. For example, we may share a list of the most commonly bookmarked pages in the Wikipedia, or the sites most frequently bookmarked within a "News" folder. Such data is never released in a form that can be associated with individual users. Second, we only share data about bookmarks that are held by a substantial number of users. Finally, you may explicitly opt to share all or portions of your bookmarks with other users; you can do so by visiting my.xmarks.com and selecting "Share."
Usage data: We may share aggregate usage data with affiliates, business partners, advertisers, etc.
Additionally, the following describe extraordinary circumstances in which we may also share information:

Business Transfers: As we continue to develop our business, we might sell part or all of our business or buy other businesses. In such transactions, user information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy (unless, of course, the user consents otherwise). In the event that Xmarks, Inc. or substantially all of its assets is involved in an acquisition or merger, user information will be one of the transferred assets.
Protection of Xmarks and Others: We may release registration and other information when we believe such release is appropriate to comply with the law or regulation or upon the request of law enforcement or government officials, enforce or apply our Terms of Service and other agreements, or protect the rights, property, or safety of Xmarks, our users, or others. However, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from users for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Policy.
Third-Party Service Providers: We may employ or allow other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf, such as operating user support forums or providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>What choices do I have</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>If you don't want us to receive the data associated with a feature in the Xmarks Add-on, you may disable that feature from the Settings dialog within the Add-on or uninstall the Add-on entirely. For example, if you do not want us to receive queries that you conduct, disable our Search and Discovery features.
If you want to synchronize your bookmarks but don't want us to aggregate your bookmark data, you may opt out of aggregation by disabling it in your web account.
If you do not want to receive email from us about product upgrades and other offers, you may opt out of such email contact by disabling it in your web account.
If you don't want us to receive data generated by visiting our website, don't visit our website.
You may delete your web account, which will delete from our servers any synchronized bookmarks and passwords stored there, as well as your Registration Information.
You may use features in your browser to disable cookies or third-party cookies.
Firefox users who wish only to synchronize their bookmarks and passwords may download and install Xmarks BYOS Edition. This Add-on provides synchronization features similar to the standard edition, but requires that you supply your own server. By doing so, you minimize communication with us.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>What information can I access</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>After you have created a web account, you may log in to view and change information about your account. Any new information you provide replaces the old information immediately.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>How secure is information about me</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Xmarks takes the security of your information seriously and we've expended significant effort implementing industry best practices to help secure your data. We ask that you work with us to ensure that no one obtains unauthorized access to any user information.

Please remember that you play a valuable part in security. Your password to access our site, which you select at registration, should never be shared with anyone and should be changed frequently.

If you choose to synchronize your passwords using the Service, you must provide a PIN which is used to encrypt your passwords on our server. By design, this PIN never leaves your computer and you must enter it on each computer you wish to synchronize. You should treat your PIN with utmost care, never sharing it with anyone.

After you have finished using our site, you should log off and exit your browser so no unauthorized persons can use our site with your name and account information.

If you have installed the Xmarks Add-on on your computer, you should uninstall it before you sell or otherwise transfer your computer to another person.

Regardless of the precautions taken by you or by us, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet. We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you transmit such information at your own risk.

In the event that personal information is compromised as a result of a breach of security, we will promptly notify those persons whose personal information has been compromised, in accordance with the notification procedures set forth in this Privacy Policy, or as otherwise required by applicable law.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Terms of Service, Notices, and Revisions</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>If you choose to visit Xmarks.com or use the Xmarks Add-ons, your visit or use and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Policy and our Terms of Service. Please read this policy carefully and feel free to contact Customer Support if you have any questions or comments regarding its contents. We may change this policy at any time to correct technical or typographical errors, to increase your rights and protections or to comply with laws. If we change this policy in a way that reduces your rights or protections or adds new types of disclosures, we will provide notification of such changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
