<POLICY modification_date="" policy_url="http://www.integrativenutrition.com/privacy" website_category="Health" website_index="079" website_url="integrativenutrition.com">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>Integrative Nutrition Inc. ("IIN") Terms of Use, Privacy Policy, and Intellectual Property</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>GENERAL CONDITIONS</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>a. Acceptance of Terms. By accessing IIN's family of websites, including www.integrativenutrition.com and other IIN owned websites, (collectively, "the Site"), you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions described herein ("Terms of Use"). Except as specifically stated otherwise, these Terms of Use set forth the entire understanding relating to this subject matter. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not use the Site.

b. Severability. If any provision of the Terms of Use is held to be invalid or unenforceable by any law, rule, order, or regulation of any government or by the final determination of any state or federal court, all remaining provisions hereof will remain in full force and effect.

c. Choice of Law. By accessing the Site you agree that the statutes, laws, and regulations of the United States and the State of New York, USA, without regard to conflicts of law principles, will apply to all matters relating to use of the Site, and you agree that any litigation shall be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the State or Federal Courts in New York County, New York.

d. Foreign Access. The Site is controlled and operated in whole or in part by IIN in the United States. IIN makes no representation that the content in the Site is appropriate or available for use in other locations, and access to it from territories where the content may be illegal is prohibited.

e. Termination of Access. IIN reserves the right in its sole discretion to refuse or terminate access to the Site by you at any time.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>PRIVACY POLICY</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>a. Anonymous Data Collection and Use. To maintain the Site's high quality, IIN may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer the Site by identifying which areas of the Site are most heavily used and to display content according to your preferences. Your IP address is the number assigned to computers connected to the Internet. This is essentially "traffic data" which cannot personally identify you, but is helpful to IIN for marketing purposes and for improving our services. Traffic data collection does not follow a user's activities on any other websites in any way. Anonymous traffic data may also be shared with business partners and advertisers on an aggregate basis.

b. Voluntary Personal Data Submission. IIN may ask for personal data, namely when you: request a catalog or magazine, order books, take our quiz, subscribe to our newsletters, or request customer service. Prospective students wishing for detailed information about our programs are required to provide their contact information (such as name, address and email address). This information is used to contact the user about the program for which they have expressed interest. We may ask for demographic information such as gender and age, to personalize our correspondence, or to distinguish adults from minors. If you choose not to provide personally identifiable data and information, you may still use the Site, but will not be able to use the services that require such information.

c. Use of "Cookies." IIN may use the standard "cookies" feature of major web browsers. Cookies are small pieces of data stored on your computer that contains information about the user. IIN does not set any personally identifiable information in cookies, nor does IIN employ any data capture mechanisms on our website other than cookies. Cookies help us learn which areas of our Site are useful and which areas need improvement. You may choose to disable cookies through your web browser's settings. However, disabling this function may diminish your experience on the Site and some features may not work as intended. Cookie information is only used when communicating with users as per their indicated preferences and as needed for service-related communications. Third party content, such as advertisements, displayed on our site may also contain their own cookies; IIN has no access to or control over any information collected by third parties through the Site.

d. Sharing Personal Data. IIN may share personal data and information about our visitors with reliable select business partners, such as advertisers and other third parties.IIN will not otherwise share your personal data and information without your consent, except as necessary when the law requires it or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary, particularly when disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to others or interfering with IIN's rights or property.

e. Contacting You. IIN may use your contact information to inform you of changes to the Site, or, if requested, to send you additional information about IIN.  IIN has a no spam policy and provides you with the ability to opt-out of our communications by selecting the unsubscribe link at the footer of all e-mails. IIN will not sell, rent or share your email address, and you may unsubscribe at any time through the unsubscribe link at the footer of all e-mail communication.

f. Assignment of Rights. In the event of an assignment, sale, joint venture, or other transfer of some or all of IIN's assets, you agree IIN can assign, sell, license or transfer any information that you have provided to us. Please note, however, that the purchasing party cannot use the personal data and information submitted to us under this Privacy Policy in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this Privacy Policy without your prior consent.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Any unauthorized use of any material contained on this Site may violate copyright laws, trademark laws, the laws of privacy and publicity, and communications regulations and statutes. IIN monitors use of its copyrighted material on the Internet and will seek legal action against any infringing parties.

a. Copyrights

All content found on IIN's site, except as noted otherwise, is exclusively and solely owned and copyrighted by IIN. No such content may be copied, reproduced, distributed, republished, downloaded, displayed, posted or transmitted in any form or by any means including, but not limited to, electronic, mechanical, photocopying, recording or otherwise, without IIN's prior written consent. You may not "mirror" any content contained on this Site without express written consent from IIN.

b. Trademarks

The following trademarks and logos are the property of IIN (collectively, "IIN's Marks"):

Name Trademarks: Integrative Nutrition®, Institute for Integrative Nutrition®, and IIN™

Logo Trademarks: the IIN Spiral:iin swirl® and the IIN Logo: iin logo

Slogan Trademarks: "Are you IIN?"™, "Could One Conversation Change Your Life?"™, and "Future of Nutrition"™

This list of IIN's Marks is current as of February 2012 and may be expanded in the future. The absence of a trademark or logo from this list does not constitute a waiver of IIN's trademark or other intellectual property rights concerning that mark or logo.

When permitted to use IIN's Marks in print or online, you must either include the appropriate ™ or ® symbol with each use, or use the appropriate trademark attribution notice. An appropriate example of notice would be: "Integrative Nutrition® and Institute for Integrative Nutrition® are registered trademarks of Integrative Nutrition Inc."

IIN's Site may also display trademarks, logos, and/or service marks of other third parties. Users are not permitted to use any of these third party trademarks, logos and/or service marks without prior written consent from the respective rights holder.

c. Digital Millennium Copyright Act (DMCA) Notice

IIN respects the rights of other copyright holders. If you believe your copyright is being infringed, IIN will respond to notices of alleged infringement submitted in accordance with 17 USC §512(c)(3).

Notice may be sent by email to: intellectualproperty@integrativenutrition.com or by physical mail at:

Integrative Nutrition
Attn: Legal Dept. - DMCA Takedown
3 E 28th Street
New York, NY 10016
intellectualproperty@integrativenutrition.com
(877) 730-5444</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>SECURITY</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>IIN takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, all information is protected both online and off-line. But, due to the nature of the Internet, IIN cannot completely ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted to us or through our Services. Submitting information is done at your own risk. IIN's Site has security measures in place to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information that IIN obtains from you, but IIN makes no assurances about our ability to prevent any such loss, misuse, to you or to any third party arising out of any such loss, misuse, or alteration.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>THIRD PARTY LINKS</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>The Site may contain links to other websites, not controlled by IIN. If you choose to visit other websites, IIN is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of those other websites, and it is your responsibility to review the terms and privacy policies of those websites to confirm that you understand and agree with their policies.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>DISCLAIMER</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>a. No Warranties. Information on the Site  is provided "as is" without warranty of any kind, either express or implied, including, but not limited to, the implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, and non-infringement.

b. No Liability. In no event will IIN be liable for damages of any kind, including without limitation any special, indirect, incidental, or consequential damages, even if IIN has been advised of the possibility of such damages.

c. Accuracy. Although every effort is made to ensure the accuracy of published information on IIN's web pages, the Site may inadvertently contain technical inaccuracies or typographical errors. This information may be changed or updated without notice. IIN assumes no responsibility for errors or omissions on the Site or in documents referenced by or linked to the Site.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>MODIFICATIONS</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>IIN reserves the right to change the Site, these Terms of Use, or the policies and conditions that govern the use of the Site at any time. Please review this page periodically for any updates or changes. These Terms apply to all visits to the Site, both now and in the future. Your continued access of the Site shall be deemed your notification and acceptance of these changes.

Be assured that even if the Terms change in the future, IIN will not use any personal information you have submitted to us under these Terms in a manner that is materially inconsistent with these Terms without your prior consent.

Questions regarding these Terms of Use should be directed to legal@integrativenutrition.com</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
