<POLICY modification_date="July 19, 2013" policy_url="http://www.usairways.com/en-US/privacy.html" website_category="Recreation" website_index="048" website_url="usairways.com">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>US Airways Privacy Policy
Date effective: July 19, 2013</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>We respect your privacy</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Thank you for your interest in US Airways. Your privacy is important to us. As part of our corporate commitment to respect your privacy, this Privacy Policy explains what information we collect from or about you and your devices, how we use and disclose it, and the choices you have about that.

This Privacy Policy applies to the usairways.com website, US Airways mobile website, US Airways mobile application (the 'US Airways App') and all related sites, applications, services and tools where this policy is referenced, regardless of how you access or use them, including from mobile devices (collectively, 'Sites and Services'). Where our information practices apply uniquely to your interactions via the US Airways App, or with our websites, we have tried to so indicate in this Privacy Policy.
You may direct any questions about this Privacy Policy, or the underlying practices to privacy@usairways.com.
This Privacy Policy is not a contract and does not create any legal rights or obligations. Rather, this Privacy Policy communicates US Airways' intended business practices with respect to information collected from and about visitors to (and users of) the Sites and Services in the course of offering, promoting, and selling our services to the public. This Privacy Policy and the underlying information practices are subject to change at any time. We will notify users of any substantial changes by updating the Privacy Policy here with an announcement on our home page when such changes are made. This page will be updated to reflect any such changes so you should review this page regularly for the most recent version of our Privacy Policy.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Types of information we collect and how we collect it</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>In order to sell and promote commercial air travel and other products and services, we collect and maintain certain information about you and your device(s) as you interact with our Sites and Services. We collect some information from you directly (i.e., when you book a flight or create a frequent flier profile), and other information by automated means from your computer, smartphone, or other device you use to access our websites or mobile applications.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Information you directly provide to us</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We actively collect the following information which you are solicited to provide in the course of purchasing flights, making or changing reservations, registering for or utilizing a Dividend Miles membership, participating in promotions or sweepstakes, and otherwise interacting with our Sites and Services:
Name, address, telephone numbers
Email addresses
Cell phone, fax and pager numbers
Date of Birth
Gender
Credit/debit card number(s), associated billing address, expiration date(s) and security code(s)
Passport number, nationality and country of residence
Known Traveler number
Redress number
Dividend Miles account number and flight information
Travel-related details such as travel company, travel companion(s), emergency contact(s), seating preferences, and special dietary requests or medical needs
Information from the use of products and services, such as online check-in, ancillary purchases, flight status notifications, and self-service devices
Information provided via participation in surveys, focus groups, contests, sweepstakes and other promotional or marketing efforts
Corporate contract, employer and/or other corporate affiliation (for example, employer name, title, address and contact information)</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Information we collect about your computer/other devices</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>In the course of offering the Sites and Services, we may use cookies or other similar technologies that are necessary to your access and use of the Sites and Services, to assess performance, to enhance functionality and to deliver content, including advertisements, tailored to your interests on our site or third party sites, as described below. You can learn more about cookies, web beacons such as pixel tags and Clear GIFs, or other tracking technologies by visiting the online resource All About Cookies.
allaboutcookies.org
Operationally necessary
We use session cookies, which are temporary and exist while a visitor is reading and navigating our websites, then are normally deleted when you close your browser. None of these cookies collect or store personally identifying information such as contact information or the credit card number associated with your profile or purchase. Instead, these technologies allow access to the Sites and Services, prevent fraudulent activity and improve security, or allow you to book flights or otherwise interact with our Sites and Services.
Functionality-related
We use cookies or other tracking technologies to allow us to offer you enhanced functionality when accessing or using our Sites and Services, which may include recognizing and identifying you or your device when you sign in, and keeping track of your preferences or settings such as language, interests or past transactions so that we may enhance your experience with our Sites and Services.
Performance-related
We use cookies that collect information about how you use the Sites and Services, such as the type of device, the operating system, the location, browser types, internet service providers (ISPs), pages visited, frequency of visits, and the number of clicks, and information about your interactions with our Sites and Services. These technologies allow us to measure whether a certain page was visited, an email was opened, or if ad banners on our websites and other sites were effective, for example and generally help us to understand how visitors use our Sites and Services, and allow us to improve our Sites and Services.
Advertising or targeting-related
We use first-party or third-party cookies and web beacons or similar tracking technologies to deliver content, including advertisements relevant to your interests on our websites or third-party sites. The Advertising or Targeting-Related tracking technologies allow US Airways and select partners (described in more detail in 'Your choices: Cookie management' below) to automatically receive certain types of information about your device or your interactions with our Sites and Services. If you are a Dividend Miles member, we may link this device or behavioral information with your member profile or other information about you which you provide, such as in the course of creating a profile or making a reservation or purchasing services for the purpose of serving advertisements targeted to your interests or profile at usairways.com and elsewhere on the internet.
If you wish to disable, block, or reject cookies or other tracking technologies, please see the 'Cookie management: Your choices' section below, though this may affect the quality of service we can provide you.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Dividend Miles members</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We offer our customers a frequent flier program called Dividend Miles, which offers travel rewards (i.e., mileage credit used for redeeming travel on US Airways or other airline partner travel), convenience, access to services, and special offers for members. In addition to eligibility for these program benefits, customers who create a Dividend Miles account profile can personalize and improve their online or mobile experiences by receiving access to specialized areas of the Sites and Services, including the Dividend Miles and Dividend Miles 'Book award travel' areas.

We also sell mileage credits to our partners that participate in the Dividend Miles program such as credit card companies, hotels, car rental agencies, retailers and dining rewards programs. We share with these partners certain information you have provided to us to the extent needed to administer and deliver the benefits of the Dividend Miles program and its related services such as debiting or crediting your mileage balance when you use or earn miles. When you enroll in the Dividend Miles program, you may also elect to receive information and promotional materials from these partners. For information about the collection, use, sharing, and security practices of these partners, please consult the program terms and conditions and the privacy statements and disclosures published and distributed by these partners. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully to understand how we profile and tailor advertisements to the interests of our Dividend Miles members and offer you the opportunity to opt out of these advertisements and information sharing with our partners, as noted below.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>How your information will be used</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We use the information you actively provide us about yourself, such as in creating or editing a profile or making a reservation, to complete your purchases and other requests, and to process, confirm, update and fulfill the travel and other products or services you request from us. In addition, we may use this information for the following:
To register and service your Dividend Miles account;
To administer and deliver the benefits of the various Dividend Miles programs;
To enhance or customize the products and services we, or other third parties as described below, provide to you (for example, at the explicit request of a Dividend Miles member, storing payment information to make subsequent purchases more convenient);
For internal operations such as information systems management, accounting, billing and audits,;
To contact you to respond to your questions or requests, to resolve issues, and/or to provide you technical support; and
To provide scheduled email newsletters, promotional or special offers such as sweepstakes and contests, and occasional mailings that we believe may be of interest to you.
We may use the information automatically collected from your computer or other devices for the following uses:
To improve our products and services;
To customize and enhance the user experience of our Sites and Services;
To administer, upgrade, and protect our Sites and Services, email servers, and other computer systems;
To analyze trends, track user movement and habits, and gather statistical information for aggregate use; and
To customize and serve advertising and other marketing communications that may be visible to you on our Sites and Services or elsewhere on the internet.
Please note that we may share information that we collect from and about you and your devices with our Dividend Miles partners, service providers and other third parties, as described in the 'Who we share your information with' section below.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Who we share your information with</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Government Entities
We may disclose information about you or your devices, including data identifying you, your travel plans, history or status when compelled or requested to do so by U.S. or foreign law enforcement or government authorities, pursuant to a court order, subpoena, or other legal or regulatory requirements, or when we believe in good faith that it is in the interests of aviation security or that disclosure is otherwise necessary or advisable.
Affiliates
We may share your personal information with our parent company, any subsidiaries, or other companies or entities under common control with us, in which case we will require such parties to honor this Privacy Policy with respect to such shared information.
Business transitions
In the event we undergo a business transition involving another company, such as a merger, corporate reorganization, acquisition, the sale of all or a portion of our assets, or in the event of bankruptcy, information that we have collected from or about you or your devices may be disclosed to such other company as part of the due diligence or business integration process and may be transferred to such company as one of the transferred assets.
Third party marketing partners who may receive email address or other contact information
If you are a Dividend Miles member, we may share your email address or name and postal address with program partners and related service providers in order to offer you products or services of interest through promotional emails or in some cases, postal mailings. These partners may receive other information about you as a Dividend Miles member, such as how many miles you have or other non-identifying information permitting them to match you with offers or promotions or services which are expected to be of interest to you. We contractually obligate these partners to limit their use of your information to sending you these marketing communications, and to honor your marketing preferences if you choose not to receive future marketing messages. Unless you opt out as set forth below, by submitting your information when creating a Dividend Miles account, or by other actions you take with us either offline or on our Sites and Services, you give your consent to receive advertising and promotional communications from us and our marketing partners, and for us to share your personal information with our Dividend Miles partners and/or related service providers. At any time, if you would rather us not share your information with our Dividend Miles partners, you may opt out of such sharing as described in the 'Your choices: Marketing preferences' section below.
Third parties using cookies and pixels to target advertisements
As noted above in the 'Information we collect from/or about the computer or other devices' section, we allow third parties to place and read cookies and pixels on our domains and, if you have enabled this, on your computer or device so that they can receive certain information about you or your device, though not your contact or payment details. For example, a contract partner may receive non-identifying information such as flight details, gender, and whether you are a Dividend Miles member, so that your printed boarding pass will include advertisements relevant to your destination. We also contract with parties identified below to aggregate information about users of our Sites and Services for purposes of creating targeted advertising packages and campaigns on usairways.com domains or other third party sites or networks, so that for example a relevant US Airways advertisement is displayed to you elsewhere on the internet.

We will not knowingly cause or permit personal details such as your contact information or payment information to be provided to these third party interest-based advertising partners.

To learn more about our individual interest-based advertising partners, and how to opt out of the placement or reading of these tracking technologies, please see the section 'Your choices: Cookie management' below.
Third party service providers
We also may share the information you provide about yourself, such as in creating a profile or making a reservation, with companies who perform services on our behalf, including, but not limited to, payment processing, marketing assistance, email delivery, hosting services, customer service, and data analysis. We contractually obligate these third party service providers to protect the confidentiality of the information disclosed to them and they are not permitted to use your information for any purpose other than to provide services to US Airways. In addition, when you purchase services or products through us that are to be provided by another party, such as a travel segment on another airline, hotel accommodations, travel insurance, or a rental car, we share your information with the third party service provider so that they can provide the services or products you requested. We may also receive information about you from such third party service providers related to these transactions.
Additional sharing
We reserve the right to use any information we collect from or about you or your computer and/or other device(s) in order to protect or enforce our rights, or the rights of our affiliates, customers and marketing partners. Furthermore, we reserve the right to provide non-personally identifiable information in aggregated form to any third party for any purpose.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Updating your information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>If you are a customer and need to update your information provided in connection with a reservation and other travel-related services, please contact Customer Service/Reservations by calling 800-428-4322. If you are a Dividend Miles member, you may access and update your user profile, preferences and the information you have provided us at any time by logging into your Dividend Miles account on usairways.com/myaccount or by calling 800-428-4322.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Your choices: Marketing preferences</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Dividend Miles members can opt out of receiving promotional communications by email or postal mail from us or our marketing partners, or to prevent us from sharing your personal information with any marketing partners in the future, as follows:
You may opt out of future email marketing communications received from us or our marketing partners by following the unsubscribe steps described in each such email.
You may opt out of promotional postal mailings from US Airways or our marketing partners by calling 800-428-4322.
You may opt out by logging into your Dividend Miles account at usairways.com/myaccount or by calling 800-428-4322/TTY 800-245-2966 and please note that once we receive your request, it make take up to 10 days for such opt out to become effective.
If we have shared your contact information with any such third parties prior to its receipt of your request, we may not have the ability to prevent such third parties from continuing to use and disclose your contact information, including for the purpose of sending marketing communications to you, and you may need to contact such third parties directly to prevent their further use and disclosure of your contact information.
Also note that if you opt out of our marketing communications, we may still email or communicate with you from time to time if we need to provide you with information or request information from you with respect to a transaction initiated by you, or for other service or account-related announcements, such as flight information updates and travel advisories.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Your choices: Cookie management</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>As noted, we place and read cookies, web beacons, and other tracking technologies throughout our Sites and Services to tailor the content or offers that we present to you online and in emails. Web beacons usually work in conjunction with cookies. If you do not want your cookie information to be associated with your visits to these Sites and Services, then you may set your browser to disable, block, or reject cookies. Generally, you can find directions to manage and turn off cookies in the Privacy and Security settings in the Help function of your browser. If you do disable, block, or reject cookies, then we will still detect an anonymous visit, but the notices that the cookies generate cannot be associated with your particular preferences.

If you disable, block, or reject cookies, the performance of the Sites and Services or our ability to provide you our services may be affected. Please note that cookies are required to purchase a reservation online and to access your Dividend Miles user profile. If you prefer to disable, block, or reject cookies, then please contact US Airways Reservations at 800-428-4322/TTY 800-245-2966 to make your reservation.

To learn more about and opt out of the different cookies that we use, see the links below.
Learn about the NAI opt-out tool on networkadvertising.org
See 'Your privacy choices' on adobe.com
Set ad settings on google.com
Learn more about Sojern, our boarding pass advertiser</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Children's privacy</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We do not knowingly solicit, collect or retain any personal information online from children under the age of 13 without parental or guardian consent other than when necessary to provide air travel and related services and/or to comply with any applicable law. Children under the age of 13 should not use our Sites and Services or provide any personal information. If you believe your child has provided personal information to us without your consent, you may log in and edit your child's Dividend Miles account at usairways.com/myaccount, by calling 800-428-4322 or contact us at privacy@usairways.com, and we will remove the information from our records and unsubscribe the child from any promotional or other marketing communications.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Links to other sites and services</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Our Sites and Services may, from time to time, provide links to sites operated by third parties. These sites are governed by different privacy policies, or may not have privacy policies. If you connect to a different site from our Sites and Services you should review the privacy policy of that site, which will govern any collection of information on that site. If you have any questions about how these other sites use your information, you should contact them directly. Please understand we have no control over those sites' privacy policies or their use of personal information that you may disclose to them and as such, US Airways cannot be held responsible with respect to such disclosure.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Security</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>The security of the information we collect from and about you and your device(s) is very important to us. We protect this information by maintaining administrative, physical and technical safeguards that are consistent with industry practice and that we believe are reasonably appropriate to protect your information. We regularly review these safeguards to reduce the risks of unauthorized access, disclosure, and improper use of personal or payment details collected from you. We also require the companies with whom we share information about you or your device(s) to maintain the information securely. Although we take reasonable steps to protect and to prevent unauthorized access to such information, we cannot be responsible for the acts of those who gain unauthorized access, and we make no warranty, express, implied, or otherwise, that we can prevent unauthorized access to any of the information that we collect from or about you or your computer or other device(s).</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>US Airways app - privacy practices</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We offer you the ability to connect with the usairways.com website, or use our applications, services and tools using a mobile device, either through the US Airways App or via a mobile optimized website. When you use the US Airways App, your device may be redirected to one or more of our webpages as we execute the various instructions (i.e., to make or change a reservation, to check-in, to check flight status, to create or modify your Dividend Miles profile, or otherwise to transmit data to or from the backend servers through which we deliver our services). The terms and provisions of this Privacy Policy apply to all such access and use of our services, whether within the mobile application itself or by linking out to our web pages, and this Privacy Policy will be referenced by the US Airways App or mobile optimized website.

In addition to the information about yourself which you actively provide to us within the US Airways App or the linked-to webpages, the US Airways App may also collect additional data elements in order to offer you additional services.

First, the US Airways App may access the unique identifier on your mobile device though we will not store this information. Instead, we will create and store a different unique identifier for your device.

Second, we may access and use your device's location information in connection with the 'find airports near me' feature. We only access and use location information if you have expressly allowed this both in your device's settings and if you specifically allow this at the time you use this feature. You may change this location election at any time by disabling the location tracking features in your device's settings. We do not store your mobile device's location information.

Third, you may elect to allow the US Airways App to store your Dividend Miles number, itinerary, user name and password locally on your device to allow the app to automatically log you in to your Dividend Miles account, or to permit you to access the information when you are not connected to the internet.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Policy updates and future changes</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>This Privacy Policy is current as the effective date stated at the top of this page. As noted above, this Privacy Policy is subject to change from time to time. Any changes will apply to all information collected by us, including previously collected information, and your continued use constitutes your consent to those changes. This page will be updated to reflect any such changes.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Contact us</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please email privacy@usairways.com.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
