<POLICY modification_date="March 01, 2013" policy_url="http://agb.traviangames.com/privacy-en.pdf" website_category="Games" website_index="038" website_url="travian.com">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>Introduction
This document is the Privacy Policy of Travian Games GmbH, Wilhelm-
Wagenfeld-Straße 22, 80807 Munich, Germany (hereafter referred to as
“TRAVIAN GAMES”). It applies to all websites, mobile apps and games
operated by Travian Games GmbH (hereafter referred to as “TRAVIAN
GAMES”).
In the event that a link contained on a website operated by TRAVIAN
GAMES redirects you to another website that is not operated by TRAVIAN
GAMES, or if you access the services of a third party (e.g. when making a
payment), please be aware that this Privacy Policy will not apply to such
third party website.
TRAVIAN GAMES collects, processes and stores any data that you willingly
submit to TRAVIAN GAMES (e.g. in standard forms or otherwise on the
websites and games operated by TRAVIAN GAMES) by electronic or other
means of communication, or which has been transferred during the
interaction between you and the websites and games of TRAVIAN GAMES,
in accordance with the following sections and in compliance with prevailing
regulations.
This includes data you provide to other users when communicating with
them on websites and via games operated by TRAVIAN GAMES.
In more detail:
Contents
1.
Visiting TRAVIAN GAMES websites
..................................................................................
2
2.
Using TRAVIAN GAMES games
..........................................................................................
2
a)
Registration ............................................................................ 2
b)
Using the games ..................................................................... 3
c)
Communication channels ......................................................... 3
d)
Investigating manipulations of game operations ......................... 4
e)
Internal research ..................................................................... 4
f)
Payment processing ................................................................. 4
3.
Transfer of your data to third parties
..............................................................................
5
4.
Technical features
...................................................................................................................
6
a)
Cookies .................................................................................. 6
b)
Web beacons .......................................................................... 6
c)
Social plug-ins ........................................................................ 6
d)
Google Analytics ..................................................................... 7
e)
Kontagent ............................................................................. 7
f)
Adeven ................................................................................... 8
5.
Revocation of consent
............................................................................................................
8
6.
Amendments to or deletion of personal data
................................................................
8
7.
Information on personal data
.............................................................................................
9
8.
Final provisions
.........................................................................................................................
9</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Visiting TRAVIAN GAMES websites</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>When you visit a website operated by TRAVIAN GAMES, your browser
automatically forwards the IP address, browser version, screen resolution
and operating system of the device you used to access the site. Your
browser will also provide the date, time and duration of the visit to the
website and the various sites you accessed during a visit. TRAVIAN
GAMES uses this information to optimize its websites and games. In
addition, TRAVIAN GAMES uses the analysis tool Google Analytics on its
websites. Please read the comments under 4. d) for more details on the
use of Google Analytics.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Using TRAVIAN GAMES games</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>a) Registration
When you register for a game operated by TRAVIAN GAMES you will be
required to enter your email address and to select a username and
password. This data will be permanently stored by TRAVIAN GAMES when
you validate the activation link sent to the email address you supplied
when you registered. If you do not validate the link, this data will be
deleted after two weeks. Please do not use your real name, the name of
another person or that of a protected registered trademark as a
username. In addition, TRAVIAN GAMES will assign a country to you
based on the IP address of the device which has been entered. This
information will be saved to enable us to offer you an appropriate
selection of payment methods.
If you click on an advertising link on any TRAVIAN GAMES website and are
then forwarded to a website operated by TRAVIAN GAMES, a cookie will
be set on your computer that contains information on which advertising
link you clicked, for which advertiser, for which game, at what time and in
which country. TRAVIAN GAMES will also assign a country to you based on
the IP address of your device. TRAVIAN GAMES will assess this nonpersonal
data to optimize its advertising campaigns and for accounting
purposes regarding its advertisers. The cookie will be deleted once the
activation link has been validated.
TRAVIAN GAMES is offering a service for an increasing number of games
that allows you to activate once only for a game and then use this game
account to move easily around multiple game worlds within this game.
The basis of this service is that the data you supply when you register for
a game will be stored in a central location by the relevant game
b) Using the games
TRAVIAN GAMES stores and processes your personal data to implement
the game user contract that has been agreed and the use options
associated with such contract (e.g. use of the games, utilization of
support, etc.). TRAVIAN GAMES also uses the analysis tools Google
Analytics and Kontagent for its games. Please read the comments under
4. d) and e) for more details on the use of Google Analytics and
Kontagent. The same applies if you access a TRAVIAN GAMES game using
one of the mobile apps operated by TRAVIAN GAMES.
c) Communication channels
The games and websites operated by TRAVIAN GAMES offer various
opportunities to communicate with TRAVIAN GAMES or other players.
TRAVIAN GAMES automatically uses filtering systems that prohibit any
communications that violate § 9 of the Travian Game GmbH General
Terms and Conditions. In particular, TRAVIAN GAMES automatically uses
filtering systems to block any mass mailings and messages that are of an
offensive, obscene or racist nature, that glorify violence or any other
objectionable statements or messages that advertise products or services.
Moreover, TRAVIAN GAMES records the use of the communication
channels for a short period to analyze and fix any technical errors, to
guarantee system security and integrity, to combat abusive and/or
unauthorized use and to generate user statistics on a non-personal basis.
The reports that are generated contain the date and time of the message,
the sender and recipient, the message text and the volume of data sent.
No employees or agents of TRAVIAN GAMES will read your messages
without your consent. Should TRAVIAN GAMES suspect any abusive
and/or unauthorized use of the available communication channels (e.g.
when a recipient reports a message), TRAVIAN GAMES reserves the right
to investigate the relevant game account and the messages sent from that
account and to take further action where appropriate.
d) Investigating manipulations of game operations
TRAVIAN GAMES will collect and store records which reflect how the
websites and games operated by TRAVIAN GAMES are used, e.g. in-game
user activities and in-game communication between users or
communication within game-related services. This includes the monitoring
of playing patterns and checks for possible manipulations of game
operations which can then serve to detect any abusive or improper
activities of users. TRAVIAN GAMES uses special programs to detect
violations of the rules of the games, e.g. programs that can detect the use
of unauthorized scripts. In order to do that it can store IP addresses, login
data of the last fourteen days and any other data the browser transfers as
header information. Furthermore, TRAVIAN GAMES employs individuals
who are specifically trained to do this and who may be employees or
freelancers working for TRAVIAN GAMES. TRAVIAN GAMES will also select
suitable individuals from its ranks of players who have expressed an
interest in performing such tasks voluntarily. The employees, freelancers
and volunteers (“specifically trained personnel”) will have access to the
same data as the special programs used by TRAVIAN GAMES to carry out
their duties. The specifically trained employees will also be assigned to
identify, detect and penalize any infringements against the current
General Terms and Conditions and game rules, e.g. the illegal use of
several game accounts or insults to other players. The specifically trained
employees act exclusively in accordance with the stipulations and
instructions of TRAVIAN GAMES and are tasked in particular with ensuring
compliance with prevailing data protection regulations. In terms of
processing personal data, TRAVIAN GAMES remains the liable party. If
TRAVIAN GAMES ascertains that you are acting in breach of your
contractual obligations, e.g. by using unauthorized scripts, TRAVIAN
GAMES expressly reserves the right to merge your IP address with other
data which TRAVIAN GAMES has stored on you to advise you of such
infringement. TRAVIAN GAMES may then take further action against the
respective user to restore normal game operations.
e) Internal research
TRAVIAN GAMES also uses the information stored by you or about you for
internal research regarding demography, user interest and user behavior.
The use of this data is pseudononymized. You can object to this data
collection and storage at any time with effect for the future. Please send
your revocation to the email address indicated below. No other costs shall
be incurred for a revocation apart from the costs of transmitting such
revocation.
f) Payment processing
You will have to supply additional information when making a payment
and the type of data depends on the kind of payment method you have
selected. TRAVIAN GAMES offers a range of anonymous payment
methods.
TRAVIAN GAMES will forward the data required to process the payment to
the service providers responsible for collecting the payment. TRAVIAN
GAMES will assign TG Payment GmbH in Munich (Germany) to provide
such payment services. Collaboration with third parties also involves
payment processing via external service providers (PayPal, credit card
companies, mobile network operators, etc.). These third parties are legally
bound to manage your personal data in a confidential and secure manner
in accordance with prevailing legislation and may only use your personal
data to fulfill their contractual obligations.
When you initiate a payment during the game, a cookie will be set that
contains a randomly generated ID number. This cookie will be required to
return you to the game once the payment process has been completed.
TRAVIAN GAMES employs persons responsible for ensuring the correct
implementation of the payment processing is adhered to and who can
therefore access any information required to do so. Such employees act
exclusively in accordance with the stipulations and instructions of
TRAVIAN GAMES and are tasked in particular with ensuring compliance
with prevailing data protection regulations. Such employees use
anonymized payment data to detect and prevent any misuse of the
payment processes. In the event of a violation, the payment process will
be canceled. In addition, TRAVIAN GAMES reserves the right to use the
available data to implement further measures and to potentially merge it
with other personal data.
TRAVIAN GAMES is entitled to provide data to third parties to whom
receivables due to TRAVIAN GAMES from the user have been assigned or
to third parties who are responsible for collecting payment to the extent
required to fulfill the collection of the receivables or the collection of the
charges.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Transfer of your data to third parties</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>In certain cases TRAVIAN GAMES will forward your personal data to the
following third parties:
• Payment providers (see above)
• IT service providers (e.g. email providers, host providers)
• Database services (e.g. analysis of advertising campaigns)
• Associated companies (e.g. payment data to TG Payment GmbH)
• State agencies (e.g. investigating authorities)
Such third parties are legally bound to manage your personal data in a
confidential and secure manner in accordance with prevailing legislation
and can only access your personal data if such data is required to fulfill
their contract, respectively there is a legal basis for such access.
Moreover, TRAVIAN GAMES will only allow third parties to contact you for
advertising purposes with your express, prior consent, in which case
TRAVIAN GAMES will forward your email address to such third parties.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Technical features</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>a) Cookies
Cookies are small files that enable TRAVIAN GAMES to record certain
information about your device, for example to identify you when you revisit
a website or to generate statistics. Most cookies are automatically
deleted when you close the browser or exit any websites or games
operated by TRAVIAN GAMES. However, some cookies may be stored for a
longer period. The above sections describe in more detail how TRAVIAN
GAMES uses cookies.
b) Web beacons
TRAVIAN GAMES uses “web beacons” (aka clear GIFs or web bugs, etc.).
A web beacon is a link placed on a website and which points to a small
graphic image. When the website is then called up with the embedded
link, the small graphic image will automatically be requested. TRAVIAN
GAMES uses web beacons to optimize websites and advertising campaigns
by counting or recording the number of visits to a particular website, if
and when an email was opened, etc. The above sections describe in more
detail how TRAVIAN GAMES uses web beacons.
c) Social plug-ins
TRAVIAN GAMES uses social plug-ins on its websites and games such as
Facebook's “Like” button or Facebook Connect and Google's “Google +1”
button. A shared feature of social plug-ins is that when you access a
TRAVIAN GAMES website that uses a social plug-in, the same data will be
forwarded to the social plug-in provider that would be forwarded if you
accessed the provider's website directly. So for example when you call up
a provider website that has Facebook's “Like” button embedded, Facebook
will receive your IP address, the browser version and screen resolution
and the operating system of the device you have used to access the site
and the URL of the website containing the “Like” button. This applies even
if you have used none of the services offered by such providers. If the
plug-in has been provided by Facebook or Google, the abovementioned
data will be transferred to the USA. Additional information will be
forwarded if you are logged in to one of these services and/or are using
the social plug-in while you are accessing the website. Please consult your
relevant provider regarding what data will be forwarded in this event.
d) Google Analytics
TRAVIAN GAMES uses the web analysis tool Google Analytics for its
websites, games and game homepages. Google Analytics uses cookies to
enable us to analyze your visit to the games and websites operated by
TRAVIAN GAMES. To do this, Google Analytics collects data using page
views, i.e. the technical features of the device used to visit the pages and
your activities on the websites and in the games operated by TRAVIAN
GAMES. Google Analytics then analyses this data in the scope of its
contractual duties for TRAVIAN GAMES to compile reports to include
information regarding from which URL the website or TRAVIAN GAMES
game was accessed, from which approximate geographical location a
website or TRAVIAN GAMES game was visited, how long the user stayed
on the website or in the TRAVIAN GAMES game and an outline of the
user's activities during the visit. TRAVIAN GAMES has configured the
Google Analytics tool such that the last octet of your IP address will be
deleted before it is saved within Europe. You can disable the use of
cookies in your browser settings, but bear in mind that this may also
restrict the use of any TRAVIAN GAMES games or websites. Alternately,
you can download and install the relevant plug-in for your browser via this
link: (https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=de) and the Google
Analytics JavaScript code will be instructed to send no information on your
visits to TRAVIAN GAMES games and websites to Google Analytics.
e) Kontagent
TRAVIAN GAMES uses the web analysis tool Kontagent for its games. For
this, code fragments are used in the source code of the game or the
mobile apps that are then activated when you carry out a particular action
specified by TRAVIAN GAMES (e.g. registration, activation, login, account
deletion, purchase of Credits, etc.). Once activated, the following data will
be sent to the Kontagent servers located in the USA: name of the game or
website, country version of the game, a randomly generated and
anonymized ID number for your account, an ID number defined for the
specified action, description of the specified action, time stamp, browser
session ID and IP address. If you access one of the TRAVIAN GAMES
games via a mobile app, the following data will also be transferred:
network status (e.g. 3G, Wi-Fi), operating system (without the version
number) and whether the device is a smartphone or tablet. Kontagent
then analyzes this data in the scope of its contractual duties for TRAVIAN
GAMES to compile reports to ascertain how a game or mobile app is used.
In addition, Kontagent uses the transferred data in an anonymized and
aggregated form to TRAVIAN GAMES and additional clients of Kontagent
to make general statements regarding user behavior. Besides this use in
an anonymized and aggregated form, Kontagent saves and uses the data
transferred from TRAVIAN GAMES only in the scope of its contractual
duties and as instructed by TRAVIAN GAMES. You can object to this data
collection and storage at any time with effect for the future. Please send
your revocation to the email address indicated below. No other costs shall
be incurred for a revocation apart from the costs of transmitting such
revocation.
f) Adeven
TRAVIAN GAMES uses the external analysis and tracking tool Adeven in its
games. In this process, code fragments are inserted into the source text
of the mobile app and then activated when a particular action or event
defined by TRAVIAN GAMES (e.g. installing an app, performing a specific
action, purchasing credits, etc.) is carried out. Once these events are
activated the following data is sent to the Adeven GmbH servers in
Germany: game name, country version of the game, a randomly
generated and anonymized ID number for your account, a defined ID
number for the specific action, description of the action, time stamp,
browser session ID, http header, MAC or IP address, network status (e.g.
3G, Wi-Fi), OS type (omitting the version number) and if it is a
smartphone or tablet. Adeven then analyzes this data in the scope of its
contractual duties to TRAVIAN GAMES to compile reports for TRAVIAN
GAMES to make general statements regarding user behavior. Adeven uses
the data transferred from TRAVIAN GAMES only in the scope of its
contractual duties and as instructed by TRAVIAN GAMES. You may object
to this data collection and storage at any time with effect for the future.
Please send your revocation to the email address indicated below. No
other costs shall be incurred for a revocation apart from the costs of
transmitting such revocation.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Revocation of consent</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>You may revoke your consent at any time unless TRAVIAN GAMES is
processing your personal data for contractual or legal purposes. If the
revocation concerns the receipt of game information or any other emails,
all game information or other emails sent to you include the option to
unsubscribe from any further game information or emails. No other costs
shall be incurred for a revocation apart from the costs of transmitting such
revocation.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Amendments to or deletion of personal data</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>You may amend your personal data at any time (e.g. to update or correct
such data) or delete your personal data in its entirety. Please note that
TRAVIAN GAMES will not be able to comply with your deletion request if
such request conflicts with any obligations to preserve records or with any
legitimate interests of TRAVIAN GAMES or third parties. If you would like
TRAVIAN GAMES to amend your personal data or to cease using your
data, please contact TRAVIAN GAMES at privacy@traviangames.com.
TRAVIAN GAMES will then make the requested changes or delete your
data as quickly as possible. However, TRAVIAN GAMES must remind you
that, for technical or organizational reasons, some measures may still be
carried out after you have submitted your request for deletion had such
measures already been initiated but not completed by that time.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Information on personal data</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Upon request, TRAVIAN GAMES will inform you of all the personal data
that is stored about you free of charge. This information will be sent to
you in electronic form, generally via email.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Final provisions</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>TRAVIAN GAMES reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any
time; however TRAVIAN GAMES shall always observe the applicable data
protection legislation.
Should you have any general questions on this Privacy Policy and on data
protection at TRAVIAN GAMES, please contact us at the addresses below.
If possible, please contact us using the email address you submitted when
you registered with the game.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
