<POLICY modification_date="" policy_url="http://m.ciao.de/Home/Privacy" website_category="Home" website_index="072" website_url="ciao.de">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>General information »Privacy policy Terms of Shopping Guide GmbH
Collection of personal data
Use of personal data
Transmission of personal data
Viewing / Changing Personal Data
Delete the account
Use of Cookies on our website
Security measures
Protection from web crawlers or spam
Transmission of data within the enterprise group
Modification of Privacy Policy</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Collection of personal data</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Personal data is collected by Ciao:
During registration at one of our panels;
After registering, when we ask panel members to provide more personal information so that we can invite them to appropriate surveys in the future;
While answering a survey.

To become a panel member, you will be asked to provide some personal and general information in a registration survey. Your e-mail address we ask to send you e-mail invitations to participate in future surveys. The other we collect information such as name, address, gender, birthday and employment status is used to assign people to appropriate market research projects. Your date of birth is needed to automatically update your age and be able to address specific age-related market groups targeted. We ask for this information so that we can determine if you qualify for certain projects. Your account information, we need to ensure that your remit the earned by taking surveys money can. Once you have registered, you will receive a Ciao ID and can pseudonymous use all Ciao offers. Your consent to the storage and processing of certain personal information may you at any time revoke in writing with immediate effect. Ciao is the data immediately, but not later than within 7 days, remove from its databases irrevocable.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Use of personal data</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Ciao commissioned by market research companies, manufacturers and wholesalers with the implementation of surveys. The information collected in these surveys will be kept strictly confidential and our customers in an anonymised form. The members IDs are replaced with individual identifying codes. Only Ciao features to the associated member name. Ciao Moreover determined data on population statistics, personal interests and behavior of its members, in order to optimize the service it through a better understanding of the structure members. Also this information is collected only as a whole and analyzed. Through your membership at Ciao, you agree to receive e-mails that invite you to participate in surveys. They are equipped with the automatic set up your personal account for the earned by participating in surveys balances agree. During registration, enter revocable, whether you agree with the sending of the e-mail newsletter, you agree to the forwarding to be we will inform you in this way about new features or promotions on our website.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Transmission of personal data</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>A disclosure of your personal information is basically only in anonymous form to our customer as part of market research projects. Ciao does not release personal information about you unless you have given us your express permission or if we are required by law.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Viewing / Changing Personal Data</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>You can always view the information in your Ciao account with your member name and Ciao Ciao your password and update as necessary.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Delete the account</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>You can delete or deactivate your Ciao account at any time. To do so, please in your profile on the "Settings" tab and select "Cancel Membership". If you delete your Ciao account, your entire person-related information that you provided at registration, promptly, at the latest within 7 days away permanently from our user database. The opinions remain under your alias still retrievable, as well as your alias deleted in justified cases on request. Unless you have received a payment from Ciao, your bank details and the date and amount of any payments of our accounts will be stored exclusively for the fulfillment of the statutory retention periods.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Use of Cookies on our website</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Ciao uses cookies, ie files that are stored on your computer, can also be accessed and used to personalize the way you use our internet site. The information saved is used for the functionality of the site by, for example, noted your visual preference or the frequency of "pop-up" windows is regulated. They are deleted after a month. Furthermore, no cookies are used by advertising partners, on the Ciao has no influence. These are used to select customer-specific advertising. You are free to prevent cookies from being saved on your hard disk by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser. The acceptance of cookies is not required to use our service. Nevertheless, we would like to point out that the rejection can lead to limited functionality.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Security measures</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>The information in your Ciao account and in your Ciao profile are password-protected so that only you have access to this personal information. Please note that you must provide your password to any other person. In e-mails that you receive unexpectedly or that you did not request, Ciao will never ask for your password. Please remember to log out of your account and close the window of your Internet browser when you leave the Ciao page, and this is especially true if you use a PC in public places. This is currently the most reliable method to ensure that no one has access to your personal information.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Protection from web crawlers or spam</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Ciao assures you that we will use your e-mail address with your express consent only for the specified in the Terms of uses. We will use your email address will not sell to third parties and will prevent your e-mail address is detected by "web crawlers" or "spiders", unless this is in our power. If you believe that your e-mail address was recorded in this way, please contact us immediately to our technical support team.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Transmission of data within the enterprise group</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Ciao belongs to the group of companies of Microsoft Corporation. You agree that your data may be transferred within that group of companies and within the Ciao group. We assure you that in the event of such a transfer the security and confidentiality is ensured unchanged and the data remain subject to the above Privacy Policy.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Modification of Privacy Policy</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>If you change the Privacy Policy, we will indicate on the Ciao website on this.

Status 09/2010</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
