<POLICY modification_date="" policy_url="http://portal.lacaixa.es/general/avisolegal_en.html" website_category="Business" website_index="072" website_url="lacaixa.es">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>Web portal legal information
Caixabank, S.A. (from here on, ”la Caixa”) is the entity that owns the portal or website of ”la Caixa” which you have accessed.

Access to the portal or any of the websites of ”la Caixa” and to the information about any of the products and services contained in it entails acceptance of the general conditions laid down in this Legal Notice. This is why you must read its contents carefully if you want to access and make use of the information and services offered about the portal or any of the websites of ”la Caixa”.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Validity of the information and contents</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>The information contained on these pages is valid on the date of their last updating.

The present conditions are valid from the date of their last updating. ”la Caixa” reserves the right to modify them at any time, in which case these changes will enter into force on their publication and will be applicable to all users of the portal or websites from this date.

The contents of any of the web pages, especially information and advertising references, make up no binding offer, unless explicitly indicated otherwise. ”la Caixa” reserves the right to introduce modifications or omit in part or fully the current contents whenever it deems appropriate and to prevent or restrict access temporarily or permanently.
”la Caixa” can include on any of its websites contents from third parties and links to web pages of third parties, always with the authorisation of their owners, as well as links to social networks and other information. In none of these cases will ”la Caixa” be responsible for the pages and contents of third parties or for their operation and availability.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Navigation and personalization</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Simple navigation through the websites of ”la Caixa” is free and does not require the user to register beforehand. Nevertheless, access, contracting or the use of some products and services may require user registration. In such a case, each of the products and services will be governed by its own specific conditions, without detriment to the conditions stipulated here.

On some of the portals and websites, users will be offered the possibility of personalising their pages, by including different screen backgrounds or configuring access to their favourite products and services, in order to make navigation and location of the resources used more efficient and functional and better adapted to the tastes and customs of each user.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Security</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>The portal and websites of ”la Caixa” are endowed with sufficient certificates, seals and ratifications of security and quality to offer users a secure environment. Notwithstanding, we recommend you consult and read carefully the Security Recommendations that ”la Caixa” makes available to all users on its portal.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Privacy and data protection policy</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>”la Caixa” complies fully with current legislation on protection of personal data and with the confidentiality commitments that are proper to banking operations.

”la Caixa” has adopted the technical measures needed to maintain the requisite level of security, depending on the nature of the personal data processed and the circumstances of the processing, with the aim of avoiding, as far as possible and always depending on the state of the technology, unauthorised disturbance, loss, processing or access.

When a customer or user is asked to fill in a form that gathers personal data, he/she will be informed about the recipient of the data, the purpose for which the data were gathered and the identity and address of the person/entity responsible for the file and of his/her power to exercise the rights of access, rectification, cancellation and opposition to the processing of his/her data. The personal data gathered will only be processed and/or transferred for the purpose expressed, and always with the consent of the user or customer.

So that the information held in our files is always up-to-date and contains no mistakes, we ask our customers and users to tell us as quickly as possible of any modifications or corrections to their personal data.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Cookies policy</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>The web pages of ”la Caixa” use cookies, which are small data files that are stored in the user or customer's computer and allow our systems to remember characteristics or preferences of his/her navigation through our web pages. The cookies can then be used to personalise access on follow-up visits, make navigation more secure, collect statistical information on the navigation done and discover user preferences.

The cookies policy of ”la Caixa” is subject to the EU and Spanish regulations in force concerning personal data processing and to the protection of privacy in electronic communications. By virtue of this, ”la Caixa” will inform users of the cookies it deploys on each website (“Information about the cookies used”) and, when necessary, will request the user's consent to their deployment.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Mobile portals and geolocation</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Some of the web pages of ”la Caixa” are adapted for use in mobile devices, for which reason the presentation and contents of the various mobile applications may not coincide or reflect precisely those of the portal or the various websites.

In addition, some of the web pages adapted for mobile devices or some applications may possess geolocation functions, in order to determine at all times the location of the mobile whenever the user turns on the function. This enables customers to access the services that ”la Caixa” has available that require geolocation.

Access to these services will need the user to turn on the geolocation function on his/her mobile, which can then be deactivated at any time.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Intellectual and industrial policy</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>The portal and web pages of ”la Caixa”, the pages that it contains and the information and contents of them include texts, documents, photographs, drawings, graphic items, data bases and computer programs, as well as logos, brands, commercial names and other distinctive signs, that are protected by intellectual or industrial copyright, of which ”la Caixa” or the companies in its Group are holders or legitimate licensees.

”la Caixa” provides no guarantee of the lawfulness or legality of the information and items contained on the web pages of ”la Caixa”, in cases when neither ”la Caixa” nor the companies in its Group are the owners.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Forbidden and permitted uses</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Any kind of exploitation of the above-mentioned work, creations and distinctive signs is forbidden without the prior and explicit authorisation of their owners, including every kind of reproduction, distribution, transfer to third parties, making them public or altering them, by means of any kind of support or medium. Failure to comply with this prohibition will constitute an infraction that can be sanctioned under current legislation.

Nevertheless, on his/her own account and risk, the user may download or copy items exclusively for his/her personal use, provided that this does not infringe any of the intellectual or industrial property rights of ”la Caixa”. In particular, items cannot be changed, modified or suppressed wholly or in part. In no case will this imply any authorisation or licence over the property rights of ”la Caixa” or its Group companies.

It is forbidden, except in cases explicitly authorised by ”la Caixa”, to establish links or hyperlinks from portals or websites of third parties to web pages of ”la Caixa” other than the main page of its portal, or to present the web pages of ”la Caixa” or the information therein under frames, distinctive signs, brand names or business or marketing names of another person, company or entity.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Financial and Stock Exchange information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>The portal or the websites of ”la Caixa” provide no investment recommendations, no legal or tax advice and no other recommendations of any kind. The information is of a general nature and in no case takes into account specific or particular criteria and objectives concerning investment or the financial situation. As such, the information contained on them must not be used to make investments or take decisions.

In the case of negotiated stock, any decision to subscribe, purchase or sell must be adopted whilst bearing in mind public information.

The contents of the web pages do not amount to an offer to sell shares in the United States of America. Shares cannot be offered, sold or subscribed in the United States of America unless they have been registered or received exemption from registration, as stipulated in the US Securities Act of 1933.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Responsibilities</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>”la Caixa” does not guarantee continuous access or the correct viewing, download or utility of the items and information contained on the web pages of ”la Caixa”, which may be impeded, hindered or interrupted by factors or circumstances beyond its control.

”la Caixa” is not responsible for the information and other contents that are part of spaces or web pages of third parties and are accessible from the web pages of ”la Caixa” through links or hyperlinks. Nor is it responsible for the information and other contents that are part of spaces or web pages of third parties from which there is access through links or hyperlinks to the portal of ”la Caixa” or to any of its web pages; or for the information and other contents on any web page of third parties that is presented under the appearance and distinctive signs of ”la Caixa”, barring explicit authorisation from the latter.

”la Caixa” and its information suppliers as third parties accept no responsibility for the information, contents of all kinds, products or services offered or provided through the web pages of ”la Caixa” by third persons or entities, even though these may belong to the same economic Group, or, in particular, for any kind of damage or prejudice that, linked to the preceding, may be caused by: i) lack of information or deficiencies in the information provided to users, or in its veracity, accuracy or adequacy; ii) non-compliance or defective or late compliance with contracts or pre-contractual relationships; iii) non-compliance with the obligations incumbent on providers of services of the information society; iv) infraction of the rights of consumers and users; v) infraction of intellectual and industrial property rights; performance of acts of disloyal competition or illicit publicity; vi) infraction of the right to data protection, to professional secrecy, to honour, to personal and family privacy and to people's images; vii) in general, non-compliance with any laws, customs or codes of conduct applicable; and viii) any decision taken based on information supplied through the portal of ”la Caixa”.

Neither ”la Caixa” nor the suppliers of information as third parties accept any responsibility for damage, prejudice, losses, claims or expenses, caused by (i) interference, interruptions, faults, omissions, phone breakdowns, delays, blockages or disconnections in the operation of the electronic system, brought about by defects, overloading or errors in the telecommunications lines or networks, or by any other reason outside the control of ”la Caixa”; (ii) illegitimate interference by use of malignant programs of any kind or through any communications medium, such as computer viruses or anything else; iii) inappropriate or improper use of the web pages of ”la Caixa”; (iv) errors of security or navigation caused by malfunction of the Navigator or the use of out-of-date versions of it.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Applicable legislation</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>The present general conditions will be governed by Spanish law.


© Caixabank, S.A. 2013 Barcelona.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
