<POLICY modification_date="November 01, 2013" policy_url="http://wiki.xbmc.org/index.php?title=XBMC:Privacy_policy" website_category="Games" website_index="054" website_url="xbmc.org">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>XBMC:General disclaimer
(Redirected from XBMC:Privacy policy)
XBMC Media Center is a free and open source cross-platform media player and home entertainment system software. The services for the XBMC software (including developer tools, resources, download areas, files, source code, product information, documentation, communication forums, bug tracker, wiki, etc. all collectively called "services") that the XBMC Project, its members, and websites provide are for the purpose of providing support to the XBMC community. The structure of the project allows anyone to alter the contents of provided in these services. These services and all content, products and services on them are provided on an “as is”, "with all faults", and "as available" basis, without warranty of any kind, either express or implied. Your use of these services is at your own risk. XBMC disclaims all warranties, express or implied, including without limitation, warranties of merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose.
XBMC disclaims liability for any direct, indirect, incidental, special, consequential, exemplary, punitive or other damages, or lost profits, that may result directly or indirectly from the use of these services and any material that is downloaded or obtained through the use of these services.
This includes, without limitation, any damage to computer systems, hardware or software, loss of data, or any other performance failures, any errors, bugs, viruses or other defects that result from, or are associated with the use of this website.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>1 No formal peer review</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>None of the contributors, sponsors, administrators, or anyone else connected with XBMC in any way whatsoever can be responsible for the appearance of any inaccurate or libelous information or for your use of the information contained in or linked from these services.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>2 No contract; limited license</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Please make sure that you understand that the information provided by any of these services is being provided freely, and that no kind of agreement or contract is created between you and the owners or users of these services, the owners of the servers upon which it is housed, the individual contributors to these services, any project administrators, sysops or anyone else who is in any way connected with the XBMC project subject to your claims against them directly. You are being granted a limited license to copy anything from this site; it does not create or imply any contractual or extracontractual liability on the part of XBMC or any of its agents, members, organizers or other users.
There is no agreement or understanding between you and XBMC regarding your use or modification of this information beyond the Creative Commons Attribution-Sharealike 3.0 Unported License (CC-BY-SA); neither is anyone at XBMC responsible should someone change, edit, modify or remove any information that you may post on any service provided for XBMC.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>3 Copyright</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Only text is assumed to be released under the Creative Commons Attribution-Sharealike 3.0 Unported License. Images are assumed to be under a different license unless otherwise specifically noted.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>4 Trademarks</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Any of the trademarks, service marks, collective marks, design rights or similar rights that are mentioned, used or cited in the services provided for XBMC are the property of their respective owners. Their use in any XBMC service does not imply that you may use them for any other purpose other than for the same or a similar use as contemplated by the original authors of content provided by these services under the CC-BY-SA licensing scheme. Unless otherwise stated XBMC are neither endorsed by nor affiliated with any of the holders of any such rights and as such XBMC cannot grant any rights to use any otherwise protected materials. Your use of any such or similar incorporeal property is at your own risk.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>5 Jurisdiction and legality of content</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Publication of information found in any of the services provided for XBMC may be in violation of the laws of the country or jurisdiction from where you are viewing this information. The servers providing these services are located in different locations of the world and is maintained in reference to the protections afforded under local and federal law in respect to their location. Laws in your country or jurisdiction may not protect or allow the same kinds of speech or distribution. XMBC does not encourage the violation of any laws; and cannot be responsible for any violations of such laws, should you link to the domain of the websites of these services or use, reproduce, or republish the information contained therein.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>6 Final Remarks</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Yes, it gives most of us a headache to read all of this, but it's important so thank you for your patience and now, enjoy XBMC!
Category: XBMC
Log in / create accountProject pageDiscussionReadView sourceView history
Google Search

Navigation
Wiki help
Toolbox
This page was last modified on 13 November 2013, at 22:34.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
