<POLICY modification_date="" policy_url="http://www.iberia.com/us/legal-information/" website_category="Recreation" website_index="077" website_url="iberia.com">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>Personal data protection and information security
Any personal data provided during the "Online Reservation and Purchase" process will be included in a file that Iberia L.A.E S.A. OPERADORA, Sole-Shareholder Company is responsible for and will be used in order to manage the requested service, obtain supplementary services or facilitate the immigration process and entry into a State's territory. Similarly, we hereby inform you that, in compliance with the express request made to all airline companies for the purpose of controlling and safeguarding public security, Iberia will be authorised to report your data as a passenger to the government authorities of the country of origin, transit or destination at any time prior to your arrival for the purpose of internal security control. The United States also requires this information for planes that fly over their air space. This information may also be provided to other States which, by virtue of that stipulated in any applicable laws or treaties, require this information to fly over their air space.
In accordance with the laws and regulations applicable in Spain and abroad, in certain cases the Carrier may be obliged to report personal data to the relevant Spanish or foreign public authorities (customs, immigration, etc.), in particular for the purposes of preventing and combating terrorism and other serious crimes.
It should be noted that certain of the aforementioned recipients may be located outside of the European Union and have access to all or part of the personal data gathered by the Carrier (surnames, given name, passport number, trip details, etc.) in order to correctly perform the Passenger Transport Agreement or as the result of a specific law being enacted. Any data transferred outside the European Union is done so in accordance with that established in Personal Data Protection Organic Law 15/1999, of 13 December.
Certain personal data must be gathered in order to make the Reservation and establish the Transport Agreement. Naturally, Passengers may exercise their right of objection to the gathering and processing of this data, however, this could lead to the trip being cancelled or make it impossible to access certain specific additional services that were requested (special meals, etc.). It should also be noted that, in accordance with the laws and regulations applicable in Spain and abroad, failure to report certain data, or reporting incorrect data, could lead to the passenger being denied boarding onto the plane or entry into a foreign country, whereby the Carrier may not be deemed liable for this incident.
The act of visiting this website does not imply that the user is obliged to provide any personal information. When users are asked to provide personal data, they will be informed whether the data being gathered is voluntary or mandatory. Should the user refuse to provide any mandatory data, they will not be able to assess the service for which the data was requested. Similarly, data may be provided voluntarily for the purpose of rendering the services offered in the most optimal manner possible.
In the event the users of this website are required to provide their e-mail address in order to access certain services offered, they may request not to receive any type of communication from Iberia that may be sent. Iberia will provide the users that subscribed to any type of e-mail list on the website with the adequate mechanisms to unsubscribe to the list.
IBERIA registers IP addresses (which all users have when accessing the website) exclusively for internal purposes, such as for obtaining statistics regarding access and market segmentation. IBERIA does not associate IP addresses with information that could identify the user personally, by providing third parties with informative extracts of traffic to the website that do not affect the anonymity of the user, with data on the number of visits to a certain section of the website, traffic flows and trends, etc.
Access to this website may also imply the use of cookies. Cookies are small amounts of information that are stored on your browser in order for the server to remember certain information that only the server that created the cookie may subsequently read. In general, cookies have a limited duration. Cookies do not allow users to be contacted through their telephone number, e-mail address or by any other means of contact. Cookies are not able to extract information from the user's hard drive or steal personal information. Those users who do not wish to store cookies or who want to be notified when they are added, may configure their browsers accordingly.
This web page uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc., a Delaware company whose main office is at 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View (California), CA 94043, USA ("Google").
Google Analytics uses cookies, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyse how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process this information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google.
This website may use tracking tags on certain web pages for measuring and optimising marketing campaigns, but does not store any of the user's personal information under any circumstances.
You may choose not to allow your data or information to be processed and refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however, please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.
All users whose personal data is processed, may exercise their rights of objection, access, correction and deletion with regard to their data under the terms envisaged by Personal Data Protection Organic Law 15/1999. These rights may be exercised through one of the following channels:
In writing by sending a request, together with the documentation evidencing your identity, to the following address:
IBERIA L.A.E. S.A.
Dirección Sistemas / U. Seguridad Informática
Zona Industrial nº 2
28042, Madrid
By fax, sending a request, together with the documentation evidencing your identity, to + 34 91 587 55 64, addressed to "Attn: Personal Data"
Pursuant to Law 56/2007, on Measures to Promote the Information Society, users may also send a request by e-mail to atencion_datospersonales@iberia.es, signing the request electronically with the Spanish electronic National Identification Document (DNI), whereby in this case, further evidence on the part of the applicant is not necessary.

In order to exercise your right of cancellation, you may use the following document
If you are unable to view PDF files, you can download the file by clicking on this button

For any further clarifications or questions, please contact the company at the following e-mail address: atencion_datospersonales@iberia.es

The interested party is hereby informed that the data processing necessary in order to process his request may include operational communications, which may or may not be sent via electronic means (e-mail, telephone, etc.), and which in any case will not require any consideration on the part of the interested party, including the occasional quality survey sent to verify the user's degree of satisfaction with the services provided by the company.
The interested party is also informed that, for the purpose of recording and checking the veracity of the information provided during the purchase process, the data provided may be verified with information managers for the sole purpose of preventing erroneous or fraudulent operations.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
