<POLICY modification_date="" policy_url="http://www.ratemyprofessors.com/PrivacyPolicy.jsp" website_category="Reference" website_index="089" website_url="ratemyprofessors.com">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>RATEMYPROFESSORS PRIVACY POLICY


RMP ACQUISITIONS, LLC ("RATEMYPROFESSORS") VALUES THE PROTECTION OF INDIVIDUAL PRIVACY. THIS DOCUMENT SETS FORTH RATEMYPROFESSORS' ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY ("PRIVACY POLICY") FOR RATEMYPROFESSORS' WEBSITES, INCLUDING THE WEBSITES WWW.RATEMYPROFESSORS.COM, WWW.RATEMYPROFESSORS.CA, WWW.RATEMYPROFESSOR.CA, RATEMYPROFESSORS.CO.UK, RATEMYPROFESSOR.CO.UK, RATEMYPROFESSORS.CO.NZ, AND RATEMYPROFESSOR.CO.NZ (COLLECTIVELY, THE "SITE"). BY USING THE SITE, YOU, THE USER ("YOU") INDICATE THAT YOU HAVE READ AND AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, DO NOT USE THE SITE IN ANY MANNER. THIS PRIVACY POLICY DOES NOT GOVERN PRIVACY PRACTICES ASSOCIATED WITH OFFLINE ACTIVITIES.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Personal Information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>During your interactions with the Site, RateMyProfessors may request personal information from you. RateMyProfessors currently does not use personal information other than to process your request that required you to submit personal information, to facilitate your participation in RateMyProfessors' services, to send you reminders, for record-keeping purposes and to alert you regarding RateMyProfessors products, services or promotions that RateMyProfessors believes may be of interest to you. RateMyProfessors does not make any visitor-provided personal information available to third parties. Such visitor-provided personal information and other user information may be shared with and transferred to non-affiliated third parties in the event of a bankruptcy, merger, acquisition, transfer of control, joint venture or other business combination involving RateMyProfessors (or its successors).</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Other Information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>RateMyProfessors may use server logs to record a visitor's Internet Protocol (IP) address and to collect general information about the visit to the Site, such as the time and length of the visit, and the web pages accessed during the visit. RateMyProfessors may use this information for Site management and performance monitoring. RateMyProfessors currently does not make any of this information collected by RateMyProfessors available to third parties.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Advertising</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>The Site may contain third party advertising in the form of pop-up or banner ads delivered to you while you visit the Site. RateMyProfessors' third party advertising partners providing such advertising (Partners) may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that the Partners believe may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and how you might limit collection of this information, please contact us using the contact information at the end of this Privacy Policy.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Links</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>The Site may contain links to third party sites at which personal information is collected and used. Your visit to any third party website is governed by the privacy policy applicable to that site. RateMyProfessors cannot control nor is it responsible for any such third party collection or use of your personal information.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Chat Rooms and Newsgroups</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>The Site may offer chat rooms, newsgroups, or other forums which permit individuals to interact online. Any information you transmit online in such forums will be made public and RateMyProfessors cannot control nor is it responsible for the use any third party may make of such information.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Children</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>The Site is a general audience site which is neither designed nor intended to collect personal information from children who are under the age of 13. In order to ensure compliance with the provisions of the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, children under the age of 13 should not provide any personal information to the Site.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Security</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>RateMyProfessors uses commercially reasonable efforts to ensure that any information you give to RateMyProfessors is stored and maintained in a secure environment. All credit card information is stored in encrypted format.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Cookies</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>RateMyProfessors may use cookies and other tools such as clear gifs from time to time to allow RateMyProfessors to automate access and the data entry functions of the Site such as to tailor the Site to your preferences or interests, customize promotions or marketing, or identify which areas of the Site are more popular. A cookie is a small, unique text file that a website can send to your computer hard drive when you visit that site. RateMyProfessors does not make any cookie information collected by RateMyProfessors available to third parties.

RateMyProfessors' Partners may also use cookies and other tools such as clear gifs for advertising management purposes such as to allow the Partners to tailor advertising to your preferences or interests.

Most web browsers can either alert you to the use of cookies or refuse to accept cookies entirely. If you do not want RateMyProfessors or the Partners to deploy cookies in your browser, you can set your browser to reject cookies or to notify you when a website tries to put a cookie on your computer. Rejecting cookies may affect your ability to use of some of the products and/or services at the Site.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Privacy Policy Changes</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We reserve the right to revise this Privacy Policy at any time by updating this posting without advance notice to you. Such revisions shall be effective to you immediately upon posting. Notice of material changes will be posted on the RateMyProfessors homepage. However, we encourage you to check this Privacy Policy often for updates. We may also email you about these changes.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>RateMyProfessors Contact Information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact RateMyProfessors using one of the options below:

RateMyProfessors.com, LLC
1515 Broadway
New York, New York 10036
Attn: Business and Legal Affairs, Office Number: 24-40

E-Mail: info@ratemyprofessors.com
Site: www.ratemyprofessors.com</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
