<POLICY modification_date="" policy_url="http://www.jal.co.jp/en/footer/security.html" website_category="Recreation" website_index="047" website_url="jal.co.jp">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>Japan Airlines Co., Ltd., Japan Transocean Air Co., Ltd., JAL Express Co., Ltd., J-Air Co., Ltd., Japan Air Commuter Co., Ltd., and Ryuku Air Commuter Co., Ltd. (hereinafter "JAL Group Airlines") shall handle and protect the customers' personal information in accordance with the "Act on the Protection of Personal Information" of Japan and "JAL Group's Basic Policies on Information Security and the Protection of Personal Information."</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Obtaining Personal Information and Purpose of Use</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>JAL Group Airlines shall acquire the customers' personal information through appropriate and fair means and use it for the purposes below.
(1) To provide air transportation services (Reservations, sales, check-in, airport handling, cabin services, etc. Including cases of interline transportations,joint operations, code-sharing, contract operations, etc. in addition to normal transportation services)
(2)	To provide services relating to JAL Mileage Bank (hereinafter "JMB")
(3)	To provide other products and services
(4)	To provide information and communications; to conduct questionnaires relating to products, services, various events, campaigns, and such
(5)	To conduct sales analysis, investigations and research; to develop new services and products
(6)	To conduct operations relating to 1-5 above; to respond to inquires, etc.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Management and Protection of Personal Information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>JAL Group Airlines shall appropriately manage and protect the customers' personal information, in accordance with "JAL Group's Basic Policies on Information Security and the Protection of Personal Information."</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Provision of Personal Data to a Third Party</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>JAL Group Airlines shall not disclose or provide the customers' personal data to a third party, except in cases described below. The provision of personal information to service providers and the joint use of personal information shall be implemented in accordance with Articles 4. and 5. below.
(1)	Cases in which the customer personally gives his/her consent
(2)	Cases in which the provision of personal data is based on laws
(3)	Cases in which the provision of personal data is necessary for the protection of the life, body, or property of an individual and in which it is difficult to obtain the consent of the person
(4)	Cases in which the provision of personal data is specially necessary for improving public hygiene or promoting the sound growth of children and in which it is difficult to obtain the consent of the person
(5)	Cases in which the provision of personal data is necessary for cooperating with a state institution, a local public body, or an individual or entity entrusted by one in executing the operations prescribed by laws and in which obtaining the consent of the person might impede the execution of the operations concerned</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Provision of Personal Information to Service Providers and Relevant Management</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>JAL Group Airlines may entrust the handling of personal information, within the scope required to achieve the purpose of use, to a third party other than the company itself. In this case, the JAL Group Airlines shall conduct appropriate management and supervision in accordance with item 6 of "JAL Group's Basic Policies on Information Security and the Protection of Personal Information."</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Joint Use of Personal Information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>JAL Group Airlines shall jointly use the customers' personal information as follows.
Purpose of joint use
To provide air transportation services; to provide services closely related to air travel such as tours, hotels and baggage home delivery; to accumulate mileage and manage mileage awards; to provide information, e.g. sales promotion materials including those of partner companies, questionnaires, product development, ; and to conduct other operations relating to those
Data to be used jointly
Membership number, customer's name, birthday, gender, address, TEL/FAX numbers, e-mail address, information on employment (company name, department, job title, address, TEL/FAX numbers), mailing address of items sent to customers, e.g. ticket, itinerary, type of member's card, member's service qualifications, membership region, accumulated mileage, reservations/boarding information, need for arrangement of wheelchair, etc.
Range of users
JAL Group Airlines (*1) , JALCard, Jalpak, JAL Hotels, JAL ABC, and JAL Sales companies
*1 JAL Group Airlines are Japan Airlines Co., Ltd. , Japan Transocean Air Co., Ltd., JAL Express Co., Ltd., J-AIR Co., Ltd., Japan Air Commuter Co., Ltd., and Ryukyu Air Commuter Co., Ltd.
Administrator of personal information
Japan Airlines Co., Ltd.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Request for Disclosure, etc. and Inquiries</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>(1) "Notification of purpose of use," "Disclosure," "Correction, etc." "Stopping the use, etc." of retained personal data

We will respond to requests by a customer or his/her representative as follows in accordance with the "Act on the Protection of Personal Information" of Japan.
Notification of purpose of use
We will notify the purpose of use of such retained personal data as may lead to the identification of the person concerned. However, in the following cases, we may reject a request, in whole or in part, and give the reason why.
[1] Cases in which notifying the person of the purpose of use or publicly announcing it might harm the life, body, property, or other rights or interests of the person or a third party
[2] Cases in which notifying the person of the purpose of use or publicly announcing it might harm the rights or legitimate interests of the JAL Group Airlines
[3] Cases in which it is necessary to cooperate with a state institution or a local public body in executing the operations prescribed by laws and in which notifying the person of the Purpose of Use or publicly announcing it might impede the execution of the operations concerned
Disclosure
We will disclose such retained personal data as may lead to the identification of the person concerned. (When the retained personal data does not exist, we will respond accordingly.) However, in the following cases, we may reject a request, in whole or in part, and give the reason why.
[1] Cases in which disclosure might harm the life, body, property, or other rights or interests of the person or a third party
[2] Cases in which disclosure might seriously impede the proper execution of the business of the entity concerned handling personal information
[3] Cases in which disclosure violates other laws
Correction, etc.
When requested by a person to correct, add, or delete such retained personal data as may lead to the identification of the person concerned on the ground that the retained personal data is contrary to the fact (hereinafter "Correction, etc."), we will, except in cases in which special procedures are prescribed by any other laws for such correction, addition, or deletion, make a necessary investigation. As a result, when we have corrected, added, or deleted all or part of the retained personal data as requested, we will notify the effect without delay. When we have decided not to make such correction, addition, or deletion, we will notify and give the reason without delay.
Stopping the use, etc.
When requested to stop using, erase or stop providing to a third party such retained personal data as may lead to the identification of the person concerned (hereinafter "Stopping the use, etc."), and where it is found that the request has a reason, we will stop using, erase or stop providing to a third party the retained personal data concerned without delay to the extent necessary for redressing the violation. However, if it costs a great deal or otherwise difficult to stop using or to erase the retained personal data concerned, we may take necessary alternative measures to protect the rights and interests of the person.
When we have stopped using, erased or stopped providing to a third party all or part of the retained personal data as requested, we will notify without delay. When we have decided not to stop using, not to erase or not to stop providing a third party the retained personal data, we will notify and give the reason without delay.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
