<POLICY modification_date="December 10, 2013" policy_url="http://www.hi5.com/terms_of_service.html?#privacy_policy" website_category="Society" website_index="013" website_url="hi5.com">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>PRIVACY POLICY
Updated as of December 10, 2013</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>User Privacy</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>This Privacy Policy ("Policy") explains how your personal information is collected, used and disclosed by hi5 Inc. ("hi5") and its parent company, Tagged, Inc. ("Tagged"). This Policy applies to the websites of hi5 and Tagged, including www.hi5.com, www.tagged.com and any other online and mobile applications and services operated by hi5 or Tagged (collectively, the "Sites").

The Sites are intended to let you meet and interact with new people and stay in touch with friends. Like any website that offers a service where you register and provide information about yourself or your opinions, it is wise to pay attention to your personal information. At hi5, we understand this, and have established this Policy to explain how information is collected on the Sites, and how this information is used and disclosed.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>How Does hi5 Protect Children's Privacy</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>The safety and privacy of children is extremely important to us.

hi5 is a general audience web site that complies with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). Our registration process is designed to restrict children under the age of 13 from becoming members of hi5 and using our site. If we receive information suggesting that a user who has registered with hi5 is under the age of 13, we require the user to provide evidence confirming that the user is at least 13 years old. If the user fails to provide such information within 48 hours, we immediately terminate the user's account and nullify all personally identifiable information displaying on the site.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>What Is the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) requires that commercial web sites obtain parental consent (under most circumstances) prior to the collection of any personally identifiable information from children whom they know to be under the age of 13. In addition, COPPA requires that web sites that collect personal information from children under the age of 13 provide parents with:

Notice. Parents must be provided notice regarding what information is collected, how the information will be used, and with whom the information may be shared.
The ability to prevent further use of the information collected about the child and prevent any future collection of personal information from the child.
The ability to access and review their child's personal information.
COPPA also limits the amount of personal information a web site can collect from a child. Web sites may not collect any more personal information than is necessary to participate in a given game or activity.

For more information about COPPA, please visit the Federal Trade Commission's web site.

Parents: If your child is under the age of 13 and has joined hi5 using a false age, please notify hi5 at http://www.hi5.com/contact.html and we will immediately cancel your child's account and nullify all personally identifiable information displaying on the site. If you would like to know more about our site, information practices, stored information about your child, or how to close your child's account, please contact hi5 by sending a letter to hi5 Inc., 110 Pacific Ave Mall, Box #117, San Francisco, CA 94111. We will happily respond to all letters from parents with Privacy questions or concerns.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>User Information Collected by hi5</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Personally Identifiable User Information
We collect information about you in various ways when you use our Sites. For example, we collect personally identifiable information you provide to us, such as when you register on the Sites, including. your first and last name, email address, zip code, a user-chosen password, and date of birth and other personal information. To complete the registration process, hi5 sends a validation email message to each user, with a URL link back to the Sites. This URL contains an alphanumeric identifier and a user-specific numeric passcode that allows us to confirm the user's identity. We may also obtain information from other sources and combine that with information we collect on our Sites. hi5 may store and process personally identifiable information in the United States and other countries.

Cookies and Passive Data Collection
hi5 logs standard user information and clickstream data for all users, including a user's IP address, operating system, and page views. When users visit particular pages within hi5, a UserID may be placed in the URL, allowing customized features for the user. Users should be aware that other websites visited before entering hi5 might place personally identifiable information within a user's URL during a visit to their website, and hi5 has no control over such websites. Accordingly, some of this information may be logged by a subsequent website that collects URL information. In addition to the standard log information, hi5 uses a variety of technologies to create a more personalized experience for its users. Cookies are small data files sent by websites to a user's browser and hard drive that identify the computer to the website. We use cookies to allow enhanced features, such as allowing registered users to bypass typing their passwords before entering the website. We may also use cookies to enable customizable content for users, as they become available. Users have the option, within their Internet browsers, to disable cookies and continue to access the hi5 website. Pixel tags are tiny graphic files that are included in HTML-encoded e-mail messages. We use pixel tags to gather information about the e-mails we send to our registered users. When such a message is opened in an HTML-capable e-mail program, the recipient's computer accesses our server to retrieve the pixel tag file, and allows us to record and store the date and time, the recipient's e-mail address, and other standard logging information. The pixel tag also may read cookies. hi5 web pages may also contain similar pixel tags that allow us to count users who have visited those pages, to compile aggregated statistics about site usage, and to deliver co-branded services as they become available. hi5 pixel tags collect only a limited set of information including a cookie number, time and date of a page view, and a description of the page on which the pixel tag resides. You can configure your Internet browser to warn you each time a cookie is being sent or to refuse cookies completely. However, unless you accept cookies, you will not have access to certain hi5 services. hi5 web pages may also contain pixel tags placed there by third party ad servers, to monitor the effectiveness of their advertising. We do not have access to, nor control over, advertisers' cookies or how they may be used. If you would like more information about advertisers' use of cookies, and about your option not to accept these cookies, please click here.

Other local storage. We, along with our partners and vendors, use other kinds of local storage, such as Local Shared Objects (also referred to as "Flash cookies") and HTML5 local storage, in connection with the hi5 services. Sometimes called "browser cookies," these technologies are similar to the cookies discussed above in that they are stored on your computers and can be used to store certain information about your activities and preferences. However, these objects are stored in different parts of your computer from ordinary browser cookies. Many Internet browsers allow you to disable HTML5 local storage or delete information contained in HTML5 local storage using browser controls. For information about disabling or deleting information contained in Local Shared Objects, please click here. Please note that disabling these technologies may interfere with the performance and features of hi5.

Web beacons. We, along with our partners and vendors, may also use technologies that communicate information from your Internet browser to a web server, including so-called "pixel tags," "web beacons," "clear GIFs," or similar means (collectively, "Pixel Tags"). Pixel Tags, which can be embedded in web pages, videos, or emails, can allow a web server to read certain types of information from your browser, check whether you have viewed a particular web page or email message, and determine, among other things, the time and date on which you viewed the Pixel Tag, the IP address of your computer, and the URL of the web page from which the Pixel Tag was viewed. We use Pixel Tags to improve your hi5 experience, including to provide you with content customized to your interests.

Document Retention Schedule
All personal information collected by hi5 in connection with your use of the Sites, including, without limitation, your name, location, email address, pictures, friend connections, messages, comments, login information, IP addresses and other data, will be stored only for as long as reasonably necessary for the purposes for which it was collected or to comply with any applicable legal reporting or documentation retention requirements.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>How hi5 Uses the User Information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Personally Identifiable Information
We use personal information collected through our Sites for purposes described in this Policy or disclosed to you on our Sites or in connection with our services, including the hi5 referral program and friend list building. Personally identifiable information including members' pictures and names are displayed to people in order to facilitate user interaction on hi5 and Tagged. Email addresses are used, among other purposes, to invite new friends to join hi5 and to add users to members' friends' networks. To facilitate searching and finding friends and acquaintances on the service, the Sites allow users to search for other members using first and last name, email address, location and schools where users may have attended. We also use email addresses to send useful information to all registered users regarding the Sites, including news about products and services offered by hi5, Tagged and our selected partners. For example, we provide users with an opportunity to send their friends invitations to join hi5. The user can send such invitations either by entering the email address of the referral or importing an address book and selecting the specific email addresses that they would like to invite. This results in an email being sent from that registered user to the referral address, encouraging the referral to sign up on the Sites. If the referred person does not sign up within a few days, we may also send periodic reminders from the registered user to the referral address. All registered users will be able to view other users' Stats, Profiles, Comments, photos, Feed updates, About Me, Tags, Videos, Groups, Questions, Gifts and friend list pages, which may include personal information. From time to time, hi5 may share the email address and/or other personally identifiable information of any registered user with third parties for marketing purposes, to target advertising and to improve user experience on hi5's pages in general. We may also link or combine with other personal information we get from third parties, to help understand your needs and provide you with better service.

Cookies and Passive Data Collection
hi5 uses cookie, IP address, clickstream and URL information to, among other purposes, improve the content of the Sites, the quality of hi5 servers, and to provide enhanced features to users, where available. We use cookies to save UserIDs, session validators, and on users' browsers and hard drives, and may use them to provide tailored products or services to those users, as they become available. We also cross-match user information with information collected from cookies and clickstream data in order to test features of the Sites, and to better personalize our various offerings for users. IP Addresses also help us to diagnose problems with our server, to administer the hi5 site, and to otherwise provide the hi5 service to its users. IP addresses may be disclosed to a third party if we believe in good faith that the law or legal process so requires, or to protect the rights or property of hi5 or others. From time to time we may extend various offers from various partner companies, including news or additional details on products and services. A user's usage history may result in specifically tailored special offer screens or products. We may also produce aggregate reports for advertisers. For example, we may report to advertisers the number of users who clicked on an ad, or the number of users that visited different portions of the Sites.

Profile Information
hi5 allows Members to provide information to a profile and other parts of the site that is accessible to other users. We use this profile information for the purposes of providing our services to you, such as to analyze demographics, to better personalize our various offerings for users, or to enable other users to find your profile. All information, including any personally identifiable information, which is disclosed by users in his or her public profile and other parts of the site are available for others to see on the Sites. Please do not post direct contact information in either your profile or other locations, such as your email addresses, URLs, instant messenger IDs, phone numbers, full names, or addresses. We also caution you not to share sensitive information (such as social security numbers, credit card numbers, and driver's license numbers) with other users whom you do not know or place such information in your profile. You are aware that when you publish content or information using the "everyone" setting, you are allowing everyone, including people off hi5 and Tagged, to access that information and to associate it with you.

Sharing Your Content and Information
hi5 allows Members to upload and share content and information. You own the content and information that you post on hi5 and have the ability to control how it is shared through your privacy settings.For content that is covered by intellectual property rights, including but not limited to photos, videos and written compositions ("IP Content"), you specifically give us the following permission: you grant us a non-exclusive, transferable, sublicensable, royalty-free, worldwide license to use any IP Content that you post on or in connection with hi5 and Tagged ("IP License"). For example, hi5 and Tagged may make commercial use and/or otherwise display your name and/or IP Content in or in connection with endorsements of and/or advertisements promoting hi5, Tagged and their services. This IP License ends when you delete your IP Content or your account, unless your IP Content has been shared with others, and they have not deleted the IP Content. When you delete IP Content it is removed from the Sites. However, you understand that we may maintain backup copies of the IP Content, as part of our document retention policy.

Invitations
The Invite Friends feature is an easy way for hi5 users to invite friends through email. The email address(es) that you supply to use this service may be used to send invitations, and in some cases invitation reminders, to connect with you on hi5.

Surveys and Contests
At various times we may offer surveys or contests to users. Surveys may ask for contact, demographic or unique identifying information to increase the value of the results. Contests may require contact information or other demographic or personally identifiable information in order to determine eligibility. hi5 may use information collected from surveys and contests for the entertainment of users, and to determine, notify and contact winners of various contests. In addition, users' demographic and/or personally identifiable information and responses to survey and contest questions may be used by hi5 and/or shared with third parties in order to provide specifically tailored special offers or advertisements. hi5 will not share a user's email address with third parties unless the user specifically opts-in to such sharing during the completion of or registration for a survey or contest.

Third Party Links and Ad Servers
Please be aware that links to third party websites and third-party ad server advertisements that are found on hi5 may, or may not, use cookies, pixel tags and web tags. hi5 may provide links to third party websites, which may, or may not, use cookies, pixel tags and web tags. Ad servers may also use these tools to compile information about where users saw particular advertisements, and to determine which ads were clicked on. We are not responsible for, or have any control over, the privacy policies of those third party websites and ad servers, and encourage all users to read the privacy policies of each and every website visited when linking directly from hi5.

Protection of hi5 and Others
hi5 may disclose personally identifiable information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process. hi5 may also disclose information about its users to law enforcement officers or others, in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to: enforce our Terms of Service; respond to claims that any posting or other content violates the rights of third-parties; respond to your requests for customer service; or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of hi5, Tagged, their users or the general public.

Security
hi5 uses industry standard security measures to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Although we make good faith efforts to store the information collected by the Sites in a secure operating environment that is not available to the public, we cannot guarantee complete security. Further, while we make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party "hackers" from illegally obtaining this information.

Updating or Removing User Information
As a registered user, you may, at any time, choose to correct or update the information you have submitted to us. This may be done by the following method:

Log in to your hi5 account on our Sites.
Click the "Account" link on the top right hand corner.
Change or edit any of the information there.
As a registered user, you may, at any time, cancel your account by following the instructions set forth here: http://help.hi5.com/t5/Account-Privacy-Settings/How-do-I-cancel-my-account/ta-p/133

Opt-Out
Users can manage their mailing preferences to specify which type of email to opt-out of on their Account Settings page when they are logged in, simply by un-checking the boxes under the Email Preferences section, indicating which type of email they would not like to receive. Canceling one's account will also prevent a user from receiving future communications from hi5, and hi5 will not share the user's information with third parties for marketing purposes. However, you may still receive a user generated invitation form your friends asking you to join hi5.

No Spam Policy
We at hi5.com are opposed to spam. Our No Spam Policy and Terms of Service prohibit all users from engaging in any activity involving spam on our service. Violations of these policies may result in immediate termination of service and legal action against any spammer. hi5's Terms of Service expressly prohibit users from uploading, posting, emailing, transmitting or otherwise making available junk mail, commercial advertisements, or other form of commercial solicitation on the Sites or through hi5's services. Any violation of our policies, by sending unsolicited email advertisements to or through hi5.com computer systems, will use or cause to be used hi5.com servers, located in California. Accordingly, any unauthorized use of hi5.com computer systems is a violation of our policies and certain federal and state laws, including the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act (18 U.S.C. sect 1030 et seq.), Section 502 of the California Penal Code and Section 17538.45 of the California Business and Professions Code. Such violations may subject the sender and his or her agents to civil and criminal penalties.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Other Disclosures</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Change of Ownership
In the event of a change in ownership, or a direct merger or acquisition with another entity, we reserve the right to transfer all of hi5's user information, including email addresses and postal addresses, to a separate entity. All registered users will be notified of any change in ownership, merger or acquisition of hi5's assets by a third party, and may choose to modify any of their registration information at that time.

Revisions to This Policy
hi5 reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this Policy from time to time. If we make any changes to this Policy, we will change the " Updated as of" date above.

Contacting hi5
Users with questions about this Policy and any of the aforementioned statements may contact hi5 by sending a letter to hi5 Inc., 110 Pacific Ave Mall, Box #117, San Francisco, CA 94111.

USE OF THIS SITE SIGNIFIES YOUR AGREEMENT TO THE PRIVACY POLICY.
Effective Date December 10, 2013.

Online Safety &gt;&gt;</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
