<POLICY modification_date="" policy_url="http://www.bounty.com/bmedia/privacy-statement" website_category="Health" website_index="087" website_url="bounty.com">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>Privacy Statement
The nature of our website (the “Site”) means that we will obtain, use and disclose (together “Use”) certain Personal Information (as defined below). We will comply with the requirements of the Data Protection Act 1998 in relation to any such Personal Information and will, within reason, ensure that your data is secure and monitored with regard to access, both internally and externally.

This statement sets out the principles governing our Use of your Personal Information on our Site. By using our website you agree to this Use.

1. When you use the services contained on our Site you will need to provide certain personal information such as your name and e-mail address (“Personal Information”). We will store this Personal Information and use it to provide you with information and otherwise for the normal use and improvement of our Site. If you would like to review or modify any part of your personal information then you should send an email to privacy@bounty.com.

2. We may transfer or disclose Personal Information if required to disclose such information by law. We may also transfer or disclose Personal Information to our professional advisers and to such other parties as we consider necessary in the administration of our Site and our related business.

3. Subject to you ticking certain boxes on the Site when prompted in order to provide your consent, we may transfer or disclose your Personal Information to other companies who may contact you with details of products or services which may interest you, but you can always tell us not to do this by contacting us as described in 12 below.

4. We may also use the Personal Information, and similar Personal Information you may provide us in response to any user surveys which you complete, to aggregate user profiles and, unless you opt out by contacting us as described in 12 below, to send you information about new products and services which we think may interest you.

5. Subject to you ticking certain boxes on the Site when prompted in order to provide your consent we may also pass your Personal Information to our business associates and affiliates (including those outside the European Economic Area) who may contact you with details of products or services which may interest you, but you can always tell us not to do this by contacting us as described in 12 below.

6. To enable us to monitor and improve our Site, we gather certain aggregated information about you when you use it, including details of your operating system, browser version, domain name and IP address, the URL you came from and go to and the parts of our Site you visit.

7. We may aggregate statistics, traffic patterns and related Site information and disclose such aggregate data to third parties for marketing, advertising or other promotional purposes but such aggregate data will not include any Personal Information.

8. A cookie is a small file, which is stored by our browser on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies only to store information such as your user ID and your session identifiers. We do not store other Personal Information such as passwords, preferences, etc. in cookie files.

9. You may submit notes, messages, bulletin boards postings, ideas, suggestions, concepts or other material (“Content”) to us for publication on the Site. All Content submitted by you to us must:

a. be legal, honest, decent and truthful and comply with all applicable laws, regulations, standards or codes of conduct;
b. not infringe the copyright, design, privacy, publicity, data protection, trade mark or any other rights of any third party, nor be obscene, abusive, threatening, libellous or defamatory of any person; and
c. not advertise or otherwise solicit for funds or is a solicitation for goods or services.

We have the right to monitor Content and may edit, reject or remove Content if we believe it does not comply with the above.

10. All Content submitted to us will become the property of Bounty throughout the world except any portion of the material that is Personal Information. You have sole responsibility for the Content which you submit to us for publication on the Site and you shall indemnify and shall keep us fully and effectively indemnified on demand from and against all actions, claims, losses, liability, proceedings, damages, costs, expenses, loss of business, loss of profits, business interruption and other pecuniary or consequential loss (including legal costs and expenses) suffered or incurred by us and arising directly or indirectly out of the publication of material submitted by you to us.

11. Whilst we will take all reasonable steps to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee the security of any Personal Information you disclose online. You accept the inherent security implications of providing information on-line over the internet and will not hold us responsible for any breach of security unless we have been negligent or in wilful default.

12. You can opt out of receiving various communications from us or our business associates, permit us to change Personal Information you have previously provided by emailing privacy@bounty.com ; You may ask us any further questions relating to our privacy policy by sending an email privacy@bounty.com.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
