<POLICY modification_date="" policy_url="http://www.hkjc.com/english/corporate/corp_privacy.asp" website_category="Sports" website_index="094" website_url="hkjc.com">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Personal Data ( Privacy ) Ordinance Notice</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Hong Kong Jockey Club and its subsidiaries (collectively referred to as "the Club"; each a "HKJC bodies") is committed to ensuring the confidentiality of personal information it holds and safety. To fulfill this commitment, we will implement the Hong Kong SAR Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance ("the Ordinance") principles and requirements. This Privacy Policy Statement is to explain this would protect the privacy practices.

The purpose of this Privacy Policy Statement, the Hong Kong Jockey Club's subsidiaries include, but are not limited to: HKJC Horse Race Betting Limited; HKJC Football Betting Limited; HKJC Lotteries Limited; Racing Club Limited. You can obtain further information on the Hong Kong Jockey Club, a subsidiary of the annual report or contact our Data Protection Privacy Officer Hong Kong Jockey Club.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Collection of Personal Data</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>"Personal Information" means any direct or indirect evidence of personal identity information. To handle the transaction will be between you, this will be the collection and use of personal information it considers necessary. The types of personal information collected may include, but clubs are not limited to, the following:


Contact information, such as your name, email address, mailing address, telephone number and fax number;
The unique identity verification information, such as your Hong Kong identity card number and passport number;
Billing information, such as your credit card number, bank account information and billing address;
Demographic information such as age, sex, nationality, marital status, preferences, educational background and employment history;
Jockey Club to provide personal information is not mandatory, but does not provide personal information may result in the Jockey Club can not process your application or provide facilities and services to you.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Use of Personal Data</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Your personal information is available for the following purposes: -

Provide the following services in respect of the Club facilities, services and support, or transactions:
The principal activities of the Club - horse racing, betting and Membership Services;
Racecourse, clubs, restaurants, hospitality and entertainment; and / or
Charitable or non-profit affairs including the arts, community service, conservation, culture, education, environmental protection, health care, music, recreation and sports ("charitable or non-profit affairs").
Apply for membership, horse ownership, eligibility audit facilities or services;
For publicity, marketing and customer management purposes, such as sending offers and promotional materials (see below "direct marketing") to you;
The principal activities of the Club in accordance with the relevant regulations or by-laws, as well as requiring disclosure of the information would be observed in accordance with the laws horse; and
Will facilitate communication with your horse.
This will also be used from time to time statistical information on the nature of the customer's non-recognition, to more effectively design and improve the facilities and services provided by the club. This information will not disclose any personal identity.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Direct Marketing</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Jockey Club intends to use your personal data for the Jockey Club Jockey Club or agency (or the Jockey Club Jockey Club institution or agent) for direct marketing purposes, for which the individual may provide your horse will be kept at the agency's personal data to Other agencies or the horse will be business partners for their direct marketing purposes. For the kinds of personal data to be used and the proposed sale of the species, see below. Only unless an exemption or the regulations will receive your consent, otherwise they would not be so used, and / or provide your personal information.

For the purposes of direct marketing above, the Club intends to:

Use your name, contact details and demographic information; and
Promotions and marketing arrangements provided below or by horse or horses will be institutional facilities, services, support and related projects and activities categories:
Horse racing, betting and Membership Services;
Racecourse, clubs, restaurants, hospitality and entertainment;
Horse and Jockey Club will be issued or associates of associates cards, smart cards, or stored value cards;
Charitable or non-profit business or project.
You may feel free to stop any use of your personal data for direct marketing purposes in any of the above. If so, you may contact the Privacy Officer Jockey Club data protection.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Disclosure of Personal Data</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Your personal information will be provided to the horse will be kept confidential. Provided that such information is available to provide services to the Jockey Club employees, agents, service providers and consultants to disclose (or they can be contacted or informed of such information), in order to help achieve the goal of collecting data involved. Your personal information will also be available to other horses agencies involved in order to help achieve the goal of collecting information (subject to any of the above "direct marketing" to agree to the request) and available to business partners of the Association for the above "direct Promotions "purposes. This will get you in the prescribed consent, or in the case of the law, your personal data will start for the other disclosures made.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Data Retention</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Unless the law specifically provides otherwise, when the purpose of the initial data collection is completed, this will take all reasonable and practicable steps to delete your personal data.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Data Security Commitment</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Ma is committed to protect the security of your personal information. This will be from the physical, technological and organizational three aspects to take various measures to help protect your personal data, prevent data access, processing, erasure or other use of unauthorized or accidental.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Change the privacy policy statement</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>If this will make any changes to the Privacy Policy in the future will be on our website www.hkjc.com make an announcement, so that you always know what the collected data may use such information, and whether this would be to any person to disclose such information.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Access to and Correction of Personal Data</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>You have the right to request access to the personal information about you to save the club, and request correction of such information. Under the Ordinance, we will deal with these may charge a reasonable fee upon request.

You can write to the following persons made the request:
Sports Road, Happy Valley, Hong Kong
Jockey Club Headquarters
Data Protection Privacy Officer
Jockey Club Headquarters
Data Protection Privacy Officer</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
