<POLICY modification_date="" policy_url="http://www.hdfcbank.com/aboutus/terms_conditions/privacy.htm" website_category="Business" website_index="024" website_url="hdfcbank.com">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Who is covered by this Policy</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>All visitors ("visitors") who visit the site http://www.hdfcbank.com and provide information to HDFC Bank online are covered under this Policy</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Information covered by this Policy</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>This Policy seeks to cover private information of the Visitors provided to HDFC Bank online as also any information collected by the bank server from the visitors browser. ("the Information")</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>The Features of the Policy</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>All Information collected shall only be used to provide the Visitor with the best possible services.
The Information shall not be shared with any external organisation unless the same is necessary to enable HDFC Bank to provide you services or to enable the compilation of a transaction, credit reporting, or the same is necessary or required pursuant to applicable banking norms or pursuant to the terms and conditions applicable to such Information as agreed to with HDFC Bank. Needless to add, confidentiality norms as applicable to banks shall be adhered to. HDFC Bank may also share Information to provide you with superior services and a range of offers.
HDFC Bank will use the Information to improve the visitor experience on the site and make subsequent offers to the visitor on products which may be of interest to him / her.
The HDFC Bank website uses cookies. Cookies are small data files that a website stores on your computer. We use persistent cookies which are permanently placed on your computer to store non-personal (Browser, ISP, OS, Clickstream information etc) and profiling information (age, gender, income etc). While cookies have unique identification nos, personal information (name, a/c no, contact nos etc) SHALL NOT be stored on the cookies.

We will use the information stored in the cookies to improve visitor experience through throwing up relevant content where possible. We will also use the cookies to store visitor preferences to ease visitor navigation on the site.

We may in the future implement encryption of the cookies.
HDFC Bank also may disclose information about you as permitted or required by law.
At HDFC Bank, we value your relationship and will at all times strive to ensure your privacy.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
