<POLICY modification_date="" policy_url="http://www.wine-searcher.com/privacy.lml" website_category="Recreation" website_index="074" website_url="wine-searcher.com">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>Wine-Searcher's Privacy Policy
Your security and privacy are important to us.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Payment Security</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>With Wine-Searcher's 'Pro Version' subscriptions, your credit card details are completely secure. During the authorization process your number is held in an encrypted form at all times, and it is removed from our server immediately after the process is complete. We do not store credit card numbers after payment.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Personal Details</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We take our site users' privacy very seriously and never pass details to third parties. All information is held in a secure form on our server.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Emails</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Email addresses collected for notifying wine availability are used solely for that purpose. We will not sell or share our site users' email addresses. We never spam.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Search History</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>All searches on the site are recorded and we summarize that information for generating statistics (such as our pages showing the top searches last month). Within the Pro Version you can access your own recent history of contacts with wine merchants.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Price Lists and other Merchant Data</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We use price data and merchant details for various additional services; including (but not limited to), calculating average prices, valuation services, "where to buy" links on third party websites via our wine widgets, and as data supplied to third party applications (typically mobile phone apps).</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Cookies</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We use cookies to improve usability (e.g. to remember which currency you prefer to use). If you use the Pro Version, cookies make that part of the site much easier to use.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Third party advertising</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Wine-Searcher is a participant in the Amazon Europe S.a r.l. Associates Programme, an affiliate advertising programme designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon.de, Amazon.fr and Amazon.it.

Also, we use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and would like to know your options in relation to not having this information used by these companies, click here.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Site Secured By</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Click for company profile

If you have any queries about our privacy conditions, please do not hesitate to ask.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
