<POLICY modification_date="March 10, 2006" policy_url="http://www.b92.net/eng/rules.html" website_category="Arts" website_index="088" website_url="b92.net">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>Using any part B92.net portal and all parts of the "RDP B92 Ltd." (hereinafter only B92.net), you automatically accept all current terms of use.
Users are required to read the rules of use, and is considered to visitors of the portal B92.net, or any part thereof, at any time to meet with the current rules, and that they understand them completely.
No part B92.net portal can be used for unlawful purposes or for promotion of the same.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>B92.net Portal</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Company "RDP B92 doo" visitors in good faith to use the contents B92.net portal. All visitors have the right to use the content B92.net portal, they do not violate copyright rules.
B92.net portal consists of its own content, content partners and advertisers, free content, and content created by visitors and links to external sites.
B92.net content is published in good faith. All contents B92.net Site at your own risk and B92.net can not be held liable for any damages resulting from the use.
Access B92.net website and all its contents is allowed to persons of any age.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Copyright</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>B92.net holds copyright on all its contents (textual, visual and audio materials, databases and programming code). Unauthorized use of any part of the portal is considered copyright infringement B92.net portal and is subject to prosecution.
Any commercial use or distribution without the permission of the copyright holder (B92.net, partners, customers ...) is considered a breach of copyright and subject to prosecution.
If you believe that B92.net violated your copyright, the case will be looked into immediately, and the material in question will be removed immediately after the eventual establishment factual.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Links to external sites</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>B92.net contains links to sites outside of our own website.
B92.net links published in good faith and can not be held responsible for the content of outside sites.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>External collaborators</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>B92.net protect user's privacy to the fullest extent possible. B92.net agrees that in good faith to use the data obtained from the users while using the portal, so that private information will not be distributed or sold to a third party without the permission of the user.
B92.net be in accordance with law to collect certain information about users received while using the Site (only information about your computer and the information on the Internet service provider) or data entered into the registration. These data B92.net used to have information about the users who use it, and thereby improve the portal and its contents further directed and adapted for the public to visit him. Based on these data, we find that the most popular activities among which the audience.
B92.net undertakes to private information, such as e-mail addresses, names, without the permission of each individual user to sell or distribute, in addition to demographic data for a group of users without revealing private information.
B92.net is committed to protecting the privacy of the users of the portal, except in cases of violation B92.net portal or illegal activities.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Send photos to the page of your photos</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Web site B92.net allows your visitors to submit their photos to konkuristi setup in the photo gallery "Your photos". This does not mean that all published photos that visitors submit only one that editorial B92 chooses. Due to the large number of photos you get on a daily basis and for different quality and current events, website B92 has a right not to publish photos without any additional explanation of reason for the failure. Please also send us subsequently mails with requests for explanation because physically we are not able to answer these types of questions.
Authors whose photographs have been published will be signed as they are sent in the form to send but will not be informed about setting up their photos.
Due to the inability to verify the authenticity of the website photos, Web site or the RDP B92 B92 AD can not be responsible for the veracity of author photos as well as due to any breach of copyright in photographs. Any liability for photos of the author photos or those who have posted. My photos are posted in good faith and with the assumption that those who sent photos and real authors.
In case you find a photo that you know is copyrighted, or the author signature is incorrect, please contact us at the address foto@b92.net to take the necessary steps to correct the error.
RDP B92 AD does not become the owner of the published images, but reserves the right to use the image in its other programs.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>YouTube</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>B92 publish video files that are located on servers YouTube.com.
Video files that are marked as "Related" are set automatically YouTube software that B92 does not and can not affect. Therefore B92 is not responsible for the content of the video files.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Modifying and changing rules</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>B92.net reserves the right without prior notice to change or modify these rules. About important changes and additions B92.net can notify users via email or publishing on the website.
Using any content on the website B92.net believes that you are familiar with the latest rules.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
