<POLICY modification_date="" policy_url="http://www.fcbarcelona.com/club/detail/card/legal-terms" website_category="Sports" website_index="074" website_url="fcbarcelona.com">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>PRIVACY POLICY. PROTECTION OF PERSONAL DATA

In accordance with Spanish Organic Law 15/1999, of December 13, in relation to the Protection of Data of a Personal Nature, data concerning the users that access the www.fcbarcelona.com, given their consent, will be included in an automated file that is the responsibility of FUTBOL CLUB BARCELONA, whose domicile is Avinguda Arístides Maillol s/n (08028) Barcelona.

Users can voluntarily decide whether or not to provide their consent for the data that they supply of their own free will to be included in the file that is the responsibility of FC BARCELONA, which is used to keep users informed, to offer them products and/or services both of FUTBOL CLUB BARCELONA itself and of other organizations that collaborate with the Club that, through agreement, may have some special offer that could be of interest to the members, supporters and internet users that have supplied their details. The user is also willing for FC BARCELONA to be able to provide his or her personal details to third party collaborators in order for these to be able to make offers and/or send communications to users for commercial or promotional purposes in relation to products or services that could be of interest to them.

If the user is not willing for his or her details to be included in any files and later used for informative and commercial purposes, he or she simply has to check the box denying authority to include said data in any files. Should any user provide this authority but later decide to revoke that authority or make any modifications to the data supplied, he or she must send an e-mail to oab@club.fcbarcelona.cat, or write to the address of the party responsible for the file indicated above. The user reserves the recognized right to access, cancel, rectify or oppose any of their details, and reserves the right to be told how many times these details have been supplied to others, if at all.

FC BARCELONA possesses the technical knowledge and means required for the processing of computer databases and the provision of certain services and possesses and employs the security measures required for proper data protection and security in accordance with the regulations established by Spanish Law 15/1999, on the Protection of Data of a Personal Nature.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
