<POLICY modification_date="June 10, 2010" policy_url="https://www.gsb.stanford.edu/privacy-policy" website_category="Reference" website_index="030" website_url="stanford.edu">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>Privacy Policy
Share on twitter Share on linkedin Share on facebook Share on google_plusone_share More Sharing Services
0
Stanford Graduate School of Business is committed to protecting your personal information and respecting your privacy. In general you can visit our website without telling us who you are or revealing information about yourself.

Some websites covered by this policy may request personal information from you in order to complete a form or transaction. Your information may be shared with third parties, such as event registration systems, to complete your transaction. Your information also may be collected by Stanford University and the Stanford Graduate School of Business for marketing and development. Stanford University and the Stanford Graduate School of Business will not sell any personal information to third parties for purposes of marketing, advertising, or promotion.

Stanford Graduate School of Business uses various methods to collect other kinds of information, including cookies, referrers, IP addresses, and system information.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Our Information Collection Practices</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Stanford Graduate School of Business uses website analytics tools to retrieve information from your browser, such as the site you came from, the search engine(s) and keywords you used to find our site, and the pages you view within our site. Additionally, we use technologies such as cookies and web beacons (described below), to collect information about the pages you view, the links you click, and other actions you take on our website. Lastly, we collect certain standard information that your browser sends to every website you visit such as your IP address, browser type and language, access times, and referring website addresses.

When you visit the Stanford Graduate School of Business website we gather and store this information to allow us to track the use of our website and make improvements. This information is stored and used in the aggregate only and is not used to obtain personal data or to contact you personally.

Some Stanford Graduate School of Business department sites use online data entry forms to collect personal information from web visitors who choose to identify themselves for the purpose of transacting e-commerce or receiving products, services, or information. Stanford GSB sites that collect data of any type are required to abide by and provide a link to our Privacy Statement. We request no more information than is required to fulfill the purpose for which the information is being collected.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Cookies and Web Beacons</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We use cookies, small snippets of data sent to your computer, to track usage patterns, traffic trends, and visitor behavior. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies. Choosing to accept cookies enables some online services to work more efficiently or makes the use of those services more convenient. You may set your browser to refuse cookies from any website that you visit. If you set your browser to refuse cookies, you may be unable to fully use certain portions of the website.

We may utilize web beacons, also known as clear GIFS, from third parties to help us compile aggregated statistics regarding the effectiveness of our site. Web beacons are used in combination with cookies to help understand how visitors interact with our site. We may include web beacons in promotional email messages or our newsletters in order to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon. We prohibit web beacons on our website from being used by third parties to collect or access personal information.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Referrers</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>A referrer is the information passed along by a web browser that references the web URL you linked from. Our web server automatically gathers this information.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>IP Addresses</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Web servers use your IP address to identify your computer so that data, such as the web pages you request, can be sent to you. Our web server automatically gathers them.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>System Information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>System information includes time, type of browser being used, the operating system or platform, and CPU speed. Your web browser sends this information automatically when you are connected to a website. This information is used by Stanford Graduate School of Business to identify broad demographic statistics and may be used to provide information appropriate for your computer system. Stanford Graduate School of Business will not use this information to attempt to identify your personal information.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Security</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>While no system can provide guaranteed security, we take reasonable efforts to keep information you provide to us secure, including encryption technology, and physical security at the location of the server where information is stored.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Links to Other Sites</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>The Stanford Graduate School of Business website includes hyperlinks to sites maintained or controlled by others. Stanford Graduate School of Business is not responsible for and does not routinely screen, approve, review, or endorse the contents of or use of any of the products or services that may be offered at this or any other website. We advise you to review the individual privacy policies of the respective sites.

Effective date: June 10, 2010</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
