<POLICY modification_date="" policy_url="http://www.nic.in/terms-use" website_category="Regional" website_index="047" website_url="nic.in">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>Disclaimer
This Portal is designed, developed and hosted by National Informatics Centre, Government of India.
Though all efforts have been made to ensure the accuracy and currency of the content on this Portal,the same should not be construed as a statement of law or used for any legal purposes. In no event will the Government or NIC be liable for any expense, loss or damage including, without limitation, indirect or consequential loss or damage, or any expense, loss or damage whatsoever arising from use, or loss of use, of data, arising out of or in connection with the use of this Portal.Links to other websites that have been included on this Portal are provided for public convenience only.
Material featured on this Portal may be reproduced free of charge after taking proper permission by sending a mail to us. However, the material has to be reproduced accurately and not to be used in a derogatory manner or in a misleading context. Wherever the material is being published or issued to others, the source must be prominently acknowledged. However, the permission to reproduce this material shall not extend to any material which is identified as being copyright of a third party. Authorisation to reproduce such material must be obtained from the departments/copyright holders concerned.
These terms and conditions shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the Indian Laws. Any dispute arising under these terms and conditions shall be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of India.
Privacy Policy
NIC Portal does not automatically capture any specific personal information from you, (like name, phone number or e-mail address), that allows us to identify you individually.
If the NIC Portal requests you to provide personal information, you will be informed for the particular purposes for which the information is gathered and adequate security measures will be taken to protect your personal information.
We do not sell or share any personally identifiable information volunteered on the India Portal site to any third party (public/private). Any information provided to this Portal will be protected from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

Hyperlinking Policy

Links to external websites/portals
We do not object to you linking directly to the information that is hosted on our site and no prior permission is required for the same. However, we would like you to inform us about any links provided to our site so that you can be informed of any changes or updations therein. Also, we do not permit our pages to be loaded into frames on your site. Our website's pages must load into a newly opened browser window of the user.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
