<POLICY modification_date="" policy_url="https://account.ankama.com/en/privacy-policy" website_category="Games" website_index="027" website_url="dofus.com">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>Article no. 1 : Privacy Policy - Ankama
By accessing or using the ANKAMA websites (collectively the " Website "), you acknowledge that you have read and accepted these rules concerning the use of personal data. If you disagree with these, you are asked not to access the Website.

In some sections of the Website, for the needs of a specific activity (contest, poll, etc.) or to purchase products or services, the ANKAMA company (the "Company") may ask you for certain personal details. The use of these services is optional and you are, therefore, not bound to provide any of these details. However, to purchase products and services or access certain sections of the Website you must provide it as precisely as possible.

ANKAMA will use the information in a responsible way, undertaking to make every effort to prevent its circulation. ANKAMA reserves the right to take legal proceedings against any person who attempts to access personal details that does not concern them.

The personal details you sent us may be shared with other ANKAMA subsidiaries in countries outside the European Union, particularly Brazil and Singapore.

ANKAMA may also share your personal details with third party service providers situated outside the European Union, particularly Canada and the USA.

These details are sent to recipients outside the European Union to build good customer relationships. ANKAMA has taken every necessary precaution to ensure that your personal details are sufficiently protected either under contractual clauses established by the European Commission, or because these transfers are carried out for an American company which complies with the Safe Harbor principles.

As a user, and in application of current legislation, you are the sole person authorised to access, modify and erase your personal details. You can exercise this right through the online technical support, https://support.ankama.com, or by post: Ankama - Personal Info, 75 bd d'Armentières, BP 60403, 59057 Roubaix cedex 1, FRANCE indicating your last name, first name, e-mail address and home address.

The Company may need to gather navigation information for statistical needs via the use of cookies. The acceptance of these cookies is compulsory for any subscription.

As regards external pages connected to the Website by a link pointing from these to the Website and vice versa, please note that ANKAMA shall not be responsible for their contents and their non-respect of this confidentiality policy.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
