<POLICY modification_date="" policy_url="http://companieshouse.gov.uk/legal/termsAndConditions.shtml#privacy" website_category="Society" website_index="084" website_url="companieshouse.gov.uk">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>Terms and Conditions

Show all
Disclaimer

The information available on this site is not intended to be comprehensive, and many details which may be relevant to particular circumstances have been omitted. Accordingly it should not be regarded as being a complete source of company law and information, and readers are advised to seek independent professional advice before acting on anything contained herein. Companies House cannot take any responsibility for the consequences of errors or omissions.

Notes for Users of Company Search or Disqualified Directors Search

The information available here is an extract from the Register of Companies / Register of Disqualified Directors which are updated on a regular basis. This may mean that occasional inaccuracies occur which we correct as soon as they are drawn to our attention. If you spot something which you think might be wrong, let us know so we can, if necessary, correct the database.

Company Information Supplied by Companies House

Companies House is a registry of company information. We carry out basic checks to make sure that documents have been fully completed and signed, but we do not have the statutory power or capability to verify the accuracy of the information that companies send to us. We accept all information that companies deliver to us in good faith and place it on the public record. The fact that the information has been placed on the public record should not be taken to indicate that Companies House has verified or validated it in any way.

When Companies House examines accounts it only makes basic checks on them, for example to ensure that the appropriate documents are there, that they are for the correct financial year and that they have been signed. If, subsequently, we receive a complaint that the accounts do not comply with the Companies Acts in some way we have a duty to draw this to the company's attention and, if appropriate, to ask for a set of revised accounts which do comply with the requirements.

Links to external websites

It is our policy to obtain permission to link to other websites. We are not responsible for the content or reliability of the linked websites. Listing should not be taken as endorsement of any kind. We cannot guarantee that these links will work all of the time and we have no control over the availability of linked pages.

Our cookie policy

When we provide services, we want to make them easy, useful and reliable. Where services are delivered on the internet, this sometimes involves placing small amounts of information on your device, for example, a computer or mobile phone. These include small files known as cookies. They cannot be used to identify you personally.

First-party cookies (cookies set by us)
Third-party cookies (cookies set by other sites through our pages)
How to control and delete cookies
What are cookies?

Cookies are small text files that websites save to your computer. The cookies used by government websites don't contain any of your personal information, and we can't use them to find out who you are.

These pieces of information are used to improve services for you through, for example:

remembering settings, so you don't have to keep re-entering them whenever you visit a new page
remembering information you've given (e.g. your postcode) so you don't need to keep entering it
measuring how you use the website so we can make sure it meets your needs
How we use cookies

The list below shows all of the cookies that are set by this website and the third-party services we use. If you have any queries about these cookies or would like more information about them, please get in touch.

First-party cookies (cookies set by us)

These are cookies set by this website. Some are necessary to the functionality of the site, others provide information to us that we analyse to monitor and improve the site. These first-party cookies do not store or collect any personal information or anything that makes you personally identifiable to us. Typically, the cookies generate a random, unique number to store information about a user.

If you have any further questions about our use of cookies please email us at enquiries@companies-house.gov.uk.

First-party cookies (cookies set by us)
Name of cookie	Type of cookie	Expiry period	Reason for use of cookie	Description
chcookie	Persistent cookie	2 months	Analytics	Used to improve our understanding of how people use our website and services, through web analytics
_pk_id.1.fc5d	Persistent cookie	2 years	Analytics	Used to improve our understanding of how people use our website and services, through web analytics
_pk_ses.1.fc5d	Session cookie	 	Analytics	Used to improve our understanding of how people use our website and services, through web analytics
ch_session	Session cookie	At end of session	Strictly necessary	Used to manage the items stored in your shopping basket or your progress through filing transactions
PIWIK_SESSID	Session cookie	 	Analytics	Used to improve our understanding of how people use our website and services, through web analytics
transaction	Persistent cookie	1 day	Your visit	WebFiling uses a cookie which remembers which service within WebFiling was being carried out in the event of a session timeout
chwebcheck	Persistent cookie	1 year	Your visit	WebCHeck uses a cookie which remembers the user for subsequent visits. The user is given the choice to explicitly allow this during login
ch_survey	Persistent cookie	1 year	Your visit	Companies House website occasionally runs surveys which use a cookie which remembers if the user has a) chosen to not take part in the survey, or b) has already taken part in the survey.
survey_ch	Persistent cookie	28 days	Your visit	Companies House website occasionally runs surveys which use a cookie which remembers if the user has a) chosen to not take part in the survey, or b) has already taken part in the survey.
chwebsite_survey	Persistent cookie	7 days	Your visit	Companies House website occasionally runs surveys which use a cookie which remembers if the user has a) chosen to not take part in the survey, or b) has already taken part in the survey.
Third-party cookies (cookies set by other websites through this site)

We want to provide interesting and engaging content on our website. On a number of pages we use 'plug ins' or embedded media. For example, we embed YouTube videos and Google Maps in many pages. The suppliers of these services may also set cookies on your device when you visit the pages where we have used this type of content. These are known as 'third-party' cookies.

Third-party cookies (cookies set by other websites through this site)
Name of cookie	Type of cookie	Expiry period	Reason for use of cookie	Description
NID	Persistent cookie	6 months	Media	This cookie is set by Google Maps when you visit any of our pages which includes an embedded Google Map
PREF	Persistent cookie	2 years	Media	This cookie is set by Google Maps when you visit any of our pages which includes an embedded Google Map
testcookie	Session cookie		Media	This cookie is set by Google Maps when you visit any of our pages which includes an embedded Google Map
khcookie	Session cookie		Media	This cookie is set by Google Maps when you visit any of our pages which includes an embedded Google Map
SNID	Persistent cookie	6 months	Media	This cookie is set by Google Maps when you visit any of our pages which includes an embedded Google Map
original_referer	Session cookie		Your visit	This cookie is set by Twitter when you load any of our pages that include a list of "Latest Tweets"
_twitter_sess	Session cookie		Social networking	This cookie is set by Twitter when you load any of our pages that include a list of "Latest Tweets"
guest_id	Persistent cookie	2 years	Social networking	This cookie is set by Twitter when you load any of our pages that include a list of "Latest Tweets"
k	Persistent cookie	1 week	Social networking	This cookie is set by Twitter when you load any of our pages that include a list of "Latest Tweets"
pid	Persistent cookie	2 years	Performance / Networking	This cookie is set by Twitter when you load any of our pages that include a list of "Latest Tweets"
PREF	Persistent cookie	10 years	Media	This cookie is set by YouTube when you load a video embedded on one of our pages
VISITOR_INFO1_LIVE	Persistent cookie	240 days	Media	This cookie is set by YouTube when you load a video embedded on one of our pages
use_hitbox	Session cookie		Media	This cookie is set by YouTube when you load a video embedded on one of our pages
Shopping cart / transactional areas
There are some areas of our site that make use of shopping carts or forms technology which at times have to make use of cookies - the ones used on a permanent basis are detailed in the cookies table. From time to time we may add functionality to our site e.g. surveys, comparisons etc., and these often come from 3rd parties – we will endeavour to ensure full disclosure of any cookies.

Areas of the site requiring a login
Accepting the use of login functionality, without exception, you must explicitly agree to the setting of specific cookies, which allow this area to function. The cookies in use for secure areas are provided within the terms and conditions of use for the appropriate area.

How to control and delete cookies

We will not use cookies to collect personally identifiable information about you. However, if you wish to restrict or block the cookies which are set by our websites, or indeed any other website, you can do this through your browser settings. The ‘Help' function within your browser should tell you how.

Alternatively, you may wish to visit the About Cookies website, which contains comprehensive information on how to do this on a wide variety of browsers. You will also find details on how to delete cookies from your machine as well as more general information about cookies.

Cookies: Frequently Asked Questions
How to control cookies
How to delete cookies
Please be aware that restricting cookies may have an impact upon the functionality of our website.

If you wish to view your cookie code, just click on a cookie to open it. You'll see a short string of text and numbers. The numbers are your identification card, which can only be seen by the server that gave you the cookie.

For information on how to do this on the browser of your mobile phone you will need to refer to your handset manual. To opt-out of third-parties collecting any data regarding your interaction on our website, please refer to their websites for further information.

Local Shared Objects (Flash cookies)
Some of our pages include videos embedded from YouTube, which uses the Adobe Flash Player. To improve user experience, Local Shared Objects - or Flash cookies as they are commonly known - are employed to provide features such as auto-resume and for saving your preferences. Flash cookies are stored on a user's terminal much the same as cookies are, however it is not possible to manage them at browser level in the same way. How to delete or disable Flash cookies

information collected behalf of HMRC
Companies House through the Joint Registration Service will act as agents for HMRC and provide an optional service whereby when a person registers a new company, a facility will be offered so that person can also register the company for Corporation Tax.  Once incorporation at Companies House has been accepted the Corporation Tax information will be sent to HMRC and will not be retained by Companies House.
Personal information
The Companies House Executive Agency website does not store or capture personal information, but merely logs the user's IP address (Internet Protocol: standard allowing data to be transmitted between two devices) which is automatically recognised by the web server.

If you register to receive updates, or order or purchase materials, your information will be held on a secure server and the data will not be shared with any organisations outside Government. It will be used only to provide you with any electronic products you have ordered, email updates on the topics you have requested, or postal information if you request that service. If you respond online to a consultation exercise your data will only be used to facilitate the analysis of responses.

This privacy statement only covers our website at www.companieshouse.gov.uk and sub-sites of this domain. This privacy statement does not cover other websites linked to from this domain.

Companies House Executive Agency may use information it holds to prevent and detect fraud. We may also share such information, for the same purpose, with other organisations that handle public funds.

If you have any queries please contact the Companies House Contact Centre on +44 (0)303 1234 500 or email
Acceptable use of companies House Researchable Databases

The Companies House searchable databases are designed to meet the needs of a wide range of users wishing to interrogate our information on-line.

Due to limitations of equipment and bandwidth, they are not intended to be a source for bulk downloads.

Individuals, companies, IP addresses or blocks of IP addresses who deny or degrade service to other users by generating unusually high numbers of daily database accesses, whether generated manually or in an automated fashion, may be denied access to these services without notice.

Companies House Mobile Application
Responsibility for network data charges
Analytics
Third-party components
Responsibility for network data charges

Companies House are not responsible for any costs incurred with your mobile operator and/or your ISP by downloading, installing and using the Application, including downloading any information that populates the Application.

Analytics

Companies House collects data about your use of the Application. The data is sent anonymously to Companies House where it is used to help improve the Application. The data allows us to gain insight into which features are used the most often, how frequently users launch the application and which versions are used. We generate a unique identifier (UID) that is used to uniquely identify your device. The UID is based on the device's network MAC address and each time the same device is used, the same UID is generated. This allows Companies House to count the number of unique devices that use the Application, or a specific function in the App, in a given period. It does not allow Companies House to identify the user of the device, but does allow Companies House to tell devices apart. The UID is NOT stored on the device, but it is generated each time the App is launched. If you do not want usage information to be recorded, then you may prevent the collection of data by turning off the analytics.

Third-party components

The Application for Apple uses the following third-party components:

MBProgressHUD v0.5
MIT License Copyright (c) 2011 Matej Bukovinski
https://github.com/jdg/MBProgressHUD
NoticeView
MIT License Copyright (c) 2012 Webbo, L.L.C. All rights reserved.
https://github.com/tciuro/NoticeView
NSString+MD5Addition, UIDevice+IdentifierAddition
MIT License Copyright (C) 2012, Georg Kitz, @gekitz
https://github.com/gekitz/UIDevice-with-UniqueIdentifier-for-iOS-5
SSTextView (part of SSToolkit)
MIT License Copyright (c) 2008-2012 Sam Soffes
https://github.com/samsoffes/sstoolkit
jQuery JavaScript Library v1.5.1 &amp; Sizzle.js
MIT License Copyright 2011, John Resig &amp; Copyright 2011, The Dojo Foundation
http://jquery.com/ &amp; http://sizzlejs.com
jQuery Flot Plugin v. 0.7 &amp; Multiple Plugin/Patch
MIT license Copyright IOLA, December 2007
http://code.google.com/p/flot/
http://code.google.com/p/flot/issues/detail?id=159
Moment.js v1.6.2
MIT license Copyright Tim Wood
http://momentjs.com/
The Application for Android uses the following third-party components:

jQuery Flot Plugin v. 0.7 &amp; Multiple Plugin/Patch
MIT license Copyright IOLA, December 2007
http://code.google.com/p/flot/
http://code.google.com/p/flot/issues/detail?id=159
Moment.js v1.6.2
MIT license Copyright Tim Wood
http://momentjs.com/
MapView Balloons project
https://github.com/jgilfelt/android-mapviewballoons
Apache Licence version 2 (http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0.html)
Joda Time project
MIT License Copyright (c) 2008-2012 Sam Soffes
http://joda-time.sourceforge.net
Apache Licence version 2 (http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0.html)</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
