<POLICY modification_date="" policy_url="https://irctc.co.in/beta_htmls/term.html" website_category="Regional" website_index="068" website_url="irctc.co.in">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>Privacy Policy

IRCTC respects and protects the privacy of the individuals who use IRCTC's services. Individually identifiable information about you is not willfully disclosed to any third party without first receiving your permission, as explained in this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy").

Cookies: Upon your first visit to www.irctc.co.in, we send a "cookie" to your computer. A cookie is apiece of data that identifies you as a unique user. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service and to understand our user base more. We do this by storing user preferences in cookie sand by tracking user trends and patterns of how people transact on our site. IRCTC will not disclose its cookies to third parties except as required by a valid legal process such as a search warrant or court order.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Be aware, however, that some parts of our services may not function properly if you refuse cookies.

What Information Do We Collect? : Except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information, we do not collect any unique information about you (such as your name, email address, etc.). IRCTC notes and saves information such as time of day, browser type, browser language, and IP address with each query. This information is used to verify our records and to provide more relevant services to users.

Links to Other Sites: people over whom IRCTC exercises no control develop the sites linked to www.irctc.co.in. Other parties, such as those advertising on our pages or those advertising thorough our envelopes carrying tickets are also in no way under the control or influence of IRCTC. These other sites /parties may send their own cookies / messages to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. Our users may give such information or data only at their personal discretion.

With Whom Does IRCTC Share Information? : IRCTC will not share your personal data with advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties without your express consent. However, we may divulge aggregate information about our users. For example, we may disclose how frequently the average user visits www.irctc.co.in, or the age distribution of our aggregate customer set or the frequency of use of PNR enquiry page etc. etc. Please be aware, however, that we will release specific personal information about you if required to do so in order to comply with any valid legal process such as a search warrant, court order etc.

Your consent and changes to the Privacy Policy By using the www.irctc.co.in, you consent to the collection and use of your information as we have outlined in this policy and to our Terms &amp; Conditions. IRCTC may decide to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

Who can I ask if I have additional questions? :Do contact us at 24X7 Hrs. Customer Support at 011-39340000 . Our email address is care@irctc.co.in</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
