<POLICY modification_date="February 09, 2009" policy_url="http://metatalk.metafilter.com/17338/Does-MeFi-have-a-privacy-policy" website_category="News" website_index="094" website_url="metafilter.com">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Why doesn't Metafilter have a privacy policy?</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>The MetaFilter Network LLC is an Oregon-based company, which collects a one time membership fee from registered users, and makes enough money from advertising to support a few awesome admins, and pay for shiny new servers. Metafilter is a fairly high traffic site, and receives 11.5 million pageviews from 3.5 million unique users every month.

MetaFilter would thus seem to meet any reasonble definition of a commercial website.

California's Online Privacy Protection Act (OPPA) requires that all commercial websites that collect "personally identifiable information" on users who reside in California must have a conspicuous privacy policy on their web sites – even if that company is based outside California, including overseas.

This law went into effect in 2004, and as a result, practically every corporate website in the world now has a "privacy policy" link on the bottom of the front page, which leads to a document explaining what kind of information the website collects.

There is probably at least one Metafilter user in California, and thus, it seems reasonable to assume that Metafilter is collecting personally identifiable data on California residents.

Furthermore, a recent comment by Cortex seemed to imply that Metafilter is logging the identity of users who author anonymous posts.

After seeing Cortex's comment, I tried to find more information about the extent to which Metafilter is logging on my activity with the website, but I couldn't find anything. There certainly isn't a privacy policy linked from the front page, and 10 mins of googling didn't come up with anything.

So.. my two part question is this: Why doesn't Metafilter have a privacy policy, and if one does exist, why isn't there a prominent link to it on the front page as required by California law.

(I'm not a lawyer, but I am a privacy geek)
posted by genome4hire to Etiquette/Policy at 1:41 AM (275 comments total) 6 users marked this as a favorite</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
