<POLICY modification_date="" policy_url="http://www.sutterhealth.org/policy/" website_category="Health" website_index="086" website_url="sutterhealth.org">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>Privacy and Disclosure Statements</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Our Web Site and Your Privacy</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We make the following assurances of privacy for visitors to our Web site:

The Sutter Health Web site is designed to provide useful information about our organization and to connect users with physicians, facilities, services and employment opportunities within Sutter Health.

Our Web site does not promote or sell products of any kind. We do hope that the information provided encourages the visitor to consider using the Sutter Health network for medical care, or that visitors might decide to join our organization as an employee, volunteer or donor.

We keep track of visits to our Web site via an automatic monitoring program that tells us, among other things, how many visits are made to the site; the time of day and date of those visits; and the areas visited. This information is used to evaluate the effectiveness of our site and the effectiveness of any promotion of our site. It helps us answer questions such as these: Are we providing information on our Web site that is useful? Which information is most useful? How have we made you aware that our Web site exists?

The monitoring program does not provide us with any personal information about a visitor. We cannot discern the name, address or any other personal information about visitors to our site.

If we wish to gather such personal information, it will be requested via a form on the site that the user voluntarily completes and submits. The form will describe the way in which the information will be used.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Who Funds Our Web Site</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>The Sutter Health Web site is funded entirely by the operating income of the Sutter Health network. Please visit the About Sutter Health section to learn more about our status as a non-profit health care organization.

We accept no outside funding for the creation or maintenance of our Web site, nor do we accept advertising income in exchange for promotion of any product or service via our Web site.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Who Oversees Our Web Site</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>The information on our Web site is managed by the Sutter Health Communications and Marketing Department, in the Sutter Health home office in Sacramento. Questions, concerns or suggestions can be directed to:

Webmaster@sutterhealth.org

Comments or questions will be routed to the appropriate individual within the organization. You can also contact us via U.S. mail at:

Sutter Health
Communications Department
2200 River Plaza Drive
Sacramento, CA 95833</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Our Health Information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>All health-related information provided via our site is intended to educate and inform visitors about illnesses and conditions and ways to maintain optimum health. It is not intended to diagnose personal physical conditions and is not a substitute for consulting with one's own personal health care provider. By viewing our Web site health information, you are agreeing to the following terms and conditions.

Our health-related information is derived from three sources:

Our Sutter aligned physicians and medical experts — Information posted on the site, such as our preventive health guidelines, have been reviewed and approved by clinical leadership groups within the Sutter Health network.
2. Our affiliation with HealthWise — The bulk of our health information and education material is provided by HealthWise. You can learn more about the HealthWise Knowledgebase by visiting their web site, www.healthwise.org
Our affiliation with MedlinePlus - Sutter Health's Web site contains third-party health information and educational material provided by MedlinePlus. To learn more about the MedlinePlus public service, please read their Quality Guidelines, Disclaimers and Privacy Policy.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Our Physician Referral Feature</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Our physician referral feature is intended to help visitors to our Web site learn about physicians who are on the active medical staffs of Sutter-aligned hospitals, or who are members of Sutter-affiliated medical groups. The information on each physician in our referral feature is provided by that physician, via the records maintained by the hospital medical staff or the medical group. The information is updated on a regular basis. For more details, the Web visitor is encouraged to call the individual physician's office at the number provided on the Web site.
Find a Sutter Health doctor</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Our Job Search Feature</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Our job search feature is intended to help connect Web site visitors with employment opportunities at the various Sutter-affiliated organizations. The information on current job openings is provided by each Sutter-affiliated organization and is updated on a regular basis. Each Sutter-affiliated hospital, physician group or service is a separate business and therefore a separate employer, with its own employment policies, wage and salary scale and benefit package. Details of employment with a Sutter affiliate is best determined by contacting that facility.
Jobs at Sutter Health</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
