<POLICY modification_date="January 01, 2011" policy_url="https://www.usaa.com/inet/pages/privacy_promise?wa_ref=pub_subglobal_footer_privacy_promise" website_category="Business" website_index="088" website_url="usaa.com">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>USAA Privacy PromiseReach a Representative
Print | Revised Jan. 2011</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>What does USAA do with your personal information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Why?	Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some, but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What?	The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:
Social Security number and income.
Account balances and account transactions.
Credit history and insurance claim history.
How?	All financial companies need to share customers' personal information to run their everyday business as permitted by law. For example, we share with print and mail companies that assist us in sending mail. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers' personal information, the reasons USAA chooses to share and whether you can limit this sharing.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Reasons we can share your personal information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Does USAA share?	Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes —
such as to process your transactions, maintain your accounts, respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus	Yes	No
For our marketing purposes —
to offer products and services provided or endorsed by USAA	Yes	No
For joint marketing —
sharing with other financial companies to jointly market the other company's products or services	No	We do not share
For everyday business purposes of the USAA family of companies —
this can include information about your USAA transactions and experiences	Yes	No
For everyday business purposes of the USAA family of companies —
this can include information about your creditworthiness or insurability	Yes	Yes*
For non-USAA companies to market to you	No	We do not share
To limit our sharing
Visit us online: usaa.com/optout, or
Call 1-800-531-7154 — our menu will prompt you through your choices.
You can contact us at any time to limit our sharing. When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share and protect your information as described in this notice.

*Please note: If you are a new customer, we can begin sharing this information among the USAA family of companies 30 days from the date we provided this notice.
Questions?	Call 1-800-531-7154 and ask to speak to a representative.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Who we are</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Who is providing this notice?	United Services Automobile Association (USAA) and its family of companies, including companies identified with the USAA name and logo and Garrison Property and Casualty Insurance Company.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>What we do</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>How does USAA protect my personal information?	To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal laws. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
How does USAA collect my personal information?	We collect your personal information, for example, when you:
Open an account, or deposit money.
Pay your bills, or apply for a loan or insurance.
Use your credit or debit card, or direct us to sell securities.
We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates or other companies.
Why can't I limit all sharing?	Federal laws give you the right to limit only:
Sharing among affiliated companies for everyday business purposes — information about your creditworthiness and insurability.
Affiliates from using your information to market to you.
Sharing for non-affiliates to market to you.
What happens when I limit sharing for an account I hold jointly with someone else?	Your choices will apply to everyone on your account.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Definitions</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>USAA family of companies (affiliates)	Companies owned or controlled by USAA. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies in the USAA family of companies.

The USAA family of companies include: companies with a USAA name; financial companies, such as USAA Savings Bank and Garrison Property and Casualty Insurance Company; and non-financial companies, such as USAA Alliance Services Company and USAA Educational Foundation.
Non-USAA companies (nonaffiliates)	Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.

USAA does not share with non-USAA companies so they can market their products to you.
Joint marketing	A formal agreement between a USAA company and a non-USAA financial company to market the non-USAA company's products or services to you.
We need to share with print and mail companies to send these communications.
We only share with non-USAA financial companies to service transactions you request.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Other important information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Depending on where you live and what products you own, you may receive another privacy notice that describes additional rights.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Your Choice to Limit USAA Marketing</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Who is providing this notice	The USAA family of companies is providing this notice. This includes USAA companies that provide insurance, banking, investments, financial planning and member services.
Your right to limit marketing	Federal law gives you the right to limit some, but not all, marketing from USAA and requires us to give you this notice. If you limit marketing you will continue to receive:
A response when you contact us about a product.
Communication from the companies you do business with.
Communication sent to the general public, or to all members.
Information used for marketing	You may limit companies in the USAA family from marketing their products or services to you based on your personal information they receive from other USAA companies. This information may include your:
Income
Account transactions or insurance transactions
Credit history or driving history
The information used will vary, depending on the product marketed.
Renewal of your choice	Your choice to limit marketing offers from the USAA companies will apply for at least 5 years.

Before your choice expires, you will receive a renewal notice allowing you to continue to limit marketing offers from the USAA companies for another 5 years.
Opting out	To limit marketing offers:
Visit us online at usaa.com/optout, or
Call 1-800-531-7154 — our menu will prompt you through your choices.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
