<POLICY modification_date="December 10, 2013" policy_url="http://www.tagged.com/terms_of_service.html?#privacy_policy" website_category="Computers" website_index="084" website_url="tagged.com">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>Updated as of December 10, 2013</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>User Privacy</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Tagged is a social discovery website that lets you meet and interact with new people and stay in touch with friends. Like any website that offers a service where you register and provide information about yourself or your opinions, it is wise to pay attention to your personal information. At Tagged we understand this, and have established this Privacy Policy to explain how information is collected on our website, and how this information is used. Members Must Be 18 years of age or older. Tagged is intended solely for use by persons 18 years of age or older. All persons under 18 are prohibited from registering on Tagged.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>How Does Tagged Protect Children's Privacy</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>The safety and privacy of children is extremely important to us.

Tagged is a general audience web site that complies with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). Our registration process is designed to restrict children under the age of 13 from becoming members of Tagged and using our site. If we receive information suggesting that a user who has registered with Tagged is under the age of 13, we require the user to provide evidence confirming that the user is at least 13 years old. If the user fails to provide such information within 48 hours, we immediately terminate the user's account and nullify all personally identifiable information displaying on the site.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>What Is the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) requires that commercial web sites obtain parental consent (under most circumstances) prior to the collection of any personally identifiable information from children whom they know to be under the age of 13. In addition, COPPA requires that web sites that collect personal information from children under the age of 13 provide parents with:

Notice. Parents must be provided notice regarding what information is collected, how the information will be used, and with whom the information may be shared.
The ability to prevent further use of the information collected about the child and prevent any future collection of personal information from the child.
The ability to access and review their child's personal information.

COPPA also limits the amount of personal information a web site can collect from a child. Web sites may not collect any more personal information than is necessary to participate in a given game or activity.

For more information about COPPA, please visit the Federal Trade Commission's web site.

Parents: If your child is under the age of 13 and has joined Tagged using a false age, please notify Tagged at parentcare@tagged.com, and we will immediately cancel your child's account and nullify all personally identifiable information displaying on the site. If you would like to know more about our site, information practices, stored information about your child, or how to close your child's account, please contact Tagged by sending a letter to Tagged.com, 110 Pacific Ave Mall, Box #117, San Francisco, CA 94111 or by submitting a request at help.tagged.com. We will happily respond to all letters from parents with Privacy questions or concerns.
User Information Collected by Tagged</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Personally Identifiable User Information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>All users begin using Tagged's services by registering on the Tagged website. When registering, users provide personally identifiable information, which includes their first and last name, email address, zip code, a user-chosen password, and date of birth, and other personal information. To complete the registration process, Tagged sends a validation email message to each user, with a URL link back to our website. This URL contains an alphanumeric identifier and a user-specific numeric passcode that allows us to confirm the user's identity.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Cookies and Passive Data Collection</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Tagged logs standard user information and clickstream data for all users, including a user's IP address, operating system, and page views. When users visit particular pages within Tagged, a UserID may be placed in the URL, allowing customized features for the user. Users should be aware that other websites visited before entering Tagged might place personally identifiable information within a user's URL during a visit to their website, and Tagged has no control over such websites. Accordingly, some of this information may be logged by a subsequent website that collects URL information. In addition to the standard log information, Tagged uses a variety of technologies to create a more personalized experience for its users. Cookies are small data files sent by websites to a user's browser and hard drive that identify the computer to the website. We use cookies to allow enhanced features, such as allowing registered users to bypass typing their passwords before entering the website. We may also use cookies to enable customizable content for users, as they become available. Users have the option, within their Internet browsers, to disable cookies and continue to access the Tagged website. Pixel tags are tiny graphic files that are included in HTML-encoded e-mail messages. We use pixel tags to gather information about the e-mails we send to our registered users. When such a message is opened in an HTML-capable e-mail program, the recipient's computer accesses our server to retrieve the pixel tag file, and allows us to record and store the date and time, the recipient's e-mail address, and other standard logging information. The pixel tag also may read cookies. Tagged web pages may also contain similar pixel tags that allow us to count users who have visited those pages, to compile aggregated statistics about site usage, and to deliver co-branded services as they become available. Tagged pixel tags collect only a limited set of information including a cookie number, time and date of a page view, and a description of the page on which the pixel tag resides. You can configure your Internet browser to warn you each time a cookie is being sent or to refuse cookies completely. However, unless you accept cookies, you will not have access to certain Tagged services. Tagged web pages may also contain pixel tags placed there by third party ad servers, to monitor the effectiveness of their advertising. We do not have access to, nor control over, advertisers' cookies or how they may be used. If you would like more information about advertisers' use of cookies, and about your option not to accept these cookies, please click here.

Other local storage. We, along with our partners and vendors, use other kinds of local storage, such as Local Shared Objects (also referred to as "Flash cookies") and HTML5 local storage, in connection with the Tagged services. Sometimes called "browser cookies," these technologies are similar to the cookies discussed above in that they are stored on your computers and can be used to store certain information about your activities and preferences. However, these objects are stored in different parts of your computer from ordinary browser cookies. Many Internet browsers allow you to disable HTML5 local storage or delete information contained in HTML5 local storage using browser controls. For information about disabling or deleting information contained in Local Shared Objects, please click here. Please note that disabling these technologies may interfere with the performance and features of Tagged.

Web beacons. We, along with our partners and vendors, may also use technologies that communicate information from your Internet browser to a web server, including so-called "pixel tags," "web beacons," "clear GIFs," or similar means (collectively, "Pixel Tags"). Pixel Tags, which can be embedded in web pages, videos, or emails, can allow a web server to read certain types of information from your browser, check whether you have viewed a particular web page or email message, and determine, among other things, the time and date on which you viewed the Pixel Tag, the IP address of your computer, and the URL of the web page from which the Pixel Tag was viewed. We use Pixel Tags to improve your Tagged experience, including to provide you with content customized to your interests.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Document Retention Schedule</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>All personal information collected by Tagged in connection with your use of the Tagged website, including, without limitation, your name, location, email address, pictures, friend connections, messages, comments, login information, ip addresses and other data, will be stored by Tagged indefinitely in a safe and secure manner.
How Tagged Uses the User Information</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Personally Identifiable Information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Tagged uses personally identifiable user information for the purposes of the Tagged website, the Tagged referral and friend list building. Personally identifiable information including members' pictures and names are displayed to people in order to facilitate user interaction on Tagged. Email addresses are used for the purposes of inviting new friends to join Tagged and to add users to members' friends' networks. To facilitate searching and finding friends and acquaintances on the service, Tagged allows users to search for other members using first and last name, email address, location and schools where users may have attended. We also use email addresses to send useful information to all registered users regarding the Tagged website. For example, we provide users with an opportunity to send their friends invitations to join Tagged. The user can send such invitations either by entering the email address of the referral or importing an address book and selecting the specific email addresses that they would like to invite. This results in an email being sent from that registered user to the referral address, encouraging the referral to sign up on the Tagged website. If the referred person does not sign up within a few days, we may also send a reminder from the registered user to the referral address. All registered users will be able to view other users Stats, Profiles, Public Journals and friend list pages, which may include personal information and responses to survey questions. From time to time, Tagged may share the email address and/or other personally identifiable information of any registered user with third parties for marketing purposes. In addition, Tagged may share a registered user's email address with third parties to target advertising and to improve user experience on Tagged's pages in general.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Cookies and Passive Data Collection</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Tagged uses cookie, IP address, clickstream and URL information to improve the content of the Tagged website, the quality of Tagged servers, and to provide enhanced features to users, where available. We use cookies to save UserIDs, session validators, and on users' browsers and hard drives, and may use them to provide tailored products or services to those users, as they become available. We also cross-match user information with information collected from cookies and clickstream data in order to test features of the Tagged website, and to better personalize our various offerings for users. IP Addresses also help us to diagnose problems with our server, to administer the Tagged site, and to otherwise provide the Tagged service to its users. IP addresses may be disclosed to a third party if we believe in good faith that the law or legal process so requires, or to protect the rights or property of Tagged or others. From time to time we may extend various offers from various partner companies, including news or additional details on products and services. A user's usage history may result in specifically tailored special offer screens or products. We may also produce aggregate reports for advertisers. For example, we may report to advertisers the number of users who clicked on an ad, or the number of users that visited different portions of the Tagged website. This information will not include personally identifiable information about a user, or a specific user's online usage patterns.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Profile Information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Tagged allows Members to provide information to a profile and/or journal entries that is accessible to other users. We use this profile information for the purposes of providing our services to you, such as to analyze demographics, to better personalize our various offerings for users, or to enable other users to find your profile. All information, including any personally identifiable information, which is disclosed by users in his or her public profile and journal entries are available for others to see. Please do not post direct contact information in either your profile or your journal, such as your email addresses, URLs, instant messenger IDs, phone numbers, full names, or addresses. We also caution you not to share sensitive information (such as social security numbers, credit card numbers, and driver's license numbers) with other users whom you do not know or place such information in your profile. You are aware that when you publish content or information using the "everyone" setting, you are allowing everyone, including people off Tagged, to access that information and to associate it with you.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Sharing Your Content and Information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Tagged allows Members to upload and share content and information. You own the content and information that you post on Tagged and have the ability to control how it is shared through your privacy settings. For content that is covered by intellectual property rights, including but not limited to photos, videos and written compositions (IP Content), you specifically give us the following permission: you grant us a non-exclusive, transferable, sublicensable, royalty-free, worldwide license to use any IP content that you post on or in connection with Tagged ("IP License"). For example, Tagged may make commercial use and/or otherwise display your name and/or IP Content in or in connection with endorsements of and/or advertisements promoting Tagged and its Services. This IP License ends when you delete your IP content or your account, unless your content has been shared with others, and they have not deleted the content. When you delete IP content it is removed from the website. However, you understand that we may maintain backup copies of the content, as part of our document retention policy.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Invitations</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>The Invite Friends feature is an easy way for Tagged users to invite friends through email. The email address(es) that you supply to use this service will only be used to send invitations, and in some cases invitation reminders, to connect with you on Tagged.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Surveys and Contests</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>At various times we may offer surveys or contests to users. Surveys may ask for contact, demographic or unique identifying information to increase the value of the results. Contests may require contact information or other demographic or personally identifiable information in order to determine eligibility. Tagged may use information collected from surveys and contests for the entertainment of users, and to determine, notify and contact winners of various contests. In addition, users' demographic and/or personally identifiable information and responses to survey and contest questions may be used by Tagged and/or shared with third parties in order to provide specifically tailored special offers or advertisements. Tagged will not share a user's email address with third parties unless the user specifically opts-in to such sharing during the completion of or registration for a survey or contest.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Third Party Links and Ad Servers</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Please be aware that links to third party websites and third-party ad server advertisements that are found on Tagged may, or may not, use cookies, pixel tags and web tags. Tagged may provide links to third party websites, which may, or may not, use cookies, pixel tags and web tags. Ad servers may also use these tools to compile information about where users saw particular advertisements, and to determine which ads were clicked on. We are not responsible for, or have any control over, the privacy policies of those third party websites and ad servers, and encourage all users to read the privacy policies of each and every website visited when linking directly from Tagged.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Protection of Tagged and Others</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Tagged may disclose personally identifiable user information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process. Tagged may also disclose information about its users to law enforcement officers or others, in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to: enforce our Terms of Service; respond to claims that any posting or other content violates the rights of third-parties; respond to your requests for customer service; or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Tagged, its users or the general public.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Security</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Tagged uses industry standard security measures to prevent the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Although we make good faith efforts to store the information collected by the Tagged website in a secure operating environment that is not available to the public, we cannot guarantee complete security. Further, while we make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party "hackers" from illegally obtaining this information.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Updating or Removing User Information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>As a registered user, you may, at any time, choose to correct or update the information you have submitted to us. This may be done by the following method:

Log in to your Tagged account on our website.
Click the "Account" link on the top right hand corner.
Change or edit any of the information there.

As a registered user, you may, at any time, cancel your account by following the instructions set forth here: http://help.tagged.com/t5/Account-Privacy-Settings/How-do-I-cancel-my-account/ta-p/133</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Opt-Out</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Users can manage their mailing preferences to specify which type of email to opt out of on their Account Settings page when they are logged in, simply by un-checking the boxes under the Email Preferences section, indicating which type of email they would not like to receive. Canceling one's account will also prevent a user from receiving future communications from Tagged, and Tagged will not share the user's information with third parties for marketing purposes. However, you may still receive a user generated invitation from your friends asking you to join Tagged.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>No Spam Policy</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We at Tagged.com are opposed to spam. Our No Spam Policy and Terms of Service prohibit all users from engaging in any activity involving spam on our service. Violations of these policies may result in immediate termination of service and legal action against any spammer. Tagged's Terms of Service expressly prohibit users from uploading, posting, emailing, transmitting or otherwise making available junk mail, commercial advertisements, or other form of commercial solicitation on the Tagged website or through Tagged's services. Any violation of our policies, by sending unsolicited email advertisements to or through Tagged.com computer systems, will use or cause to be used Tagged.com servers, located in California. Accordingly, any unauthorized use of Tagged.com computer systems is a violation of our policies and certain federal and state laws, including the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act (18 U.S.C. sect 1030 et seq.), Section 502 of the California Penal Code and Section 17538.45 of the California Business and Professions Code. Such violations may subject the sender and his or her agents to civil and criminal penalties.
Other Disclosures</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Change of Ownership</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>In the event of a change in ownership, or a direct merger or acquisition with another entity, we reserve the right to transfer all of Tagged's user information, including email addresses and postal addresses, to a separate entity. All registered users will be notified of any change in ownership, merger or acquisition of Tagged's assets by a third party, and may choose to modify any of their registration information at that time.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Revisions to This Policy</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Tagged reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy and our other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner. Notice of any revision, amendment, or modification will be posted on the website, and a user's continued use of Tagged will signify agreement to such changes.
Contacting Tagged

Users with questions about this Privacy Policy and any of the aforementioned statements may contact Tagged by sending a letter to Tagged.com, 110 Pacific Ave Mall, Box #117, San Francisco, CA 94111 or by submitting a request at help.tagged.com.

USE OF THIS SITE SIGNIFIES YOUR AGREEMENT TO THE PRIVACY POLICY.
Effective Date December 10, 2013.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
