<POLICY modification_date="" policy_url="http://www.manutd.com/en/General-Footer-Section/Privacy-Policy.aspx" website_category="Kids_and_Teens" website_index="060" website_url="manutd.com">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>About us</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Manchester United is a group of companies which includes Manchester United Limited, Manchester United Football Club Ltd and Manchester United Interactive Ltd (together "MU", "we" and "us"). For a full list of companies in the Manchester United Group please click here.

MU takes the privacy of all its fans, customers and website users very seriously and takes great care to protect your information.

This privacy policy explains what information we collect about you, how we may use it, and the steps we take to ensure that it is kept secure. We also explain your rights and how to contact us.

Please note, this website contains links to other websites which are provided for your convenience. We are only responsible for the privacy practices and security of this site. We recommend that you check the privacy and security policies and procedures of each and every other website that you visit.

By using this website and giving your information to us, you indicate your consent to us and our commercial partners collecting and using your personal information in accordance with the terms set out in this policy.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>What information do we collect</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>In order to provide you with services, we may collect personal information about you from our website, telephone conversations, emails and written and verbal communications. We may, for example, keep a record of your name, address, delivery address, email address, telephone number and credit card details. We may also record details of any disability or health needs you may have at the time of booking an event or service which will take place at the stadium or any of our other premises to help to ensure your safety.

We may supplement the information that you provide with other information that we obtain from our dealings with you or which we receive from other organisations, for example, our commercial partners.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>How will we use your information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>All personal information that we obtain about you will be recorded, used, and protected by us in accordance with current data protection legislation and this privacy policy. We will primarily use your personal information to provide our products and services to you and, for example:

- to administer and provide products and services you request
- to communicate with you in the event that any products or services you have requested are unavailable
- for fraud screening and prevention purposes (see below for further details)
- for record keeping purposes
- to carry out market research so that we can improve the products and services we offer
- to track activity on our website
- to create an individual profile for you so that we can understand and respect your preferences and to calculate the level of any loyalty reward due to you</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Disclosure of your information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>In order to provide our products and services to you, we may need to appoint other organisations to carry out some of the processing activities on our behalf. These will include, for example, delivery organisations, fraud screening companies (see below) and mailing houses. In these circumstances, we will ensure that your information is properly protected.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Fraud Prevention and Screening</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>In order to combat credit and debit card (payment card) fraud, MU uses 3rd Man Limited to provide payment card fraud screening services.

In order to do this, MU provide 3rd Man with details of all transactions where made using a payment card.  This information includes:

- name, address and contact details of the purchaser;
- details of products/services purchased; and
- financial/payment details (including credit card details).

3rd Man will then analyse and (if applicable) match this data with details of other transactions provided to it by other retailers/service providers in order to assess if there is a fraud risk associated with the purchase.  On completion of this analysis, 3rd Man will provide MU with a risk assessment for that particular purchase and we may cancel any transaction if we reasonably consider that it presents a fraud risk to MU.  In such circumstances, MU will act in good faith in attempting to contact any purchaser of goods or services to allow them the opportunity to pay using cleared funds.

If you have any further queries as to the details of this service, please contact us at the address set out below.

Please note that while the information disclosed to 3rd Man and the results of any assessment will not be directly disclosed to any other third party, they may be used by 3rd Man to make risk assessments on behalf of other customers.

Where we do provide 3rd Man with this information we will ensure that your information is properly protected.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>MU commercial partner programme</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Manchester United teams up with a selection of carefully chosen commercial partners, an up-to-date list of our partners is available by clicking here or from the address below.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Offers and opportunities</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Our commercial partner programme is designed to support the Club and also to bring customers, fans and website users a diverse range of MU associated and MU branded offers (such as MU Finance offers) at competitive prices. MU and/or these commercial partners would like to contact you to tell you more about the offers available to you and about a range of other MU initiatives in a number of ways, including by post, telephone, text/picture/video message, digital television, fax or by email. If you express an interest in an offer from one of our commercial partners, that partner may let us know. This enables us to take your views and interests into account when choosing our commercial partners and developing the programme.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>What to do if you do not want to receive details of offers</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Please be assured, you are under no obligation to buy anything or to participate in any MU initiatives, however, if you prefer not to be contacted either by us or any of our commercial partners, you can opt out by clicking the relevant boxes on the screen upon which you provide information or by writing to us by mail or email (see the section "How to contact us" below). You can change your mind at any time.

Please note, if you do opt out of receiving information, we and/or our commercial partners will be unable to keep you informed of new services, products, events or special offers that may interest you and our ability to inform you of ticketing opportunities may be affected.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Use of your information outside the European Union</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Some of the organisations to which we may disclose your personal information are situated outside of the European Union. In order to provide you with the products and services you require, we may need to transfer your personal information to these countries some of which do not have laws that protect privacy rights as extensively as in the United Kingdom. If we do transfer your personal information to other territories, we will take proper steps to ensure that your information is protected in accordance with this privacy policy.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Cookies</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>In common with many other website operators, we may use standard technology called 'cookies' on this site. Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive and they are used to record how you navigate this website on each visit.

For further, more detailed information on how we use cookies, please refer to our Cookie Policy.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Security of information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We take the security of your personal information seriously. When you submit your credit card details to us, we use industry standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption technology to guard your information. In addition, we have security procedures in place to protect our paper based systems and computerised databases from loss and misuse, and only allow access to them when it is absolutely necessary to do so, and then under strict guidelines as to what use may be made of the personal information contained within them.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Monitoring</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We may monitor or record telephone calls for security purposes and to improve the quality of services that we provide to you.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Changes to this privacy policy</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We aim to meet high standards and our policies and procedures are, therefore, constantly under review. From time to time we may change our security and privacy policies. Accordingly we recommend that you check this page periodically in order to review our current policies.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Updating and correcting information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>You may correct your personal information by emailing us at privacy@manutd.co.uk or by changing your profile on our website. Please include your name, address and/or email address when you contact us as this helps us to ensure that we accept amendments only from the correct person. We encourage you to promptly update your personal information if it changes.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Your rights to access your personal information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>You have the right to receive a copy of the personal information that we hold about you. We may charge a small fee towards the cost of administering any request you make. The current fee is £10.00.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>How to contact us</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Telephone  +44 (0) 161-868-8000
Email privacy@manutd.co.uk
Mail Data Protection Officer, Manchester United Limited, Sir Matt Busby Way, Old Trafford, Manchester, M16 0RA
Fax +44 (0) 161-868-8818</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
