<POLICY modification_date="" policy_url="http://www.score.org/about/policy" website_category="Health" website_index="061" website_url="score.org">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>SCORE WEBSITE POLICY</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>SCORE Association (together with its affiliated entities, “we”, “us”, etc.) know that visitors to and user (“you”, “your”) of score.org(“Website” or “Site”) care about how information about them is used and shared.  So we created this privacy and use policy (“Policy”) to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy.  Please note that if you use the Site, it means you consent and accept the terms in this Policy.

We may update our Policy periodically to reflect new uses, rules, regulations or technologies that impact your privacy.  If there are changes or additions to this Policy, we will post those changes here or in other formats for you to review.  Changes to this Policy will apply to the information collected from the date we post the revised Policy as well as to existing information held by us.  If we change our information practices or this Policy in such a way that your personal information may be used or shared in a manner not described in the Policy at the time you provided it, you may provide us notice (at the address below) that you would like to opt-out of having your information used or shared in that new manner.  This Policy will be continuously assessed against new technologies and business practices. We recommend that you review our Policy on a routine basis to view any changes.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Conditions to Use of Website</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Access to SCORE Online Mentoring:You understand that access to our services, including but not limited to online workshops and counseling, are provided as services only to citizens of the United States and its territories.

You understand that when you submit a request to participate in online counseling, and when you participate in online counseling, you are signifying that you agree to the terms and conditions of our counseling outlined as follows:  You request business management counseling from the Small Business Administration (SBA).  You agree to cooperate should you be selected to participate in surveys designed to evaluate SBA assistance services.  You authorize SBA to furnish relevant information to the assigned management mentor(s) although you expect that information to be held in strictest confidence by him/her.  You further understand that any mentor has agreed not to: (1) recommend goods or services from sources in which he/she has an interest and (2) accept fees or commissions developing from this counseling relationship. In consideration of SBA's furnishing management or technical assistance, you waive all claims against SBA personnel, SCORE, Small Business Development Centers and their host organizations, and other SBA resource mentors arising from this assistance.

You understand that our mentors are not providing advice pursuant to the authority of professional certifications or licenses that they may hold and you will not treat information provided by our mentors as such.  You further understand that you are not entering into a relationship with our mentors that entitles you to client privileges that may be associated with any professional certifications or licenses that our mentors may hold.

Cooperative Agreement:  We are funded by the U.S. Small Business Administration (SBA) (Cooperative Agreement No. SBAHQ10-S0001). The support given by SBA to us through such funding does not constitute an express or implied endorsement by SBA of any of our opinions, products, or services.

Local Chapters:  The support given by us to our various local chapters, whether in the form of funding or Web-hosting of local chapter information on its web site, does not constitute an express or implied endorsement by us of any of the opinions, products or services offered by such local chapters.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>General Disclaimer</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We make no warranty, express or implied, nor assumes any legal liability or responsibility for the accuracy, completeness, or usefulness of any information, apparatus, product or process disclosed on the Site, nor represents that its use would not infringe privately owned rights. Reference on the Site to any specific commercial product, process, or service by trade name, trademark, manufacturer, or otherwise, does not necessarily constitute or imply its endorsement, recommendation, or favoring by us. The views and opinions of originators expressed on the Website do not necessarily state or reflect our own views and opinions.

WE TRY TO KEEP THE WEBSITE UP, BUG-FREE, AND SAFE, BUT YOU USE IT AT YOUR OWN RISK. WE ARE PROVIDING THE SITE "AS IS" WITHOUT ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND NON-INFRINGEMENT. WE DO NOT GUARANTEE THAT THE SITE WILL BE SAFE OR SECURE. THE WEBSITE IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE ACTIONS, CONTENT, INFORMATION, OR DATA OF THIRD PARTIES, AND YOU RELEASE US, INCLUDING EACH OF THE ABOVE-NAMED ENTITIES, OUR DIRECTORS, OFFICERS, EMPLOYEES, AND AGENTS FROM ANY CLAIMS AND DAMAGES, KNOWN AND UNKNOWN, ARISING OUT OF OR IN ANY WAY CONNECTED WITH ANY CLAIM YOU HAVE AGAINST ANY SUCH THIRD PARTIES. IF YOU ARE A CALIFORNIA RESIDENT, YOU WAIVE CALIFORNIA CIVIL CODE §1542, WHICH SAYS: "A GENERAL RELEASE DOES NOT EXTEND TO THE RELEASE, WHICH IF KNOWN BY HIM MUST HAVE MATERIALLY AFFECTED HIS SETTLEMENT WITH THE DEBTOR." WE WILL NOT BE LIABLE TO YOU FOR ANY LOST PROFITS OR OTHER CONSEQUENTIAL, SPECIAL, INDIRECT, OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THIS STATEMENT OR THE WEBSITE, EVEN IF WE HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. OUR AGGREGATE LIABILITY ARISING OUT OF THIS STATEMENT OR THE WEBSITE WILL NOT EXCEED THE GREATER OF ONE HUNDRED DOLLARS ($100) OR THE AMOUNT YOU HAVE PAID US IN THE PAST TWELVE MONTHS. APPLICABLE LAW MAY NOT ALLOW THE LIMITATION OR EXCLUSION OF LIABILITY OR INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, SO THE ABOVE LIMITATION OR EXCLUSION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. IN SUCH CASES, OUR LIABILITY WILL BE LIMITED TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW.

Nothing in this Website disclaimer will exclude or limit any warranty implied by law that it would be unlawful to exclude or limit; and nothing in this Website disclaimer will exclude or limit our liability in respect of any fraud or fraudulent misrepresentation on our part; or any matter which it would be illegal or unlawful for the Website to exclude or limit, or to attempt or purport to exclude or limit, its liability.

By using this Website, you agree that the exclusions and limitations of liability set out in this Website disclaimer are reasonable.

If you do not think they are reasonable, you must not use this Website or any of our products or services.

If any provision of this Website disclaimer is, or is found to be, unenforceable under applicable law, that will not affect the enforceability of the other provisions of this Website disclaimer.

Third-Party Links

Third-party Internet sites that can be accessed through this Website by links contain information not under our control. Accordingly, we disclaim any responsibility for the content, products or services of any such third-party websites or any site that links to the Website. We do not necessarily recommend, endorse or approve of the content of or information gathered by any such sites. Such links are provided on this Site solely for your convenience. Your connection to any such linked site is at your own risk.

Furthermore, if you provide any information to third-parties who operate these websites, you may be disclosing personal information and different rules may apply to the collection, use, or disclosure of personal information on these sites.  We encourage you to review third-party websites' policies before revealing any personal information or other sensitive information.  We are not responsible for the privacy practices, terms of use or the content of any third-party websites.

Downloading

You may download content displayed on the Website for personal, non-commercial use. You must maintain all copyright and other proprietary notices on downloaded and/or copied material. You may not distribute, modify, transmit, use or reuse any of the content on the Website for any public or commercial purpose without our written consent or any third party we deem necessary.

Downloading for SCORE Chapters

SCORE chapters may download, duplicate and distribute proprietary Website content to clients, at SCORE-sponsored workshops and seminars. You may not distribute, modify or transmit, use or reuse any of the content on the Website that is authored by a third party without our written consent or any third party we deem necessary.

Information Security

We protect the confidentiality and security of your personal information from loss, misuse, or unauthorized alteration or disclosure by using industry-recognized security safeguards such as firewalls, coupled with carefully developed security procedures. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with applicable law and federal standards.  For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer systems with limited access, which are located in controlled facilities.  We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us by email and you do so at your own risk.

Our Web-based services are password protected and we recommend that you do not share your password with anyone and should be changed frequently. Remember that any information you voluntarily disclose online in any postings, discussions groups or chat rooms may be collected and used by others without your permission. Remember also to sign out of our Web-based services and close your browser window when you have finished your work. This prevents others from accessing your account if you share a computer or use a computer in a public place, such as a library or Internet café.

For Website security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, this Website employs commercial software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage.

Unauthorized attempts to upload information or change information on this Website are strictly prohibited and may be punishable under the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act of 1986 and the National Information Infrastructure Protection Act.

When using our website and creating a username and password, please be aware that information keyed into our website page is not encrypted with SSL encryption technology.  The content within our site is not considered high risk material and is not protected by SSL login technology.  It is recommended you do not use a username and password combination you might use on your personal banking site or other site you consider high risk information.  When you create an account on our site, password information will be sent to you via email.  Our database systems do not store any financial information or social security information on the site.  All of the passwords stored in our database are encrypted.

Regardless of the precautions taken by you or by us, “perfect security” does not exist on the Internet.  While we strive to protect your information by employing reasonable Internet security methods and practices, we cannot ensure the security of any information you transmit to us over an unsecured Internet connection.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Privacy Policy</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Scope:This privacy policy covers all of the Website.  By using or accessing our Website, you agree to our privacy practices outlined.

We value our relationship with you and place the highest importance on respecting and protecting your privacy. We want you to feel comfortable and confident when using our services and with entrusting your personal and company  information to us.

This privacy statement describes what we do with the information that we receive about you when you visit our Website. The information that we receive about you depends on what you do when you visit our Website.

All submitted information is used only for the express purposes for which it is intended, and is not made available to any third party. We only share information you voluntarily provide if required by law. We never collect information or create individual profiles for commercial marketing. However, when you join an online community and participate in online discussions, your name and other personal information you provide (except e-mail) are viewable by anyone visiting, unless you choose not to share this information with the public on your user profile page.

If you request to view a workshop on our Web site:  We receive your name, email address and city and state when you submit your registration. We also receive any other personal information that you provide in the text of your registration.

We use your name and email address to respond to send you additional information about SCORE and other program aspects that may interest you. We use your zip code to identify the general area in which you live so that we can monitor the geographical scope and impact of our services.

If you request online mentoring:  We receive your name, email address and zip code when you submit your request. We also receive any other personal information that you provide in the text of your email request.

We use your name and email address to respond to your request for business counseling. We use your zip code to identify the general area in which you live so that we can monitor the geographical scope and impact of our services and also so that we can provide counseling appropriate for your location. The SCORE mentor that receives your email request will have access to other personal information that you provide in the text of your email request. The SCORE mentor will keep this information confidential but may consult with other SCORE mentors about your situation in order to better serve you.

If you submit a testimonial or success story:  We receive your name, place of business and email address as well as the information that you submit (your testimonial or success story).

At our discretion, we may display on our site your testimonial or success story, including personal information that you provide as part of your testimonial submission.

Information Collected from Interactive Forms: The Website provides interactive forms that let you voluntarily submit personal information (such as your e-mail address, name, or organization).

Use of Personal Information:
We do not sell or rent your personal information to anyone for promotional or marketing purposes.
We do not share your personal information with anyone for their promotional or marketing use without your consent.
We use your personal or financial information to provide you with information and services you request, to tell you about other products and services, and to give you a customized interactive experience as you use our products.
We also use the information for support, to develop new features, and to improve the overall quality of our products and services.
We may also use the information to show you a history of your activity, to provide you with statistics about you or your use of our product or service, or to provide you with a better user experience.
We may summarize information about you, in a way that does not identify you personally, and combine it with other information to understand how our products are used, to deliver products and services and to help us develop new products and services.
We may use service companies to help provide you products and services who are not allowed to use your information for their own purposes.

Children's Privacy:Because we care about the safety and privacy of children online, we comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA). COPPA and its accompanying FTC regulation establish United States federal law that protects the privacy of children using the Internet. We do not knowingly contact or collect personal information from children under 13. We do not intend to solicit information of any kind from children under 13.


It is possible that a child under 13 submits personal information to us or by fraud or deception we may receive information pertaining to children under 13. If we are notified of this, as soon as we verify the information, we will immediately obtain parental consent or otherwise delete the information from our servers.

Technical Information Collected and Stored Automatically:The Website automatically records website usage information that we analyze statistically to track operational problems, to prevent fraud and to improve the effectiveness, security and integrity of the Site. This information does not identify you personally and we do not use this information to track or record information about individuals. For each page that you visit, we collect and store only the following technical information:
Date and time of access
URL address of the Website or webpage visited
Internet domain and IP address from which our Website was accessed
Type of browser and operating system used to access our Site (if provided by the browser)
URL address of the referring page (if provided by the browser)
Completion or success status of the request for a webpage or other on-line item
File size of the webpage visited

This information is only used to help us make the Site more useful for you. With this data, we learn about the number of visitors to our Site and the types of technology our visitors use. We never track or record information about individuals and their visits.

Use of Cookies:  As is standard practice on many websites, the Website uses “cookies” and other technologies to help us understand which parts of our Website are the most popular, where our visitors are going, and how much time they spend there. "Cookies" to enable you to sign in to our services and to help personalize your online experience. It is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a webpage server. Cookies contain information that can later be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to store your preferences and other information on your computer to save you time by eliminating the need to repeatedly enter the same information and to display your personalized content and appropriate advertising on your later visits to these sites.

If you would like to view a video without the use of persistent cookies, a link to download the video file is typically provided just below the video. Or, you can remove or block cookies by changing the settings of your browser. To learn more about how to disable cookies in your browser use the following hyperlink:

http://www.us-cert.gov/reading_room/securing_browser/#how_to_secure

We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as providing customer support, hosting websites, or performing statistical analysis of our services. Those service providers will be permitted to obtain only the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information and are prohibited from using it for any other purpose than for delivering the service to us in accordance with our instructions and policies.

We may access or disclose information about you, including the content of your communications, in order to: (a) comply with the law or respond to lawful requests or legal process; (b) protect our rights or property or our web site users, including the enforcement of our policies governing your use of the services; or (c) act on a good faith belief that such access or disclosure is necessary to protect the personal safety of other Website users or the public.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Copyright</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>You should assume that everything on the Website, including, www.score.org  is copyrighted, unless otherwise noted. All graphics design elements on the site are copyrighted. Use of the graphic design elements is forbidden without our expressed, written permission. We neither warrant nor represent that your use of the content displayed on this Site will not infringe rights of third parties. Any product, service, content, program or technology on this Site may be the subject of intellectual property rights such as, but not limited to, copyright, trademark or patent rights. Any such right that is not expressly given herein is reserved by us. Additional copyrights for the mapping function, online counseling function and other technologies are below.

Images, graphics and photographs on the Site are either the property of, or are used with permission by us. Use of these images by you or other third parties is prohibited unless expressly given through an authorized agreement with us or any third party we deem necessary. Any unauthorized use of these images may violate copyright laws, trademark laws, the laws of privacy and publicity, and other applicable regulations.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Contact</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>If you have any question about  your privacy or use of the Website, please email us at  webmaster@score.org with a complete description and we will try to resolve the issue for you.  You may also use snail-mail at the following addresses:

SCORE Association
1175 Herndon Parkway, Suite 900
Herndon, VA  20170
Phone: 1-800/634-0245 or 703/487-3612
Fax: 703/487-3066



SCORE Association © 1997-2011.  All rights reserved.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
