<POLICY modification_date="" policy_url="http://www.sporcle.com/privacy.php" website_category="Games" website_index="080" website_url="sporcle.com">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>Privacy Policy
Our goal here at Sporcle is to create a fun and interesting experience that entertains as well as educates. You privacy is very important to us. We will do everything we can to meet or exceed your expectations. If you have any questions or concerns, don't hesitate to contact us.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Your info</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>To use the services here at Sporcle, we only require very little information, e.g. an email and a name. We ask for this so you can log back in to your account to make changes. We ask for a unique handle so your friends can know who you are without you having to show your email address. Please don't share your password with others, as this would allow them access to your account.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Cookies (yum</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Sporcle uses cookies to make your experience easier. If you ask us, we keep track of your login information so you don't have to reenter your login information every time you come to the site.
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Advertising</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We use third-party advertising companies (for example Google Adsense) to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Changes</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Sporcle's Privacy Policy is subject to change from time to time. The most up to date version will always be available at http://www.sporcle.com/privacy.php. Your use of this website after any changes constitutes your agreement with this policy.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Contact</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, you can contact us here.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
