<POLICY modification_date="May 01, 2012" policy_url="http://www.newsnow.co.uk/privacy/policy.html" website_category="News" website_index="075" website_url="newsnow.co.uk">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>At NewsNow, we are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

This Privacy Policy relates to our website at www.NewsNow.co.uk and any other websites and online services operated by us (collectively and individually, the "Site"). Where the context allows, references to "NewsNow", "we", "us" or "our" include any of our affiliates.

This Privacy Policy explains how we use any personal information that we may collect about you when you use the Site.

By providing us with any personal information you consent to our processing it in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

If you do not consent to this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site.

Topics

The information we collect from you
Cookies
How we use your personal information
Information sharing
Information security
Managing your personal data
Tracking technology
Other sites
Changes to this Privacy Policy
How to contact us</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>The information we collect from you</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We may collect, store and use personal information when you use the Site. We collect any information your web browser sends us in the normal course of your use of the Site and by using the Site you consent to our processing it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. We may from time to time collect additional personal information (for instance, if you submit an enquiry, register with us or subscribe to a service or mailing list).

If you submit an enquiry, register for a NewsNow account, subscribe to a service (which includes free services, paid-for services and subscribing to one of our mailing lists), we will ask you to provide your name and email address. We may also request other personal information in order to be able to provide specific services or to service your requests, which will be specified at the time you sign up for those services or submit such requests. Personal information is information about you that identifies you personally and is not otherwise publicly available.

When you request a web page or any other content from the Site, it is usual for your web browser software automatically to send us your computer's IP address, software model and version, operating system, screen resolution and (depending on your browser) other details of the specifications of your browser, computer and operating system. Some browsers allow you to control such data. It is not usual for such data to contain your email address or other personal information.

We may retain correspondence with our users by email and post, as well as records of any correspondence by telephone.

We may also record and collect certain anonymous traffic data, such as pages visited, links to and from the Site clicked and services used within the Site. This information is not personal information and generally is not aggregated with personal information. We generally use such traffic data to improve our services to you and to customise and enhance your experience of the Site.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Cookies</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We may transmit cookies to your computer or other device that uniquely identify your NewsNow account or your browser. Cookies are small text files that (depending on your browser settings) are deposited on your computer's hard drive when you visit a site and may be sent back to that site when you visit again. Our use of cookies is governed by our Cookie Policy.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>How we use your personal information</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We may use your personal information as follows:


to provide and customise our services;

if you register/subscribe for any of our services, to process and administer your registration/subscription;

to perform any contract that you may conclude with us;

to perform auditing, research and analysis in order to maintain, protect and improve or develop our services;

to generate aggregate anonymised statistics;

to ensure the technical functioning of our network;

to protect the rights or property of NewsNow or our users; and/or

for any other purposes to which you consent.
We maintain a "no spam" policy. Your email address may be used to send you information and to contact you in relation to NewsNow services and to offer you the opportunity to sign up for new services. Such communications may include advertising or sponsorship elements. Where you have consented to our doing so, we may offer you services from carefully selected third parties.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Information sharing</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We may share your personal information with any of our affiliates, in which case your information will remain subject to this Privacy Policy.

We may engage trusted third parties to process your personal information on our behalf.

We may also use computer systems owned by third parties to provide our services and to process your personal information. In such circumstances your personal information may be transmitted to and from such systems by secure channels. Normally, such computer systems remain under NewsNow's exclusive control and your personal information will not be shared with the third parties owning such systems.

The above third parties do not have any independent right to share your personal information. Where any such third party's systems are not under NewsNow's exclusive control, we will endeavour to ensure that such third party will process your personal information securely, in confidence, and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

We may publish, or share with third parties, aggregated non-personal data, which will not identify you individually. We may also send an anonymised version of your information to third-party advertisers or advertising providers for the purposes of displaying customised advertisements on a NewsNow web page and/or to third-party traffic-analysis providers for the purpose of generating aggregate and anonymised data on which pages users visit and the general characteristics of the computers and networks employed by those users. Your browser may also automatically send certain data to such third parties directly.

If we become involved in any prospective or actual transaction with a third party relating to our company, our business or substantially all our assets, we may share your personal information with such third party. We will endeavour to ensure the confidentiality of any personal information involved in such transaction until (if at all) such personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

We may share your personal information if we believe in good faith that access to or use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary (a) to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) to enforce any contractual rights that we may have in relation to the services we provide to you, (c) to detect, prevent or otherwise deal with fraud, security or technical issues or (d) to protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of NewsNow, our employees or contractors, our business partners, our users or the public ("Necessary Purposes").

Some of our affiliates and/or the above third parties may be based (and/or may use computer systems that are located) in countries outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"), including countries with privacy laws that may be different from (and less protective than) those of EEA countries. We will endeavour to ensure that such persons treat your personal information securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. We may transfer your personal information to such persons who may store and process it.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Information security</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorised access to or unauthorised use, alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorised access to systems where we store personal information.

We restrict access to personal information to our employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. Those persons are bound by confidentiality agreements and will be subject to appropriate sanctions if they fail to comply with those agreements.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Others may intercept the personal information you provide to us, so any such transmission is at your own risk.

The Site is controlled by us from our offices in the United Kingdom. If you choose to visit the Site from outside the United Kingdom, you do so at your own risk, with the understanding that information collected from the Site may be collected, stored and used in a country whose privacy laws may be different from those of your home country.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Managing your personal data</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information that we process is accurate, complete and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary.

When you use our services, we endeavour in good faith to provide you with access to your personal information and, at your request, either to correct such information if it is inaccurate or to delete it (unless we believe in good faith that we reasonably need to retain such information for any of the Necessary Purposes, as defined in the "Information sharing" section above). If such information is to be deleted, please allow three working days for this to take effect.

If you make a request concerning your personal information, we will require you to identify yourself and the information that you wish to access, correct or have removed. We may decline to process requests that are unclear, unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardise the privacy of others or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information contained in back-up records). Where we process such requests, we will perform this service free of charge, except where doing so would require a disproportionate effort.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Tracking technology</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Please note that our business partners or other websites that may be accessible via the Site may use cookies or other tracking technology, over which we have no control. In particular, third parties may use cookies, web beacons and other technologies to collect information as a result of serving advertisements through any services (including, but not limited to, mobile sites, applications and device platforms) that we may own and/or operate. We do collect IP addresses and we may attempt to infer your approximate location from your IP address where (a) providing you with any location-related services, (b) responding to location-related enquiries and/or (c) endeavouring to improve your experience of the Site (such as in trying to provide you with more relevant and useful content, services and/or advertisements). We will not, however, disclose any personally identifying location-based information in relation to advertisements to any third-party advertisers or advertising providers unless we obtain your consent to our doing so.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Other sites</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>NewsNow links to websites or other services owned and/or operated by third parties. We are not responsible and accept no liability for the privacy practices of such websites or other services.

This Privacy Policy applies only to our services.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Changes to this Privacy Policy</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If so, we will post the revised version on the Site. You are encouraged to check the terms of such revised versions. If the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice and/or email notification of the changes. Each version of this Privacy Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date, and we will also keep previous versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review. If you use the Site after the date on which this Privacy Policy has been changed, we will treat such use as your consent to the revised Privacy Policy.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>How to contact us</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our use of your personal information, please contact us here or write to us at:

NewsNow Publishing Limited

The Euston Office

1 Euston Square

40 Melton Street

London

NW1 2FD
United Kingdom</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
