<POLICY modification_date="" policy_url="http://www.xscores.com/privacy.htm" website_category="Sports" website_index="096" website_url="xscores.com">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>Privacy policy





We are committed to protecting your privacy at XScores.com. We will not collect any personal information from you that you do not volunteer, and we are the sole owner of all information collected on this site. We do not sell, share, or rent this information to others in any way that we have not mentioned in this statement.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Cookies</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Like many other Web sites, XScores.com uses cookies to identify visitors. Cookies also help us improve your experience and display more prominently goods and services that might interest you. If you do not have cookies enabled, you may experience problems in accessing all features and information presented at our Web site.

For more information about cookies please visit http://www.aboutcookies.org/.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Third parties</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>XScores.com may provide third parties with aggregate statistics about our visitors, traffic patterns, and related site information. This data reflects site usage patterns gathered during thousands of customer visits to our Web site each month but does not contain behavioral or identifying information about any individual visitor/member, unless that member has given us permission to share that information. We may also provide log files and other databases of user information to third parties for analysis, so we can get a better understanding of traffic through our site and thus improve our content offerings. XScores.com also may use third party companies to provide delivery of e-mail newsletters and other messages over e-mail. XScores.com uses a third-party advertising company to serve ads when you visit our sites. This company may use information about your visits to our and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. In addition, we share web site usage information about visitors to our sites with this company for the purpose of managing and targeting advertisements on our sites.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Security</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We use reasonable precautions to keep the personal information you disclose both in your browsing and your purchases and to only release this information to third parties we believe share our commitment to privacy. However, we are not responsible for any breach of security or for the actions of these parties.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Registration Forms</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Our Web site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name, email, postal address, etc).

Contact information from the registration forms is used only to get in touch with the member when necessary. It is in the members' best interest to submit truthful information, as this is also used to verify the member's right to his or her account and/or services' subscription.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Obtaining your consent</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>By using our Web site, you give XScores.com permission to collect information about the pages served to you as an anonymous user for the purpose of calculating aggregate site statistics. If you register at XScores.com for any of our subscription services, you authorize XScores.com to use information you provide to personalize the information we deliver to you and to use your demographic information when calculating aggregate customer data. XScores.com may occasionally amend this policy. We suggest that you bookmark this page and check to see if it has changed from time to time.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Questions or Concerns</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>If you wish to change any information you have given us, or have any questions on our Privacy Policy, please do not hesitate to Contact Us</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
