<POLICY modification_date="August 28, 2013" policy_url="http://www.medcohealth.com/medco/consumer/useOfInfo.jsp?articleAppId=HelpCenterCB_PrivacyPolicy" website_category="Health" website_index="054" website_url="medcohealth.com">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>This Privacy Promise is provided by your plan sponsor's pharmacy benefit manager or, if not applicable, Express Scripts Holding Company (in either case, "we", "us" or "our") to all visitors ("you" or "your") who use the publicly available pages of the Express-Scripts.com website located at http://www.express-scripts.com/, Registered Members of the Member Website (unless otherwise expressly provided on the Member Website), and those users who have been granted authorized access to non-publicly available portions of the Express-Scripts.com website (individually and collectively, the "Site"). The Site may be accessed via the World Wide Web, mobile device or through a hyperlink embedded in an email or on a website hosted by a third party or one of our affiliated companies.

"Members" (or "Beneficiaries" in the case of the TRICARE program) are individual participants in a prescription drug benefit plan. Individual Members who are at least eighteen years old and who have submitted a completed account registration form on the Site, or have completed the appropriate registration process from their plan sponsor's website, or have completed the registration process via telephone with a customer service representative, or are otherwise qualified as a beneficiary under the TRICARE program are all "Registered Members" (or "Registered Beneficiaries" in the case of the TRICARE program) who will be provided access to the Member Website after completing the registration process.

The "Member Website" is a member-only account portal available through the Site or via mobile access which enables Registered Members to access their personal account information and to use certain other Services offered only to Registered Members.

"Services" include, for example but not limitation, access to the Member's account and the Personal Information and Protected Health Information of the Member and (subject to certain required approvals) of the Member's Covered Household Members.

"Cardholders" (or "Sponsors" in the case of the TRICARE program) are Members of a prescription drug benefit plan who carry the membership under their name for themselves and their Covered Household Members. "Covered Household Members" mean individuals who are covered through the prescription drug benefit plan under the Member's account. "Adult Dependent" means a Covered Household Member who is over the age of eighteen. If your Member Website identifies or contains a hyperlink to a Privacy Promise (or Privacy Policy) that is different from this Privacy Promise, the terms of the Privacy Promise (or Privacy Policy) provided to you as a hyperlink from your Member Website or otherwise set forth in your Member Website is the Privacy Promise (or Privacy Policy) that applies to you until such time as you are otherwise notified. The terms contained in that Privacy Promise (or Privacy Policy) will override any conflicting terms contained in this Privacy Promise.

We are firmly committed to protecting the confidentiality of your Personal Information. The term "Personal Information" means any information which can be used to identify you or any individuals who are your Covered Household Members, including by way of example, but not limitation, name, date of birth, mailing address, phone number, cell phone number, e-mail address, credit card information, and/or Social Security number. "Protected Health Information" means any information related to your and any Covered Household Members' health or medical status, including, by way of example, but not limitation, names of your doctors, health conditions, medicines, and/or prescription information and history. In addition to this Privacy Promise, the version of our "Notice of Privacy Practices" which is applicable to you and made available to you on the Site describes how we may use and disclose your Protected Health Information, and your rights to access and update your Protected Health Information and how to request restrictions on our use and disclosure of your Protected Health Information. To the extent any terms in this Privacy Promise conflict with any terms in the Notice of Privacy Practices, the Notice of Privacy Practices will control and override the terms in this Privacy Promise.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>COLLECTION AND USE OF NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>How We Collect Non-Personal Information

General Tracking Information

When you register and/or visit the public or Member Website portions of the Site, we may collect Non-Personal Information from you. "Non-Personal Information" means a data element or collection of data elements that by itself cannot be associated with a specific individual. Non-Personal Information includes by way of example but not limitation, the Internet browser or computer operating system you are using, your IP address or the automatic tracking of the pages of this Site that you access, and Site data collected on an aggregated, anonymous basis through web server logs and cookie technology (further described below), third-party ad servers, and clear GIFs. Our web server automatically collects this information, including your IP address, when you request pages from our server. We may also collect other information regarding your interactions with the Site.

Cookies

We utilize a standard technology called "cookies" and web server logs to collect information about how our Site is used. A cookie is a very small text file, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. Information gathered through cookies and web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, the time spent at our Site, and the websites visited immediately prior to and after visiting our Site. When you visit the Site, the Site's computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each website can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it. With most Internet browsers, you can erase cookies from your hard drive, block all cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your browser's instructions or online help files to learn more about these functions.

How We Use Non-Personal Information

We use two kinds of cookies - session ID cookies and persistent cookies. Session ID cookies are used to personalize your user experience, to determine ways to improve our Site, Site content, and the Services offered through the Site. These cookies are deleted from your hard drive when you close your browser session. Persistent cookies are used to collect non-personally identifiable information such as Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp and number of clicks.

We use your IP address so that we can send data (such as the web pages you request) to you. We aggregate this data with data on the pages visited by other users to track overall visitor traffic patterns to help us understand how you use the Site and your preferred and most frequently used Site pages and Services, to provide you with better service connections and improved Site use and functionality, and to provide you with information on other services and offers that may be of interest to you. We analyze utilization information in the aggregate to study outcomes, costs, and provider profiles, and to suggest benefit designs for your employer or health plan. These studies generate Aggregate Data (described below) which we may utilize, sell or disclose to other companies or organizations. We will not sell or disclose your Non-Personal Information to other companies or organizations.

We may perform statistical analyses of the traffic patterns, Site usage and behaviors associated with our Site. We may use these analyses to generate Aggregate Data from the original Non-Personal Information. "Aggregate Data" is summary level data, such as the number of users in a specific gender in a specific zip code, who have chosen a specific benefit plan. Aggregate Data does not contain information that can be used to identify or contact you, such as your name, address, telephone number or e-mail address, and does not reflect the original form of the Non-Personal Information collected from you. We may sell or disclose the Aggregate Data to other companies or organizations, and we may engage third parties who operate a Linked Site to collect Non-Personal Information from users of that Linked Site and share that Non-Personal Information with us as part of services provided on our behalf. Linked Site providers will not have the ability to translate the Non-Personal Information they collect for us into Personal Information. Please see our Linking Policy below for more details. In some cases, we may share Non-Personal Information with third parties who provide services to us.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>COLLECTION AND USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION AND HEALTH-RELATED PERSONAL INFORMATION</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>How We Collect Your Personal Information and Protected Health Information

Registration

Registration is optional; however, Registered Members are provided access to the Member Website and to information and online Services not provided on the public website, as well as the ability to login to the Member Website when revisiting the Site. When you register as a Registered Member, the Personal Information required to be submitted is limited to information that is reasonably necessary to allow you access to and use of the Member Website. Once you are a Registered Member, you may be required to provide additional Personal Information and/or Protected Health Information as necessary to effectively use the Services offered through the Member Website. The Personal Information you disclose to us during registration and in connection with the Services is provided strictly on a voluntary basis. We may also collect Non-Personal Information during the registration process as described above. When you become a Registered Member, you may be asked to provide us with the Personal Information and/or Protected Health Information of one or more of your Covered Household Members.

Purchases

In addition to providing Personal Information during the registration process, you may provide us with Personal Information or Protected Health Information on the checkout page of the Site when ordering and paying for products and/or if you choose to purchase products or services using our "e-check" electronic funds transfer program or through an automatic refill option.

Designated Caregiver

Should you choose to assign a Designated Caregiver ("Caregiver") in the "Profile" section of the Member Website, you will be asked to provide Personal Information about this individual. The Personal Information may include the individual's full name, date of birth and gender which will be used by us to properly identify your Caregiver when he or she contacts us on your behalf.

Communications

When you become a Registered Member or Registered Beneficiary, we may communicate with you for a variety of purposes in accordance with your communication preferences. By registering for use of the Member Site, you have authorized us to communicate with you through your provided e-mail address. You may change your designated communication preferences on the communication preferences page of the Member Site. For example, if you do not wish to receive e-mails or certain types of e-mails from us, you may so designate on the communication preferences page. In general, once you have authorized us to utilize a particular manner of communicating with you, we may cease communicating with you through other communication channels.

At times, we may utilize communication channels not designated in your communication preferences, or may contact you regarding a particular issue or through a particular communication channel despite an otherwise stated communication preference. In certain instances, we may communicate with you through a different communication channel, or we may utilize multiple communication channels to reach you. Examples of when we may not be able to fully follow your communication preferences include when required by law, when we are unable to reach you by your preferred communication channel, when you have reached out to us by a particular communication channel and we respond by communicating with you through the same communication channel, or in the case of an emergency or other extenuating circumstance.

You may continue to use all communication channels available to you to reach us regardless of your communication preferences.

How We Use Your Personal Information and Protected Health Information
We will not use or disclose your Personal Information or your Protected Health Information in a manner inconsistent with applicable law, this Privacy Promise or the Notice of Privacy Practices. Examples of our uses and disclosures include:

We will manage your prescription benefits and process your prescription drug claims. This process may involve sharing certain Personal Information and/or Protected Health Information with you and/or your doctor, pharmacist, health plan or plan administrator. These disclosures are made in accordance with the terms of your health plan or prescription benefit plan.
We will process and send you orders you have placed through our pharmacy.
We may send you information or contact you regarding health conditions, medicines, or programs designed to improve your health.
We may send you promotional offers or marketing information that may be of interest to you.
We may use third-party agents for purposes of marketing and transactional communications.

In certain circumstances, we may be legally compelled to release your or your Covered Household Members' Personal Information or Protected Health Information in response to a court order, subpoena, search warrant, law or regulation or the terms of the Notice of Privacy Practices.

Covered Household Members Personal Information and Protected Health Information

Our Member Website may include features through which Registered Members may view their own Protected Health Information (such as their prescription history) and their Personal Information. In addition, Cardholders may use the Member Website to view Protected Health Information and Personal Information of any Covered Household Members under the age of eighteen. When registering to use the Member Website, Adult Dependents have the ability to deny sharing their Protected Health Information or other Personal Information with other Covered Household Members, including Cardholders, spouses, parents or guardians by choosing certain privacy settings at the time of registration and/or adjusting the privacy settings at any time after registration.

Adult Dependents and Cardholders may not access the Protected Health Information or other Personal Information of other Adult Dependents unless the Adult Dependent has approved such access. Express Scripts disclaims all present and future liability for any unauthorized use or access by any Adult Dependent of another Adult Dependent's Personal Information.

How You Can Correct/Update Your Personal Information and/or Protected Health Information

You can correct or update your Personal Information or Protected Health Information at any time using the following options:

Login to the Member Website and update your Personal Information.
Call the Customer Service number on your Member ID card.
Write to:
Express Scripts
Attention: KANA Team
One Express Way, St. Louis, MO 63121

TRANSFER OF PERSONAL INFORMATION, PROTECTED HEALTH INFORMATION AND NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION

All Personal Information, Protected Health Information and Non-Personal Information obtained through our Site is owned by us. Accordingly, if we are acquired, merge with another entity, or we divest one or more of our businesses, affiliates or subsidiary companies, the Sites, and any Personal Information, Protected Health Information and Non-Personal Information obtained through them, may be transferred to an applicable entity for the purposes of continuation of Services, in accordance with applicable law and the Notice of Privacy Practices.

USAGE BY CHILDREN

As stated in the Covered Household Member Information section of this Privacy Promise, our Sites is neither intended for nor designed to attract users who are under the age of 18.

We are committed to preventing the unintentional collection of Personal Information and Protected Health Information from children under the age of 13. Any Personal Information and Protected Health Information of a child under 13 that is provided to us must be provided by the Registered Member, and not by a child under the age of 13 who is using the Site.

If you are the parent or legal guardian of a child under the age of 13 whom you have reason to believe has provided his or her own Personal Information or Protected Health Information to us, you have the right to request the removal of that child's Personal Information and/or Protected Health Information from our database. In order to request such removal, please send an e-mail to privacy@express-scripts.com. You will be required to verify your identity as the child's parent or legal guardian in order to have their Personal Information or Protected Health Information removed.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>LINKING POLICY</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>Our Site may contain hyperlinks allowing our users to connect to websites owned by our third-party vendors, distributors, and providers ("Linked Sites"). You may also access our Site through a hyperlink embedded in a Linked Site. We provide hyperlinks to the Linked Sites as part of the Services to enable you to conveniently access websites that may be of interest to you. Please note that once you click on a hyperlink that transfers you from our Site to a third party's Linked Site, you have left our Site, and this Privacy Promise will immediately cease to apply to any subsequent activity on the Linked Site. We are under no obligation to notify you when you have left our Site and have accessed a Linked Site. Use of any Linked Site will be governed by the privacy policy (if any) on the Linked Site. You may, at your option, participate in surveys or provide other information to our affiliates that control a Linked Site, and that information may be shared with us or with others subject to the privacy policy terms set forth on that Linked Site. Certain Non-Personal Information that you choose to provide through a Linked Site (such as your member ID or comments) that is subsequently provided to us by the Linked Site provider in connection with a service engagement may be identifiable to us as your Personal Information. We will not share any information that we identify as Personal Information with the Linked Site provider.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>SECURITY STATEMENT</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We are committed to protecting the privacy and security of this website across the entire transaction process. We take reasonable technical and procedural precautions to protect the information provided by our members. Our Internet infrastructure is protected using industry recognized commercial security products, including current encryption technology, and best practice procedures for maintenance of the website. In addition, our infrastructure is monitored 24 hours a day, seven days a week.

No method of transmission over the Internet or storage of data on an Internet server is 100% secure. Although we use commercially acceptable and reasonable precautions to protect your Personal Information, we do not guarantee its absolute security.

YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THIS PRIVACY PROMISE

You are deemed to have assented to the terms and conditions contained in this Privacy Promise when you use the Site and/or when you have indicated in your online registration that you accept the Terms of Use into which this Privacy Promise is incorporated. You are deemed to have accepted this Privacy Promise each time you access the Site and/or the Member Website after initial registration by using your personal login and password. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Promise, please do not use the Site. The terms and conditions contained in this Privacy Promise are subject to and may be superseded by applicable Federal and State laws.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>CHANGES IN OUR PRIVACY PROMISE</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>We use Non-Personal Information, Personal Information and Protected Health Information collected from you and from Covered Household Members only within the scope of use described in this Privacy Promise. However, we reserve the right, from time to time in our sole and absolute discretion, to change, modify, to add terms or remove terms from this Privacy Promise without advance notice to you. Changes to this Privacy Promise will be reflected when we post a new version number and updated revision date. Therefore, we recommend that you check the version number and revision date prior to using the Member Website, and that you review this Privacy Promise on a frequent basis. Your continued use of the Member Website after this Privacy Promise has been updated, as shown in the version number and revision date, indicates your agreement and acceptance of this Privacy Promise, including all changes made as of the date of your use of the Member Website.

HOW TO SEND US YOUR COMMENTS

We welcome your comments. If you have general feedback regarding this Privacy Promise, please email us. Upon submission, any suggestions you make regarding the Site become our property, and we shall have the right to use any of your comments or suggestions without further permission from or notice to you.

Specific questions regarding the enforcement of this policy should be directed to privacy@express-scripts.com.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
