<POLICY modification_date="" policy_url="https://www.usbank.com/privacy/index.html" website_category="Business" website_index="073" website_url="usbank.com">
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE />
        <SUBTEXT>Privacy
At U.S. Bancorp®, trust has always been the foundation of our relationship with customers. Because you trust us with your financial and other personal information, we respect your privacy and safeguard your information. In order to preserve that trust, the U.S. Bancorp family of financial service providers pledges to protect your privacy by adhering to the practices described below.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Bank Consumer Privacy Pledge</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>FACTS	WHAT DOES U.S. BANK DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why?	Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What?	The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:

Social Security number and income
account balances and payment history
transaction history and credit history

How?	All financial companies need to share customers' personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers' personal information; the reasons U.S. Bank chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information	Does U.S. Bank share?	Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes — such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus	Yes	No
For our marketing purposes — to offer our products and services to you	Yes	No
For joint marketing with other financial companies	No	We don't share
For our affiliates' everyday business purposes — information about your transactions and experiences	Yes	No
For our affiliates' everyday business purposes — information about your creditworthiness	Yes	Yes
For nonaffiliates to market to you	No*	We don't share

To limit our sharing


Call 800-370-8580 - our menu will prompt you through your choice or
Visit us online: http://www.usbank.com/privacy and tell us your preference on the "Exercise Your Privacy Choice" page.

Please note: If you are a new customer, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we sent this notice. When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice. However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.

To limit our direct marketing


Please note: We may contact our existing customers by mail, telephone, or email to offer additional financial products or services including products and services offered by nonaffiliates that we believe may be of interest to you. You may direct us not to send you such offers.

To limit our direct marketing to you by mail or telephone, please call 800-370-8580--our menu will prompt you through your choices, or visit us online: http://www.usbank.com/privacy and tell us your preference on the "Exercise Your Privacy Choice" page.
To limit our direct marketing to you by email, please visit us online at http://www.usbank.com/privacy and tell us your preference on the "Email Preferences" page

Questions?


Call 800-872-2657 or go to usbank.com

Who we are


Who is providing this notice?


Companies with the U.S. Bank and U.S. Bancorp names and other affiliates. Please see below for a list of other affiliates that do not have a U.S. Bank or U.S. Bancorp name.
What we do
How does U.S. Bank protect my personal information?	To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
How does U.S. Bank collect my personal information?	We collect your personal information, for example, when you

open an account or apply for a loan
use your credit or debit card or make deposits or withdrawals from your account
tell us about your investment or retirement portfolio

We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
Why can't I limit all sharing?	Federal law gives you the right to limit only

sharing for affiliates' everyday business purposes—information about your creditworthiness
affiliates from using your information to market to you
sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you

State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing. See below for more on your rights under state law.
What happens when I limit sharing for an account I hold jointly with someone else?	Your choices will apply individually—unless you tell us otherwise.
Definitions
Affiliates	Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.

Our affiliates include companies with a U.S. Bank and U.S. Bancorp name; financial companies such as
U.S. Bank National Association and U.S. Bancorp Investments, Inc.

Nonaffiliates	Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.

U.S. Bank does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you

Joint marketing	A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.

U.S. Bank doesn't jointly market

Other important information
You may have other privacy protections under applicable state laws. To the extent these state laws apply, we will comply with them when we share information about you.
For California residents: In accordance with California law, we will not share information we collect about you with companies outside of our corporate family, except as permitted by law, including, for example, with your consent or to service your account. We will limit sharing among our companies to the extent required by California law.
For Vermont residents: In accordance with Vermont law, we will not share information we collect about you with companies outside of our corporate family, except as permitted by law, including, for example with your consent or to service your account. We will not share information about your creditworthiness within our corporate family except with your authorization or consent, but we may share information about our transactions or experiences with you within our corporate family without your consent.
For Nevada residents: We may contact our existing customers by telephone to offer additional financial products that we believe may be of interest to you. You have the right to opt out of these calls by adding your name to our internal do-not-call list. To opt out of these calls, or for more information about your opt out rights, please contact our customer service department. You can reach us by calling 800-USBANKS (800-872-2657), clicking the "Email Us" link at usbank.com/privacy, or writing to P.O. Box 64490, St. Paul, MN 55164. You are being provided this notice under Nevada state law. In addition to contacting U.S. Bank, Nevada residents can contact the Nevada Attorney General for more information about your opt out rights by calling 775-684-1100, emailing bcpinfo@ag.state.nv.us, or by writing to:
Office of the Attorney General, Nevada Department of Justice, Bureau of Consumer Protection 100 North Carson Street, Carson City, NV 89701-4717

Additional U.S. Bancorp affiliates


The Miami Valley Insurance Company


Mississippi Valley Company


Elan Life Insurance Company

*Please keep in mind that, as permitted by applicable law, if you have a private label credit card account with us, we share information about you with our financial or retail partners in connection with maintaining and servicing your account, including for that financial or retail partner to market to you. Federal law does not give you the right to limit this sharing.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Exercise Your Privacy Choice</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>To exercise your privacy choice, please fill out and submit the form below. Or, you can call us toll-free at 800-370-8580.
If you have already informed us of your choice, it remains in effect. We will maintain that election even after you close your accounts. You need not tell us again of your choice each year. 1

Bout
Account Login

U.S. Bank Internet Banking
Online Investing

Enroll Today
View All Logins





Please do not share personal credit information about me within the U.S. Bancorp family of financial service providers.

Please do not solicit me for additional products and services through:
telephone marketing, or
direct mail marketing.

All items in bold are required:
Last Name

First Name

Last 4 digits of your Social Security Number

E-Mail Address

Last Name (joint owner) 2

First Name

Last 4 digits of the joint owner Social Security Number

Please complete name and Social Security number if a joint owner wishes to make an election.
Street Address

Apt 

#City 	State

Zip Code  (99999-9999) 	Telephone  (999-999-9999)

1  If you have previously indicated your preference, it remains in effect. You need not restate your choice each year.
2  On joint accounts, you must give us the name and Social Security number of each owner who wishes to make an election.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>More about the U.S. Bank1 Consumer Privacy Pledge</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>U.S. Bank is deeply committed to keeping our customers informed of our policies and practices. In order to continue that commitment, U.S. Bank has adopted a new format for our consumer privacy pledge. This new format is part of an industry-wide initiative geared to better inform our consumer customers on how information about them is collected, shared and protected. It also discusses how consumer customers may, in some instances, limit information sharing.

If you previously informed U.S. Bank of your request to limit our marketing to you and to be excluded from such sharing of information among our affiliates, you need not submit another request.

If you would like to change a preference that you previously made in regard to direct marketing or information sharing, please call 877-449-3593.

Questions About Our Use Of Information2
Why Do You Want to Know About Me?

The information we collect about you provides significant customer benefits. It enables us to understand your financial needs, improve products and services, comply with laws and regulations, provide enhanced customer service, and protect you against fraud.

Protection - We gather information about you to protect you. We need to be able to identify you and your products and services to prevent access to personal and financial information by unauthorized persons.

Customer Benefits - We also gather information to help us understand your financial needs and provide you with quality products and services. For example, if we know you own your own home, we know that a home equity loan may be a better alternative than an installment loan to finance your next purchase - because of better rates and possible tax benefits.

Product Enhancements - In some cases, we gather information to help us design or improve our products and services. For example, information obtained from customers can tell us whether to develop a new type of home mortgage loan or a checking account. This type of information enables us to identify the needs of customers and provide services to meet those needs.

Comply with Law and Regulation - We gather information to comply with laws and regulations that govern the financial services industry. For example, federal regulations require that we obtain a Social Security number or tax identification number for many types of accounts, such as bank deposit accounts that pay interest.
How Do I Benefit When You Share Information About Me and My Products and Services Within Your Affiliated Family of Banks and Companies?

We provide products and services to customers through a number of affiliated banks and companies. Our Consumer Privacy Pledge provides you with a representative list of the U.S. Bank family of financial service providers with whom your information could be shared. By allowing our affiliated banks and companies to share information about you and your products and services with each other, you enable us to serve your total financial needs. You may receive our combined bank/company account statements, easier access to certain account features, new or enhanced products, special promotional offers, and certain discounts that you might not otherwise know about or be eligible to receive.
If I Request to Be Excluded From Information Sharing Among Affiliates as Explained In the Consumer Privacy Pledge, Will All of Your Affiliated Banks and Companies Honor this Request?

Yes, all of our affiliated banks and companies will honor your request. Certain information about you and your products and services with us still may be shared as explained below. You cannot selectively request to be excluded on a company-by-company basis or product-by-product basis. To provide you with better service, if we are unable to offer you the U.S. Bank product you applied for, we may offer you the opportunity to have us forward your application and related information to another U.S. Bank company for a similar product.
If I Request to Be Excluded From Information Sharing Among Your Affiliates, What Information About Me and My Products and Services With You Will and Will Not Be Shared Within Your Family of Banks and Companies?

The Fair Credit Reporting Act and certain other laws permit you to direct us not to share certain information within our affiliated family - but these laws also permit us to share certain other information within our affiliated family. Even if you "request to be excluded from affiliate sharing of information," we will share this other information about you and your products and services within our family in order to provide you the fullest range of financial services, as discussed below.
Fair Credit Reporting Act

The Fair Credit Reporting Act is the primary law that covers information sharing within our affiliated family of banks and companies. This act permits our affiliated banks and companies to share with each other the following types of information: identification information about you; information about your transactions with any of our affiliated banks and companies; and information about the experiences of any of our affiliated banks and companies with you. However information that is categorized as "personal credit information" cannot be shared with our affiliated banks and companies if you tell us not to share this information. Personal credit information is information that bears on your creditworthiness, personal characteristics, mode of living or the like (other than identification, transactional, and experiential information described above). When you request to be excluded from affiliate sharing of information according to the procedures set out in the Consumer Privacy Pledge, we cannot share this personal credit information about you.
Other Restrictive Laws

Other laws and rulings also regulate our ability to share certain information within our affiliated family of banks and companies in particular circumstances, or to offer you products and services in particular cases. Some laws, for example, prohibit us from sharing certain information within our affiliated family of banks and companies without your expressed written or oral consent or, in a few cases, under any circumstances. Whether or not you have exercised your choice and provided us with a request to be excluded from information sharing among our affiliates, we, of course, abide by these laws.
Can You Provide Me with a Few Examples of Information That Still May Be Shared Within Your Affiliated Family of Banks and Companies If I Request to Be Excluded From Information Sharing Among Your Affiliates?

We can share identification information about you, such as your name and address. In most cases, we also can share information about your transactions or experiences with any of our affiliated banks and companies, such as your loan repayment or checking account history, as permitted under the Fair Credit Reporting Act. When we process your accounts, we can share additional information, including personal credit information about you, solely for that purpose. Some of our affiliated banks and companies, for example, share or receive information in order to provide technical or operational support services - such as to prepare your account statements or provide data processing services - for other affiliated banks and companies.
Under What Circumstances Do You Provide Information to Parties Outside Your Affiliated Banks and Companies?

We are committed to protecting our confidential information about you and your products and services with us. However, it is occasionally necessary to provide some of this information to parties outside our affiliated banks and companies. We may also provide certain information to third parties for other purposes as described below.

We are required, for example, to share information about you and your products and services with us with parties named in a lawsuit or administrative action when we are served with a subpoena or court order. We also are required to share this information with federal or state regulatory authorities, such as banking examiners or the Internal Revenue Service, as authorized by federal or state law. Consistent with the practice of other banks and financial service companies, we also share certain information about you and your products and services with us with reputable credit reporting agencies as authorized by federal law and with others who may receive certain information from us under particular circumstances - but only as lawfully permitted or required.

From time to time, we contract with parties outside our affiliated banks and companies in order to offer you certain financial products. For example, we may contract with insurance companies to offer you various insurance products. Under these programs, a limited amount of information about you or your account may be provided to the third party under an agreement requiring the third party to keep the information confidential and not use it for any other purpose. We do not provide account or personal information to non-U.S. Bank companies for the purpose of independent telemarketing or direct mail marketing of any non-financial products or services of those companies.

We also sometimes contract with outside agents or service providers to prepare your account statements, enter or calculate transactions and balances, or provide other materials or services on our behalf. These agents, service providers, and third party product providers agree to safeguard our information about you and your products and services with us, and must abide by applicable law.

We also occasionally decide to sell business assets or a business line. In these cases, we may transfer to the purchaser the related customer information.
Do You Provide Special Treatment of Information That Your Affiliated Trust Company or Bank Holds as My Trustee or Disclosed Fiduciary?

Yes, any information about you within our trust division, along with your trust or agency accounts, is subject to special protection - even within our affiliated family of banks and companies. This information is considered extremely confidential.
Questions About Direct Marketing
Does U.S. Bank Conduct Direct Marketing?

We may contact our existing customers by mail, telephone, or email to offer additional financial products or services that we believe may be of interest to you. In addition, we may from time to time purchase mailing or other lists from outside agencies or companies that are in the business of compiling lists for purchase by others for their independent use. These lists are compiled by such agencies and companies primarily from public sources of information.

The Privacy Pledge provides procedures regarding how you may direct us not to send you such offers.
How Can I Remove My Name From Lists Created by Outside Agencies and Companies That Are in the Business of Compiling Lists for Purchase?

For information on how to remove your name from mail and telephone lists created by outside agencies and companies, contact the organizations below. You must personally register your own name, address and/or telephone number directly with each organization because they cannot process any requests from us.
Direct Mail

To limit the volume of direct mail you receive, contact the Direct Marketing Association:

On-Line: dmachoice.org
By Phone: 212-768-7277

Be sure to include all versions of your name that appear in mailings you receive. The Direct Marketing Association will include your name in its consumer exclusion files so that your name may be removed from lists compiled or maintained by the agencies and companies that are members of that organization. Your name remains in the file for five years.
National Do Not Call Registry

To limit the number of telemarketing calls you receive on your home or mobile phone, go to the National Do Not Call Registry:

On-line: donotcall.gov
By Phone: 1-888-382-1222

The National Do Not Call Registry gives you a choice about whether to receive telemarketing calls at home. Most telemarketers should not call your number once it has been on the registry for 31 days.
Credit Reporting Agencies

If you would like to stop credit reporting agencies from disclosing your information to companies who want to offer you credit or other products, call the following toll-free number and follow the instructions on the recorded message: 888-567-8688.

Questions About Your Credit File
What Is a Credit File Disclosure or a Credit Report?

A credit file disclosure, commonly called a credit report, provides you with all of the information in your credit file maintained by a consumer reporting company that could be provided by the consumer reporting company in a consumer report about you to a third party, such as a lender. A credit file disclosure also includes a record of everyone who has received a consumer report about you from the consumer reporting company within a certain period of time ("inquiries"). The credit file disclosure includes certain information that is not included in a consumer report about you to a third party, such as the inquiries of companies for pre-approved offers of credit or insurance and account reviews, and any medical account information which is suppressed for third party users of consumer reports. You are entitled to receive a disclosure copy of your credit file from a consumer reporting company under Federal law and the laws of various states.
How Can I Request a Free Credit Report?

You are entitled to receive one free credit report every 12 months from each of the nationwide consumer credit reporting companies. This free credit report can be requested by web, phone or by mail. For more information, please go to: annualcreditreport.com. This central site allows you to request a free credit file disclosure, commonly called a credit report, once every 12 months from each of the nationwide consumer credit reporting companies: Equifax, Experian and TransUnion.

It is entirely your choice whether you order all three credit reports at the same time or order one now and others later. The advantage of ordering all three at the same time is that you can compare them. (However, you will not be eligible for another free credit report from the Central Source for 12 months.) On the other hand, the advantage of ordering one now and others later (for example, one credit report every four months) is that you can keep track of any changes or new information that may appear on your credit report. Remember, you are entitled to receive one free credit report through the Central Source every 12 months from each of the nationwide consumer credit reporting companies – Equifax, Experian and TransUnion – so if you order from only one company today you can still order from the other two companies at a later date.
How Do I Place a "Fraud Alert" on My Credit File?

You have the right to ask that nationwide consumer credit reporting companies place "fraud alerts" in your file to let potential creditors and others know that you may be a victim of identity theft. A fraud alert can make it more difficult for someone to get credit in your name because it tells creditors to follow certain procedures to protect you. It also may delay your ability to obtain credit. You may place a fraud alert in your file by calling just one of the three nationwide consumer credit reporting companies. As soon as that agency processes your fraud alert, it will notify the other two, which then also must place fraud alerts in your file.

Equifax: 1-800-525-6285; equifax.com
Experian: 1-888-397-3742; experian.com/fraud
TransUnion: 1-800-680-7289; transunion.com

An initial fraud alert stays in your file for at least 90 days. An extended alert stays in your file for seven years. To place either of these alerts, a consumer credit reporting company will require you to provide appropriate proof of your identity, which may include your Social Security number. If you ask for an extended alert, you will have to provide an identity theft report. An identity theft report includes a copy of a report you have filed with a federal, state, or local law enforcement agency. For more detailed information about the identity theft report, visit ftc.gov.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Online Privacy and Security</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>At U.S. Bancorp (together with the U.S. Bancorp family of financial service providers, “U.S. Bank,” “we,” “us” or “our”), trust has always been the foundation of our relationship with customers. We understand your desire for privacy, and we recognize that you trust us with your personal and financial information. Our Online Privacy Policy is designed to describe our privacy practices and principles in a format that is easy to navigate, read and understand. We pledge to treat your personal information with the utmost care and respect.

Online Privacy Policy

This Online Privacy Policy (the "Policy") describes the treatment of information that is provided or collected through any of our online interfaces to which a copy of the Policy is posted, including www.usbank.com (the "Website"), Applications we have placed on third party sites such as Facebook®, Twitter® and other social media services, and U.S. Bank's mobile applications (the "Applications," and together with the Website, the "Services"). It also explains how we collect, use and share information based on users' interactions with online advertisements, both on the Services and on online interfaces owned by third parties. Note that the Policy does not govern our privacy practices offline or with respect to information that is not provided or collected through the Services.

We pledge to use and share any information that we collect from or about our customers in accordance with the U.S. Bank Consumer Privacy Pledge, which provides choices regarding our sharing and use of information. For additional information on this Policy or our privacy practices generally, please refer to the Frequently Asked Questions (FAQs) portion of the Website or feel free to contact us directly with your questions.

While this Online Privacy Policy describes how we treat information, please be aware that additional terms and conditions may apply for certain parts of our Website and Applications.

1. Types of Information We Collect

We collect two basic types of information through the Services – personal information and anonymous information.

"Personal information" refers to information that identifies (whether directly or indirectly) a particular individual, such as information you provide on our forms, surveys, applications or similar online fields. Examples may include your name, postal address, email address, telephone number, Social Security number, date of birth or account information.

"Anonymous information" means information that does not directly or indirectly identify, and cannot reasonably be used to identify, a particular individual. Examples may include information about your Internet browser, information collected through tracking technologies (see "How We Collect Your Information" for additional information regarding our use of tracking technologies), demographic information that you provide to us (e.g., your household income) and aggregated or de-identified data.

"Location information" means information that may be collected by certain mobile applications that identifies your physical location. This information may be collected from your mobile device's location-aware features when you request certain services that are dependent on your physical location.

2. How We Collect Your Information

We collect personal information from you or about you when you provide this information to us directly. For example, we may obtain personal information when you request information, products or services from us, register on the Website or an Application, respond to surveys, contact customer support or otherwise interact with us.

In addition, we may collect information about your activity on the Services automatically using tracking technologies, such as cookies, Flash cookies and pixel tags. Definitions for the tracking technologies listed, as well as information regarding how to disable them, are available in the Online Tracking and Advertising section of the Policy.

3. How We Use Your Information

We may use information collected through the Services in order to, among other things:

Provide you with, or evaluate your eligibility for, products and services that you request from us
Communicate with you about your accounts or transactions with us
Send you important information regarding the Services, changes to this Policy and/or other similar administrative information
Allow you to participate in surveys, sweepstakes, contests and similar promotions, and to administer such promotions (note that these promotions may contain additional disclosures regarding our collection and/or use of your information)
Consistent with local law, required disclosures, and choices and controls that may be available to you:
Send you offers and promotions for our products and services, or products and services that may be of interest to you;
Personalize content and experiences on the Services;
Verify your identity and/or location (or the identity or location of your authorized representative) for security, fraud prevention and other risk control purposes; and
Provide you with advertising based on your activity on the Services and on third-party websites and applications. For additional information regarding our use of your information for personalization and tracking, please refer to the Online Tracking and Advertising section of the Policy.
Optimize or improve our products and services
Detect, investigate and prevent activities that may violate our policies or be illegal
Comply with our legal and regulatory obligations

4. How We Share Your Information

We will not share your personal information outside the U.S. Bancorp family of financial service providers, except under limited circumstances. Please refer to the U.S. Bank Consumer Privacy Pledge for additional information regarding how we may share personal information, as well as the choices you may be able to exercise in connection with such sharing.

5. Online Tracking and Advertising

We and certain trusted service providers operating on our behalf collect information about your activity on the Services using tracking technologies, including:

Cookies:

Cookies are pieces of information that are stored directly on the device that you are using. They allow us to collect information such as the type of browser you are using, the amount of time you spend using the Services, the websites or applications you visit and the preferences you have set up for your accounts. We use this information to personalize your experience, enhance security, facilitate navigation, display material more efficiently and recognize the device that you are using to access the Services. The Services do not use cookies that capture unencrypted personal information about you.

You can choose to have your device refuse to accept any cookies, and the majority of devices and browsers offer additional privacy settings for cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Each device and each browser is a little different, so look at your device Settings or your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you will not have access to many features that make your user experience more efficient and some of the Services will not function properly. Please note that you will need to manage your cookie settings for each device and browser that you use.
Flash cookies.

We may use local shared objects, sometimes known as Flash cookies, to store your preferences and to assist with online authentication by allowing us to recognize you and your device when you return to the Website or an Application. This permits us to display content based upon what you view on our websites and applications to personalize your use of the Services. Our advertisers and third-party service providers also may use Flash cookies to collect and store information. Flash cookies are different from browser cookies because of the amount and type of data, as well as how data is stored.

Cookie management tools provided by your device or browser will not remove Flash cookies. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies, please click here. If you disable Flash cookies, you will not have access to many features that make your user experience more efficient and some of the Services are unlikely to function properly.
Pixel tags, web beacons, clear GIF's and other similar technologies. These are typically small pieces of data that are embedded in images on the Website, our Applications or certain e-mail communications. They may involve the transmission of information directly to us, to another party on our behalf or to another party in accordance with its privacy policy. We may use these technologies to bring together information we collect about you.

Location tracking on mobile devices. Certain applications on mobile devices may transmit information to us about your location when you request information from them. An example includes your physical location when you search for a nearby ATM using your mobile device. We may use that information to improve the products and services we provide to you as well as improving our services generally in your area.

Information collected through tracking technologies is used for many purposes including, for example, to:

Provide useful features to simplify your experience when you return to the Services
Deliver relevant content based on your preferences, usage patterns and location
Monitor and evaluate the use and operation of the Services
Analyze traffic on the Services and on websites or mobile applications of third parties

We may associate this tracking data with your registration information, in which case we will treat it as personal information. Service providers that collect tracking data on our behalf may provide an opportunity for you to choose not to be tracked online.

Occasionally, you may encounter banner advertisements for our products and services on third-party websites and mobile applications. We use third-party advertising service providers to distribute our advertisements on websites and mobile applications where we have paid to advertise. These advertisements may use tracking technologies to capture information such as IP address, browser type and usage information in order to track the effectiveness of our advertising efforts. Such tracking technologies do not capture personal information about you, and our advertising service providers are prohibited from using any information collected except to track advertising effectiveness.

In addition, we use advertising service providers such as Google, Yahoo and MSN to place advertisements for our accounts and services on websites not affiliated with us, and to help us determine which of our advertisements are most likely to be of interest to you using non-personal behavioral information. Advertisements placed by these service providers may use tracking technologies that allow monitoring of your responsiveness to such advertisements. We restrict access and collection of information by advertising service providers for purposes other than assisting us with our advertising efforts.

U.S. Bank participates in the industry Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising managed by the Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA) (www.aboutads.info/choices). As part of this service, U.S. Bank online advertisements are sometimes delivered with icons that help consumers understand how data about them is being used. Clicking on the icon provides options for consumers who want more control and ability to opt out of such behavioral (targeted) advertising. U.S. Bank may use data collected on our website to customize advertisements to you on other sites as you browse the web. You can click on the DAA icon in our targeted advertisements to opt out if you do not want your browsing behavior used for online behavioral advertising purposes. If you prefer not to have non-personal information used for online behavioral advertising purposes, you may also opt-out here. Please note that even if you opt-out, you may still receive online advertising from U.S. Bank. Opting-out from a specific advertising provider means that the ads you do receive will not be based on your preferences or behavior. You may still see targeted pages based on your habits as you navigate www.usbank.com.

In order for behavioral advertising opt-outs to work on your device, your browser must be set to accept cookies. If you delete cookies, buy a new device, access the Services from a different device, log-in under a different screen name or change web browsers, you will need to opt-out again. If your browser has scripting disabled, you do not need to opt-out, as online behavioral advertising technology does not work when scripting is disabled. Please check your browser's security settings to validate whether scripting is active or disabled.

6. Linked Websites

The Services may contain links to third-party websites not controlled by U.S. Bank. We encourage you to be aware when you leave the Services and to read the privacy policies and terms of use of any such websites that may collect your personal information, as they will likely differ from those of the Services. U.S. Bank does not guarantee and is not responsible for the privacy or security of these websites, including the accuracy, completeness or reliability of their information.

7. Data Security and Online Risk-Free Guarantee

Your privacy is very important to U.S. Bank and we are committed to protecting your personal information from unauthorized access or use. We have implemented physical, technical and administrative security measures that comply with federal law and industry standards, including network firewalls, Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption for online sessions, dedicated security teams and secured files and buildings. Please refer to the Frequently Asked Questions portion of the Website for more information regarding data security for the Services.

In addition, U.S. Bank protects customers from liability for unauthorized online transactions with our Online Risk-Free Guarantee. The Online Risk-Free Guarantee applies to unauthorized transfers to or from your consumer accounts (those used for personal, family or household reasons) that are initiated via usbank.com, by using our mobile app, or by using our online bill pay service. It pledges that U.S. Bank will cover 100% of any losses from unauthorized online transactions, so long as they are reported to us promptly. Report to us, within 60 days of the first statement date when the unauthorized transactions appeared, and you will be covered.

You have the responsibility to help us protect your accounts by never revealing your user name or password to other individuals. These protections are subject to certain restrictions, and may not apply to commercial and small business accounts.

8. Preventing Identity Theft

In order to help us protect your personal information, it is important that you always keep your account information safe. Never share your personal ID, password or PIN with anyone, under any circumstances.

Note that U.S. Bank will never initiate a request via email for your sensitive information (e.g., Social Security number, personal ID, password, PIN or account number). If you receive an email asking for your sensitive information, you should be suspicious of the request and promptly contact us to report the suspicious activity.

Please be aware, however, that in certain telephone and in-person transactions we may ask for your full Social Security number, account number or other information to verify your identity before conducting the transactions you have requested. For example, we may ask for such information to verify your identity when you place a call to us, when you visit a U.S. Bank branch office or when we call you about a new product or service we believe that you will find valuable. We will never request that you disclose your personal ID, password or PIN under any circumstances, including such telephone or in-person transactions.

Additional information regarding identity theft and the steps you can take to help protect yourself from fraud can be found on the Federal Trade Commission website.

9. Children's Privacy

We do not use the Services to knowingly solicit data from or market to children under the age of thirteen (13) without parental consent. We request that such individuals do not provide personal information through the Services. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with information without their consent, he or she should promptly contact us and we will delete such information from our files. For additional information regarding the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), please visit the Federal Trade Commission website.

10. External Aggregation Services

Some third-party companies offer aggregation services that allow you to consolidate your financial account information from a variety of sources, such that you can view all your account information at a single online location. For example, an aggregation service might collect and consolidate your checking and savings account balances at your bank, the value of your stocks and bonds in your brokerage account and your frequent flier mileage information from an airline. In order to do so, the aggregator may request access to personal information - including identification information, account information, personal IDs and passwords - from you for each individual website. You must provide your permission and access to your personal information to allow these services to collect this data.

Please use caution when providing personal information to aggregation services. You should always ensure that the aggregator has appropriate policies and practices in place to protect the privacy and security of any personal information to which the company is gaining access. U.S. Bank is not responsible for the use or disclosure of any personal information accessed by a company or an individual to whom you provide the personal ID and password required to access your accounts through the Services.

If you do elect to provide your personal ID, password or other information about your accounts with us to an aggregation service, you will be unable to contest the validity of any U.S. Bank transaction initiated by the aggregator, whether or not you were aware of the specific transaction. Should you decide to revoke the authority you have given to an aggregation service, you may only do so by contacting us, in which case we may need to block your account until we issue new access codes.

11. Social Media Platforms

U.S. Bank may interact with registered users of various social media platforms, including Facebook® and Twitter®. Please note that any content you post to such social media platforms (e.g., pictures, information or opinions), as well as any personal information that you otherwise make available to users (e.g., your profile), is subject to the applicable social media platform's terms of use and privacy policies. We recommend that you review this information carefully in order to better understand your rights and obligations with regard to such content.

12. Updating Your Information

It is very important that you keep the information associated with your account accurate and up-to-date. If you believe that your account information is incomplete, inaccurate or otherwise not current, please contact us and provide us with the appropriate information. Alternatively, you may call or write to us at the telephone numbers or appropriate address for changes listed on your account statements, records, online or other account materials.

13. Changes to the Online Privacy Policy

From time to time, we may make changes to this Policy in order to accommodate new technologies, industry practices, regulatory requirements or for other purposes. We encourage you to review the Policy periodically to ensure that you understand how we collect, use and share information through the Services. If we do make changes to the Policy, we will also update the "Effective Date" posted at the top of the Policy.

Any changes to the Policy will become effective when the revised Policy is posted on the Website, relevant Application or other U.S. Bank online interface, as applicable. By continuing to use the Services following such changes, you are agreeing to accept the terms of the revised Policy.

14. Contact Us

If you have any questions or comments about this Policy or our privacy practices generally, we encourage you to contact our customer service department by completing our online email form or by calling 800-USBANKS (872-2657). Alternatively, you may use any of the local telephone numbers for your area that are listed in the "Contact Us" section of the Customer Service portion of the Website.

In the event you notice suspicious activity on your account or believe your personal ID, password or PIN has been compromised, please contact us immediately. Suspicious emails may be forwarded to fraud_help@usbank.com or you can call our Fraud Liaison Center at 877-595-6256.

Consumer Online Privacy Frequently Asked Questions

Consumer Online Privacy
Frequently Asked Questions</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Consumer Online Privacy Frequently Asked Questions</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>What does U.S. Bank do to keep my accounts secure?
What can I do to keep my accounts secure?
How can I learn more about preventing fraud online?
What tracking technologies does U.S. Bank use?
Why does U.S. Bank use tracking technologies?
How do I contact U.S. Bank Online Banking Customer Service by phone?
How do I contact U.S. Bank Online Banking Customer Service by email?
What if I forget my Personal ID, Password, or ID Shield answers for U.S. Bank Online Banking?

What does U.S. Bank do to keep my accounts secure?

At U.S. Bank, we understand that security is very important to our internet banking customers. We are committed to protecting your personal information from unauthorized access or use. We have implemented physical, technical and administrative security measures that comply with federal law and industry standards, including network firewalls, Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption for online sessions, dedicated security teams and secured files and buildings.

Return to Top
What can I do to keep my accounts secure?

In order to help us protect your personal information, it is important that you always keep your account information safe. Never share your personal ID, password or PIN with anyone, under any circumstances.

You can also help keep your financial information secure by choosing a password that would be difficult for someone else to guess, preferably a combination of letters and numbers that are not related to your job or personal life. Do not write your password down or leave it in a place where it might be discovered. We also recommend that you change you password regularly.

If you have reason to believe your password may have been discovered, immediately change your password. To change your Internet Banking Password log into your account at U.S. Bank Internet Banking. Next select "Security Center” on the left side of the screen and select “View or Change Security Options.”

Return to Top
How can I learn more about preventing fraud online?

U.S. Bank captures each login to U.S. Bank Online Banking. After logging in to your internet banking account look at the top of your account summary page to view the last date your accounts were accessed.

U.S. Bank will never initiate a request via email for your sensitive information (e.g., Social Security number, personal ID, password, PIN or account number). If you receive an email asking for your sensitive information, you should be suspicious of the request and promptly contact us immediately.

To learn more about additional steps you can take to help protect yourself from fraud, visit the Federal Trade Commission website.

Return to Top
What tracking technologies does U.S. Bank use?

Cookies: Cookies are pieces of information that are stored directly on the device that you are using. They allow us to collect information such as the type of browser you are using, the amount of time you spend on our websites or applications and the preferences you have set up for your accounts. We use this information to personalize your experience, enhance security, facilitate navigation, display material more efficiently and recognize the device that you are using to access the Services. These cookies do not capture unencrypted personal information about you.

You can choose to have your device refuse to accept any cookies, and the majority of devices and browsers offer additional privacy settings for cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Each device and each browser is a little different, so look at your device Settings or your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you will not have access to many features that make your user experience more efficient and some parts of our website will not function properly. Please note that you will need to manage your cookie settings for each device and browser that you use.

Flash Cookies: We may use local shared objects, sometimes known as Flash cookies, to store your preferences and to assist with online authentication by allowing us to recognize you and your device when you return to the Website or an Application. This permits us to display content based upon what you view on our websites and applications to personalize your use of the Services. Our advertisers and third-party service providers also may use Flash cookies to collect and store information. Flash cookies are different from browser cookies because of the amount and type of data, as well as how data is stored.

Cookie management tools provided by your device or browser will not remove Flash cookies. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies, please click here. If you disable Flash cookies, you will not have access to many features that make your user experience more efficient and some of the Services are unlikely to function properly.

Pixel tags, web beacons, clear GIF's and other similar technologies: These are typically small pieces of data that are embedded in images on the Website, our Applications or certain e-mail communications. They may involve the transmission of information directly to us, to another party on our behalf or to another party in accordance with its privacy policy. We may use these technologies to bring together information we collect about you

Location tracking on mobile devices: Certain applications on mobile devices may transmit information to us about your location when you request information from them. An example includes your physical location when you search for a nearby ATM using your mobile device. We may use that information to improve the products and services we provide to you as well as improving our services generally in your area

Return to Top
Why does U.S. Bank use tracking technologies?

Information collected through tracking technologies is used for many purposes including, for example, to:

Provide useful features to simplify your experience when you return to our website
Deliver relevant content based on your preferences, usage patterns and location
Monitor and evaluate the use and operation of our website
Analyze traffic on the Services and on websites or mobile applications of third parties

We may associate this tracking data with your registration information, in which case we will treat it as personal information. Service providers that collect tracking data on our behalf may provide an opportunity for you to choose not to be tracked online.

Return to Top
How do I contact U.S. Bank Online Banking Customer Service by phone?

Call the appropriate number listed below and listen for the voice prompt for online Customer Service.

Cincinnati Metro
513-632-4141
Denver Metro
303-585-8585
Minneapolis / St. Paul Metro
612-US BANKS (612-872-2657)
Milwaukee Metro
414-765-4636
Portland Metro
503-US BANKS (503-872-2657)
St. Louis Metro
314-425-2000
All Other Locations
800-US BANKS (800-872-2657)
TDD - All Locations
800-685-5065

Return to Top
How do I contact U.S. Bank Online Banking Customer Service by email?

For more information regarding our online privacy practices, email us at 1800usbanks@usbank.com.

Return to Top
What if I forget my Personal ID, Password, or ID Shield answers for U.S. Bank Online Banking?

If you forget your Personal ID, Password, or ID Shield answers, use the Login Assistance tool available in the Log In section on usbank.com.</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
    <SECTION>
        <SUBTITLE>Bank Email Preferences</SUBTITLE>
        <SUBTEXT>To begin updating your marketing email preferences, please enter your email address in the fields below then select "Next". Marketing emails are newsletters and special offers for U.S. Bank products and services.

Enter your email address:


Re-enter your email address:
Next
You can also update your preferences for other U.S. Bancorp affiliate publications. Simply select one of the links below.
U.S. Bancorp Financial News and Alerts
1-2-3 REWARDS® Visa® Card Email
Ace Rewards Visa® Card Email
AeroMexico Visa® Card Email
Caché® Visa® Email
Club CarlsonSM Visa® Card Email
Fred Meyer Rewards® Visa® Card Email
Gymboree® Visa® Email
Harley Davidson® Visa® Email
LANPASS Visa® Card Email
LifeMiles Visa® Card Email
Polaris® Visa® Card Email
Ralphs rewards plus Visa® Card Email
REI Visa® Email
SKYPASS Visa® Email</SUBTEXT>
    </SECTION>
</POLICY>
